<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jaina on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/jaina/</link><description>Recent content in Jaina on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/jaina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Proudmoore “Problem”</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</guid><description>A lot of people think Jaina has this terrible reputation regarding the men in her life, that she has “terrible taste in men”, or that she breaks guys’ hearts and/or makes them go crazy. This is utter nonsense. The problem isn’t with Jaina, the problem is that the men in her life are just plain jerks.
Have you actually LISTENED to the crap these guys say? It’s pretty sad when Garrosh of all people has treated her with more dignity and respect than her so-called close friends.</description></item><item><title>He Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</guid><description>Hey, he IS a Prophet, after all. Also, I just need to point this out while Rades is gone: Orcs are currently on the very naughty list.
But the idea of Velen as Greatfather Winter and the faction leaders as little kids was actually all Rades’, so you can’t accuse me of bias in this case. We agreed that it even makes sense, when you think about it – to a draenei who is thousands of years old maybe the rest of us would seem like children.</description></item><item><title>Never Trust A Mage</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 11:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</guid><description>You know, dealing with mages was hard enough before Mists, when they’d just portal-troll you by sending you to inconvenient, middle-of-nowhere locations.
Or when they’d summon 5-6 portals on top of one another and you’d have to click and see where you’d end up (Portal Roulette).
Or when they’d start casting you a portal, and then “accidentally” just Teleport themselves back to Orgrimmar, leaving the rest of you stuck in some wretched abyssal lair, miles from home.</description></item></channel></rss>