<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thrall on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/thrall/</link><description>Recent content in Thrall on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/thrall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Proudmoore “Problem”</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</guid><description>A lot of people think Jaina has this terrible reputation regarding the men in her life, that she has “terrible taste in men”, or that she breaks guys’ hearts and/or makes them go crazy. This is utter nonsense. The problem isn’t with Jaina, the problem is that the men in her life are just plain jerks.
Have you actually LISTENED to the crap these guys say? It’s pretty sad when Garrosh of all people has treated her with more dignity and respect than her so-called close friends.</description></item><item><title>Not a Chance, Thrall</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-a-chance-thrall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 08:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-a-chance-thrall/</guid><description>Seriously dude, we all know why this is a bad idea.
Speaking of orc babies, Vid brought up an interesting question while doing the art – what color skin would the baby of a green-skinned orc and a brown-skinned orc have? We settled on sort of an olive complexion, but only time will tell!
As for Thrall and Aggra’s kid? It’d be nice if it were a girl orc, who goes on to accomplish great things.</description></item><item><title>Seriously, Just Buy One Already</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/seriously-just-buy-one-already/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 09:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/seriously-just-buy-one-already/</guid><description>More like “Hour of Waiting For Thrall To Run The Entire Stupid Way in Ghost Wolf Form”, right?
Anyway, we never DO find out what happens to Thrall’s horse in Escape from Durnholde. Everyone else in Old Hillsbrad seemed destined for big things – Kel’Thuzad, Herod, Thrall himself, Old Blanchy – so wouldn’t it be funny if the horse also had some great destiny?
And when you think “when in history would a SURPRISE HORSE be absolutely perfect?</description></item><item><title>Thrall, Aspect of Derp</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/thrall-aspect-of-derp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 11:04:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/thrall-aspect-of-derp/</guid><description>In the final fight of Dragon Soul, players have to fight Deathwing while leaping back and forth between a few different islands, carried by Thrall’s winds.
Unfortunately, Thrall has some…issues…and will occasionally NOT give a player the wind buff, which sends them plummeting to their death in the churning Maelstrom below. This usually results in much anger and frustration, and usually a wipe.
Is he just trolling us? Or is he just really, really incompetent?</description></item></channel></rss>