<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>warriors on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/warriors/</link><description>Recent content in warriors on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:05:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/warriors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There Will Be Blood</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</guid><description>From a recent Mists beta build: Glyph of Gushing Wound.
WTF is it with WARRIOR glyphs in Mists? Cripes. Lighting themselves on fire, lightning strikes, flocks of crows, and now MORE BLOOD? Blizz is sure giving them some pretty fun cosmetic options!
Also, these might seriously be my favorite type of strip. I don’t know if Vid was quite as big a fan of this particular one though.
July 24</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 09:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</guid><description>HEY MURADIN PUT A BIRD ON IT
Like we said last week…Warrior glyphs in Mists = THE COOLEST.
Some news about the next few weeks! This weekend, we’ll be attending a Comic Expo in Calgary! Excitement! Our strip next week will be something based off the Expo, we hope. Then, the week after that we plan on presenting the special guest strip for Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt! So keep your eyes peeled!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</guid><description>A Glyph that causes a lightning strike?
…I have a sudden urge to play a warrior in Mists.
Seriously though, it’s terrific that Blizzard is giving us all these new fun cosmetic glyphs. They’re little touches, but damn are they cool.
My personal favorite so far? That would be Glyph of the Geist. BECAUSE GEISTS ARE AWESOME.
(In other news, I think Vid is going to revolt if I make her draw Garrosh again.</description></item></channel></rss>