<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Voss on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/voss/</link><description>Recent content in Voss on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:14:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/voss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Double Digits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</guid><description>I imagine tanks everywhere are shaking their heads in grim recognition of this scene. After all, how many times have they turned, scanning for the next pack of mobs to pull, only to hear that dreaded “FWOOSH” sound as an enormous ball of fire hurtles past them? Because EVERYONE KNOWS you can’t just WASTE A HOT STREAK PROC.
MAGES.
However, Vid’s lightning-fast DPS instincts served her well when it came to get Blizzcon tickets, netting her an unbelievably low 33rd in queue!</description></item><item><title>Straight Outta Halfhill</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/straight-outta-halfhill/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 12:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/straight-outta-halfhill/</guid><description>VEGGIE. BLING.
The best part about this comic is how utterly unfamiliar both Vid and myself are with these themes. We’re about as un-thug-life as you can get.
Anyway…so uh, yeah. About those farms.
We can’t be the only ones making MAD BANK off our daily produce harvests, right? It’s absurd how much these pumpkins, turnips and melons are going for! I mean, I want to level my Way cooking skills, but how can I use these priceless items for lowly FOOD when they could be netting me hundreds of pure, organically-grown profit every day?</description></item><item><title>Rage of the Friendlands</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 07:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</guid><description>While folks were helping me out to get my legendary, it occurred to me that I wanted to do something to thank them. You know, apart from just – thanking them. Initially I was going to do little character portraits for everyone, but as the list of people who were involved grew, I started to understand that might be a bit unwieldy.
So instead, Rades and I put our heads together and came up with the idea of a strip featuring all the people.</description></item></channel></rss>