<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heart of the Storm on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/</link><description>Recent content in Heart of the Storm on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 01:40:06 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekly Update VI - Happy birthday, buddy</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/what-is-this/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 22:55:27 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/what-is-this/</guid><description>New in this update Tags and Related Comics: Code to display these, and proper tagging and related comic links starting from the beginning up until the sequential storyline (I.E. everything that had tags and related comics in the first place). Next Up Search bar: Vid had mentioned wanting a search bar for the comic and that sounds like a great idea. I think this involves retrofitting the comics that don&amp;rsquo;t have tags, with tags.</description></item><item><title>And We Walked Out Once More Beneath the Stars, II</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/and-we-walked-out-once-more-beneath-the-stars-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 09:54:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/and-we-walked-out-once-more-beneath-the-stars-ii/</guid><description>Five years ago today, FDWL ended its run. This feels fitting in a way, because the comic also ran for five years. If things had been different, maybe Mike and I wouldn’t even have remembered this milestone. Or we would’ve and said, “Hey, isn’t that neat.” Neither of us played World of Warcraft anymore, and this project had been largely lost because the original website was hacked and after a few years of not fixing it, I finally let the domain name lapse.</description></item><item><title>Reflections, Part Four</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-four/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 09:57:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-four/</guid><description>Five years ago, I thought of a joke that made me laugh. I turned the joke into a single comic featuring my character Vidyala and the character of my friend Rades (aka Mike). I sent it to him to see if he thought it was funny, and whether he might like to do more comics with me. After a lot of brainstorming (especially to come up with the name), From Draenor With Love was born.</description></item><item><title>Reflections, Part Three</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-three/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 10:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-three/</guid><description>And now, Four and Wrathion’s epilogues. We thought about it long and hard, and we really felt Four deserved a happy ending, living happily ever after in Ogri’la.
Wrathion, on the other hand…well, he’s got some thinking to do.
From Draenor With Love wraps up next week, see you then!</description></item><item><title>Reflections, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 09:47:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-two/</guid><description>Part 2 of our 4-part epilogue!
Bonus points if you recognize Rades’ gift in the first panel. 😉</description></item><item><title>Reflections, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reflections-part-one/</guid><description>Bet you didn’t expect to see Garrosh’s ugly mug again, huh? You didn’t think I’d wrap up our story without making Vid draw her favorite orc one last time, did you??
If you don’t remember what Taran Zhu is referring to, it goes all the way back to the Patch 5.4: Siege of Orgrimmar trailer. Remember, the events of FDWL started when Siege of Orgrimmar began. And now, we examine the aftermath — of both stories.</description></item><item><title>And We Walked Out Once More Beneath the Stars</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/and-we-walked-out-once-more-beneath-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 09:57:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/and-we-walked-out-once-more-beneath-the-stars/</guid><description>Almost exactly three years ago, we published the first page of our revamped From Draenor With Love. That was so long ago. That was before Warlords of Draenor was even announced! It’s kind of surreal to even think about.
And now, 128 pages later, we’re drawing to a close.
When we set out on this journey, we wanted to explore some themes that we both hold close to our hearts: friendship and family.</description></item><item><title>Under the Mid-Point of That Other Sky</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/under-the-mid-point-of-that-other-sky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/under-the-mid-point-of-that-other-sky/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Whose Shadow a Single Blow Pierced with Light</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whose-shadow-a-single-blow-pierced-with-light/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whose-shadow-a-single-blow-pierced-with-light/</guid><description>We’re a week into Legion, and all around me my guildies are talking about Suramar dailies, weird squid world bosses, reputation grinds, and other max-level concerns. Me, I’m still only level 107, so I’m just ignoring it all for now! Amusingly, somehow I’ve reached 107 and finished only a single zone, Stormheim. Not via dungeon grinding, either! Just a lot of…meandering about, doing Darkmoon Faire quests, some pet battles, some Archaeology…everything but powerleveling, really.</description></item><item><title>The Ravening Beast</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ravening-beast/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ravening-beast/</guid><description>So how was everyone’s Legion launch experience? Me, I got myself trapped in the underbelly of an Alliance airship with no way out except for hurling myself out the open hatch to the sea below. Then I abandoned the breadcrumb quest into Stormheim to redo it and take more screenshots, but instead ended up stranded out there with no quests available. Then I hearthed back to Dalaran and broke my Tailoring profession quest by doing exactly the same thing.</description></item><item><title>Alone in a Dark Wood</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/alone-in-a-dark-wood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/alone-in-a-dark-wood/</guid><description>Hey, nice job Kynrind on predicting the return of Vid’s symbol in the comments last week! 😀
Yesterday was an interesting one in Azeroth — Dalaran was completely missing! And even worse, if you had logged out there, when you logged in you fell to your death!
Naturally, I had to do up a little bonus comic commemorating this bizarre moment (based on Kate Beaton’s original comic here.)</description></item><item><title>End of the Road, Part Six</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-six/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-six/</guid><description/></item><item><title>End of the Road, Part Five</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-five/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-five/</guid><description>WRATHION NO
So how about those Broken Shore and Demon Hunter cinematics?? Man, I sure wish we could get the cinematic team to do a FDWL version. 😉</description></item><item><title>End of the Road, Part Four</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-four/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 09:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-four/</guid><description/></item><item><title>End of the Road, Part Three</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-three/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-three/</guid><description>Can you really blame Wrathion? It’s not every day you see a fight like this. /popcorn</description></item><item><title>End of the Road, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-two/</guid><description>cue Pacific Rim music
Like it says, Page 5! A reveal 114 strips pages and almost 3 years in the making. Feels good, man.</description></item><item><title>End of the Road, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 10:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/end-of-the-road-part-one/</guid><description>SUSPENSE</description></item><item><title>Vacation Vid</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/vacation-vid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 10:25:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/vacation-vid/</guid><description>I’m sorry there’s no “regular” comic this Wednesday! We did our best to get a bunch of them done but the last few pages have been complicated and we’re only human, and I was going on vacation. Please accept this sketch doodle of vacation mode Vidyala instead. It’s much more pleasant than the current FDWL reality. We’ll be back with our regular updates next week!</description></item><item><title>Power Overwhelming</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/power-overwhelming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/power-overwhelming/</guid><description/></item><item><title>BRB</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/brb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 09:40:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/brb/</guid><description>I think Wrathion is my favorite character to write, especially because it’s so easy to imagine his voice saying the lines, since we heard him so much during Mists of Pandaria. Of course, it helps that his voice actor Aaron Phillips does hilarious things like read out fake Guy Fieri menus.</description></item><item><title>All Downhill From Here</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/all-downhill-from-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/all-downhill-from-here/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Full Circle</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/full-circle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/full-circle/</guid><description>Back to Pandaria. Back to the Vale. It’s been a long road, but we’ve finally come full circle.
Big thanks to Poneria for being our latest Patreon patron! We really appreciate the support! 😀</description></item><item><title>Home Is Where the Hearth Is</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/home-is-where-the-hearth-is/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 14:04:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/home-is-where-the-hearth-is/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Blinded By The Light</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blinded-by-the-light/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 11:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blinded-by-the-light/</guid><description>I have fond memories of using Blinding Light in arenas with Arcane Torrent, Rebuke, and Fist of Justice to just shut down enemy healers for an absurd amount of time. No wonder it got nerfed.
Don’t forget to login soon to reclaim your free Warcraft movie transmogs! Even if you don’t plan on seeing the movie, the transmogs look great and should fit in well to anyone’s collection. 😀</description></item><item><title>The Power of Positive Thinking</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-power-of-positive-thinking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-power-of-positive-thinking/</guid><description>Speaking of going back to Pandaria, I too have found myself back in Kun-Lai and Halfhill lately. Since Brawler’s Guild is going away in Legion, I’ve been trying to get all the special quests to unlock the Brawler’s Guild challenge bosses required for Collect Your Deck — partially for the achievement, but also for the shirts you get for beating those bosses. Gotta gear up for the wardrobe!</description></item><item><title>This Is Fine</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/this-is-fine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/this-is-fine/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The FDWL Awakens</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-fdwl-awakens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-fdwl-awakens/</guid><description>Happy Star Wars Day, and May the Fourth be with you!
We don’t normally skip a week for a special page like this, but when we noticed the date coincidence a few weeks back, we just couldn’t pass up the opportunity to have a little fun. And now, after seeing what Vid came up with, I think we definitely made the right call. (Sorry Poe, there just wasn’t room, buddy!)</description></item><item><title>The Stalwart Heart</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-stalwart-heart/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-stalwart-heart/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Something Wicked This Way Comes</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/something-wicked-this-way-comes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 09:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/something-wicked-this-way-comes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Filled With Determination</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/filled-with-determination/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/filled-with-determination/</guid><description>Vid sure has a lot to say this week!
And I think most of us would tend to agree with much of what she’s saying. The Horde and Alliance really DO just keep screwing everything up, and both sides are too damn dumb to cooperate and play nice. After all, From Draenor’s entire whole story is about trying to fix one of our bigger blunders, and restoring the Vale. Sure, Garrosh might have been the one who did the deed, but let’s face it, Pandaria was doing pretty good on the whole “control the Sha by controlling your emotions” thing before we washed up on shore.</description></item><item><title>Overconfident</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/overconfident/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/overconfident/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Happy Noblegarden!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-noblegarden/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-noblegarden/</guid><description>Happy Noblegarden, everyone! If you’re a Mage, make sure you go gather enough chocolate eggs to buy the Tome of Polymorph: Rabbit! 😀</description></item><item><title>Quieter Days</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quieter-days/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quieter-days/</guid><description>I’ve been very sick this past week, so we’re taking a brief pause from the action. In the meantime, readers seemed to really take to the nameless Aldor and Scryer characters on the last few pages! We imagined them as rivals representing opposing factions, sure, but ones where any enmity or opposition had ultimately faded into a comfortably friendly rivalry over the years of defending Shattrath together.</description></item><item><title>Together</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/together/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 10:22:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/together/</guid><description>COOL AS A CUCUMBER</description></item><item><title>That Cold Black Cloud</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/that-cold-black-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 09:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/that-cold-black-cloud/</guid><description/></item><item><title>A Warm Welcome</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-warm-welcome/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-warm-welcome/</guid><description>While this was definitely the appropriate Sha response, I can’t help but be tickled by the mental image of the Sha obediently following Khadgar’s silly arcane elemental all around Shattrath for like ten minutes, only to fail the quest at the very end because the elemental wandered out of sight or moved around a corner. Man, that quest sucks.</description></item><item><title>Colouring Page</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/colouring-page/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 10:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/colouring-page/</guid><description>Hey folks, my apologies. Due to some personal stuff I wasn’t able to get a comic done this week. Please accept instead this colouring page – it’s a slightly edited version of our page 100 comic that you can print out and colour yourself if you’d like! It was originally available only to our patrons. We’ll be back with the regular comic on schedule next week.
(A note from Sean: Though the image appears the same size as any other comic, it is much higher resolution.</description></item><item><title>Destiny, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/destiny-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/destiny-part-2/</guid><description>Well, maybe some things were simply meant to be.</description></item><item><title>Destiny, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/destiny-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/destiny-part-1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ding!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ding/</guid><description>Level (page?) 100! Oh shoot, does this mean it’s time for LFR?
Thanks to everyone who’s been reading FDWL over the years! We really appreciate the support, comments, and company we’ve had along the way! 🙂</description></item><item><title>Urgency</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/urgency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 11:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/urgency/</guid><description>As we all learned in Warlords, operating without flight is a real drag. Too bad they don’t have Avianna’s Feather!</description></item><item><title>Eli’s Coming</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/elis-coming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 10:54:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/elis-coming/</guid><description>(No, the Sha’s name isn’t Eli. It’s a song reference.)
Sorry for the font change for the Sha, but I didn’t realize that the previous font would be…well, completely unsuitable for longer passages of text. I think this new look fits it pretty well, anyway!
The Sha are such interesting enemies. We’ve seen that they clearly thrive and draw strength from negative emotions, but at the same time, they’re obviously capable of corrupting creatures and people as well.</description></item><item><title>Outmatched</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/outmatched/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 10:16:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/outmatched/</guid><description>Being almost a full expansion past Mists of Pandaria, it’s easy to forget just how freaking creepy the Sha are! And their weird shadowy, void-like essence always did strike me as one of the more sinister forms of attack. Do they burn? Do they burn your spirit? Who knows!</description></item><item><title>Chapter Seven: Pride</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-seven-pride/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 09:47:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-seven-pride/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 6</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-6/</guid><description>That does it for Chapter 6. One more to go!
It’s funny, but it’s looking like FDWL might possibly span the entire length of Warlords of Draenor. While it’s definitely not something we planned (FDWL actually started a few weeks before the Warlords announcement) it’s rather appropriate!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 5</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-5/</guid><description>Everyone knows the unspoken rules of pun battles! You should know better, Vid!
Oh, and if you don’t remember what that thing is that hit the sphere, here’s a reminder. Can’t really blame you if you’ve forgotten — that was a year and a half ago, holy crap!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 4</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-4/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 3</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-3/</guid><description>Welp, I sure hope Vid got insurance, because those Golems are not cheap!
It’s a little strange hearing all the news about the Legion alpha going on, when we’re still exploring the storyline of Mists here. Hopefully anyone reading this hasn’t forgotten about everything that happened back on Pandaria!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 11:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-2/</guid><description>And in this moment, Vid was reminded that Kura and Rades are siblings, after all…
Thanks for your patience, everyone! Right back into the action! As always, your comments and feedback is appreciated, or you can find us on Twitter!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-1/</guid><description>FIGHT! FIGHT! FIGHT!
(Okay, the Sky Golem doesn’t technically have combat capabilities in-game. But it SHOULD. Look at those claws!)</description></item><item><title>Reunion</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reunion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 10:31:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reunion/</guid><description>It’s been a long time since Rades and Vid have seen each other – 42 pages, actually! That’s half the comic!!</description></item><item><title>Logistics</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/logistics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/logistics/</guid><description>Engineers: Life’s finest problem-solvers!</description></item><item><title>Faith</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/faith/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/faith/</guid><description>And we’re finally back to the rest of the cast. 😀 It’s been a while since we’ve seen them!</description></item><item><title>Almost</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/almost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/almost/</guid><description>Well, at least now Vid won’t have to feel bad about the Mechano-Hog getting destroyed.
Speaking of, the real Vid sure was happy when she saw the script for this page, and realized she wouldn’t have to draw the motorcycles anymore! Which just means I suppose I’ll have to give her something MORE complicated to draw now…</description></item><item><title>Results</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/results/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/results/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Exit Strategy</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/exit-strategy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 09:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/exit-strategy/</guid><description>A few people were asking what Rades was pouring out of that bag back on Page #80 — I told you it’d be explained! Granted, maybe he originally intended to use it just as a distraction, but I think it still served its purpose. (We also love seeing your comments trying to predict things that haven’t been revealed or explained yet in the story — we always get a kick when you guess right!</description></item><item><title>Command</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/command/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/command/</guid><description/></item><item><title>We Always Hurt The Ones We Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/we-always-hurt-the-ones-we-love/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/we-always-hurt-the-ones-we-love/</guid><description>I guess Rades shouldn’t have turned such a blind eye to his sister’s behavior all those years ago.</description></item><item><title>Helping</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/helping/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/helping/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Stealth Mission</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stealth-mission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 09:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stealth-mission/</guid><description>First of all, curse you Blizzard for already using the funny joke!
I’ve always imagined Rades (the character) as more of a scout than a straight-up soldier, so it stands to reason he might be pretty sneaky. Not sneaky enough though, it seems…</description></item><item><title>Found</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/found/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/found/</guid><description>Annnnd we’re back! It’s been a great month off for us to get our batteries recharged, and we can’t wait to finish this story! It’s been a long undertaking, perhaps longer than either Vid or I initially realized, but we’re confident that in the end it’ll be one we can look back on proudly.
Now that Warlords’ story has mostly been told, we can breathe a slight sigh of relief, as there was always the slight worry that some of the lore events might overlap or clash with what we had in mind with FDWL.</description></item><item><title>A Little Patience</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-little-patience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 09:36:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-little-patience/</guid><description>Poor Vid. It looks like she’ll be waiting awhile longer. Actually, you’ll have to wait along with her a bit too because we are taking a vacation for the month of July!
For many personal reasons, this year has been exhausting. I’m proud we were able to maintain our schedule throughout it, but I’m going on vacation in July and getting ahead on as many comics as we would’ve needed just wasn’t feasible.</description></item><item><title>Orcient History</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/orcient-history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/orcient-history/</guid><description>Aw yeah, going back to some old TBC lore! If you never quested through Nagrand as Horde, here’s a few links:
http://wow.gamepedia.com/Jorin_Deadeye
http://wow.gamepedia.com/Garrosh_Hellscream</description></item><item><title>Kura</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kura/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kura/</guid><description>I think one of our favorite things is designing new characters. Sure, it takes us forever because we usually have vastly different ideas about attire and equipment, and then naming them takes even longer as we toss ideas back and forth and examine existing naming conventions. But EVENTUALLY they get completed and then we can love them. 😀</description></item><item><title>Speechless</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/speechless/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/speechless/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Chapter 6: Anger</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-six-anger/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-six-anger/</guid><description>Hmm, the title for this Chapter is sort of fitting, given the temperature of the WoW community right now regarding some things. Things that ultimately will not affect FDWL or its characters, however! After all, they’re on Outland. Everything’s cool there.</description></item><item><title>Safe</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/safe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 09:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/safe/</guid><description>That’s it for Chapter 5! Wrathion’s got some thinking to do.
With that, think it’s about time for a change of scenery. Let’s get out of the mountains, and pay a visit to…oh, how about…the forest.
Finally, thank you to our latest Patreon supporter, Allison! 😀</description></item><item><title>True Colors</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/true-colors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/true-colors/</guid><description>I just noticed this week that the Sargerei mobs in Shadowmoon Valley (and the Sargerei Disguise toy) use a recolor of Sablemane’s outfit! The green and purple look’s not bad, but it doesn’t quite have the zing of Sablemane’s bright orange and red, in my opinion.</description></item><item><title>Trump Card</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/trump-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 10:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/trump-card/</guid><description>Sablemane may just come to regret antagonizing Wrathion so much.
Oh, and in case you’re curious when Wrathion may have picked up one of those Ethereal spheres…
Page 32
Page 35</description></item><item><title>Dissolution</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dissolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 10:13:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dissolution/</guid><description>This arc has been a pretty rough emotional ride. It’s an unfortunate reality that this type of conversation isn’t exactly that uncommon between parent and child. In a perfect world, parents would be accepting of the choices their children make, regardless of whether or not they agree with them. But we all know that doesn’t always happen.</description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Differences</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/irreconcilable-differences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/irreconcilable-differences/</guid><description>�?
In brighter news, Blizzard Watch has brought back its WoW webcomic link list! It’s called Webcomic Wrapup now – if you want some more Warcraft (or related) webcomics in your life – and why wouldn’t you! – go check the list!</description></item><item><title>Ties</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ties/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ties/</guid><description>I imagine if any of us were in Vid’s shoes, deprived of our mounts, we’d find it a harsh awakening. I mean, going without flying mounts in Warlords has been tough enough!
The 6.2 PTR just went live this week! Don’t worry, no spoilers here, but I will just say we’re pretty keenly interested to see how some of the datamined stuff turns out! FDWL obviously takes place on the original Outlands version of Draenor…but that doesn’t mean we’re not paying close attention to the lore and history being established in-game!</description></item><item><title>Interlude</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/interlude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/interlude/</guid><description>LOOK AT THE CUTE BIRBS
oh and also I guess there’s something going on with Rades.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/patch-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/patch-notes/</guid><description>Hey all, no FDWL update this week as Vid has some RL family stuff going on. (This isn’t an April First gag.)
However, Blizzard did release their special patch notes for today! As always, they’re amazing. but also check out that first screenshot!! 😀
FDWL will be back next week like normal – think it’s maybe time to check in on Rades, we haven’t seen him in a while! Until then, have a great day, and as male Forsaken NPCs say, “Trust no one.</description></item><item><title>Family Business, Part Three</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/family-business-part-three/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 09:45:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/family-business-part-three/</guid><description>One of my favorite moments in Mists of Pandaria was after you’d completed Wrathion’s Legendary questline and defeated Garrosh, when you return to the Tavern in the Mists and get to watch Wrathion throw a temper tantrum. I liked it because of Tong – how he finally has had enough and steps in and reprimands Wrathion for his childish behavior. Or to be precise, I enjoyed it because this NEVER HAPPENS.</description></item><item><title>Family Business, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/family-business-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 09:40:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/family-business-part-two/</guid><description>Alternate title for today’s page: WRONGO</description></item><item><title>Family Business, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/family-business-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/family-business-part-one/</guid><description>Sablemane’s been chilling in Blade’s Edge for a while, but he’s still got contacts, visitors passing through. You really think he wouldn’t keep up-to-date with what’s going on back home?</description></item><item><title>Choices</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 09:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choices/</guid><description>After all that time in Highmaul, I can’t help but wonder about the ogres who, on OUR Draenor, ended up founding Ogri’la. They were such an interesting faction! I guess it wouldn’t really make sense to see them again in Warlords, since there is no area with such a prolific amount of Apexis crystals, the source of their increased intellect. At least…not yet, anyway.
Many thanks to our latest patrons, William and Buglamp!</description></item><item><title>Focus</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/focus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/focus/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Glyph of Harsh Words</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/glyph-of-harsh-words/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/glyph-of-harsh-words/</guid><description>Erm, um, maybe that’s enough of Vid for now…let’s check in on someone else next week, shall we?
Thank you to Pix for being our latest Patreon sponsor! If this is a cunning ploy to keep me from wreaking havoc in your D&amp;amp;D game, sorry, but no cigar.</description></item><item><title>Old Wounds</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/old-wounds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 09:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/old-wounds/</guid><description>Poor Vid. That was a conversation that was simply never going to go well.
Shout-out to our latest Patreon patrons, Laura, Linet, Hilde and Kelly! Thank you for your support! &amp;lt;3</description></item><item><title>Vidyala’s Story</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/vidyalas-story/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/vidyalas-story/</guid><description>WOW, RUDE
Blackrock Foundry is live! Is your guild all set to take down Blackhand? I can’t wait to see what sort of interesting mechanics Blizzard throws at us this time. And it’s always exciting when you start collecting the first new tier set of an expansion!
Thank you to our latest Patreon patrons, Orkchop, Kelsey and Nharzul! We appreciate your support! 😀
Speaking of, we’ve posted the December wallpapers to the Patreon site for our patrons to download and enjoy!</description></item><item><title>Broken</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/broken/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/broken/</guid><description>(In case you’re wondering what bridge she’s talking about, see #12: Where the Heart Is.)
Thanks to our latest Patreon supporter, Maeli! 😀 And thanks to everyone who stopped by the Livestream session yesterday! Hope you had a fun time hanging out!</description></item><item><title>Chapter Five: Fear</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-five-fear/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-five-fear/</guid><description>One of the most prevalent questions among fans when it comes to Wrathion and his crusade against the other black dragons is, “Does he know about Sablemane?” And officially, no one knows. Wrathion seems to think he’s eliminated the rest of the Black Dragonflight…but we know he’s missed at least one.
When we were planning out the FDWL storyline, Wrathion meeting Sablemane was one of our major plot points. And I’ve had the above image in my head ever since, of a totally out-of-his-element Wrathion in Blade’s Edge, gazing up in frozen shock at those iconic stone spires and impaled black dragons overhead.</description></item><item><title>Guest of Honour</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/guest-of-honour/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/guest-of-honour/</guid><description>That wraps up Chapter Four! What does Sablemane want with Wrathion? What’s going to happen to Rades? What happened to Four? At least Vid’s received some happy news…
Speaking of Wrathion, I sure am curious what we’ll see of him in Warlords. I believe his only appearance so far takes place “off-camera”, mentioned in Admiral Taylor’s Garrison Log, which doesn’t really tell us much. Clearly the Black Prince has SOMETHING in mind, SOME objective here on AU-Draenor.</description></item><item><title>DoT</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 09:39:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dot/</guid><description>Rades, you should know better than to travel with such an injury! But then again I suppose your options were rather limited.
(Technically in-game Rades has maxed out First Aid, but let’s just assume that this type of wound is beyond the scope of a few bandages.)
Many thanks to our latest Daily Quests, one of our favorite WoW comics, and tremor3258! 😀</description></item><item><title>Happy Winter Veil!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-winter-veil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-winter-veil/</guid><description>Hope everyone is enjoying the season and holidays! Vid and I are both traveling for Christmas, so no new strip next week, but in the meantime enjoy this bit of FDWL holiday art! And click here to enjoy it full-size!
In other exciting news, thank you to Rachel for being our latest Patreon supporter! With this, we’ve now reached our milestone goal to have a monthly wallpaper each month for all of our patrons!</description></item><item><title>What Goes Up</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what-goes-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 10:07:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what-goes-up/</guid><description>Poor Four. Brawler’s Guild just couldn’t really prepare her for what to do when hitchhiking on the back of an unwilling flying black dragon, I guess.
Now, if only she were an engineer, she’d be fine here! A parachute cloak, or a goblin glider, and she’d be laughing.
Sadly, Four is not an engineer.
In other business, thank you to Jasyla for being our latest Patreon supporter! &amp;lt;3</description></item><item><title>The Light Reveals, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-two/</guid><description>The funny thing about creating a weekly comic strip is that sometimes events take a little while to unfold. Though we’ve had this particular moment Patreon supporters will forgive me for not showing the sketch for this page a day early as usual – I didn’t want to spoil the final version!
If you want to be further emotionally devastated today, Unbroken is necessary reading. We used much of the physical description of the process of becoming Broken from this short story to help determine what our important character should look like.</description></item><item><title>The Light Reveals, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-one/</guid><description>I wonder if we’ll see any Broken this expansion. I know history has changed, and the orcs didn’t drink the blood of Mannoroth…but Gul’dan IS out there, green-skinned and demon-tainted. So there’s definitely fel magic on the table, albeit on a smaller scale – for now, at least. And judging from the questlines, you KNOW Gul’dan has some pretty significant plans of his own meant to further his own schemes, and probably those of the Legion, who clearly still have their eyes on Draenor…</description></item><item><title>Home Swamp Home</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/home-swamp-home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/home-swamp-home/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Be our guest</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/be-our-guest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/be-our-guest/</guid><description>What an expensive bit of therapy. The engineer in me is crying.
Hope everyone is enjoying Warlords so far! I know both Vid and I are LOVING all the new lore, familiar faces, and overall storyline. And GARRISONS! Oh my god, the garrisons. What more needs to be said. Now if you’ll excuse me, I think it’s almost time to send my followers out on today’s missions.</description></item><item><title>The one that got away</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-one-that-got-away/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 09:45:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-one-that-got-away/</guid><description>Funny story about panel 5 on this page – without meaning to, I had unconsciously modeled Four’s pose after Spider-Man comic I read twenty-four years ago. And then, after realizing this fact, I was able to identify, track down and download said comic to examine the angle of the pose. God bless the internet.
IT’S WARLORDS LAUNCH TOMORROW! If you’re taking the day off to enjoy it, make sure you have some snacks and drinks to keep you going!</description></item><item><title>More than you can chew</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/more-than-you-can-chew/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 09:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/more-than-you-can-chew/</guid><description>It’s like that Feist song.
It’s Blizzcon time! Last time Vid and I were stunned with the announcement that WoW was returning to Draenor – one might say “with love” – so it’ll be interesting to see what the big news and surprises are this time! It’s funny – when the news about Warlords of Draenor hit, we were actually a little alarmed, wondering if it was going to affect FDWL’s storyline.</description></item><item><title>Eyes on the Prize</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/eyes-on-the-prize/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/eyes-on-the-prize/</guid><description>Okay, this isn’t exactly how Flare works in-game, but Rades IS an engineer, after all.
This week’s patch notes were pretty funny, especially “Thrall received a reminder that he is currently still on Azeroth.” Of course, instead of talking like he was already on Draenor, Thrall now talks like he’s back in Orgrimmar as Horde Warchief. Oh, Thrall.
Vid got a Grand Expedition Yak this week, which means Transmog ANYWHERE, ANYTIME.</description></item><item><title>Righteous Defense</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/righteous-defense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/righteous-defense/</guid><description>Somewhere, Protection Paladins are crying in remembrance.</description></item><item><title>The Nose Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-nose-knows/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-nose-knows/</guid><description>When Vid &amp;amp; Rades were making their travel plans way back at the start of Chapter 2, there were some comments wondering about Sablemane and Wrathion. These queries continued when Sablemane actually showed up on page 25. Well, trust us, these two meeting and interacting has ALWAYS been one of the stories we’ve wanted to tell in FDWL. They’re such interesting personalities, with such great potential!
In other news, thanks to some very generous Patreon patrons, we’re looking to get our website looked at sometime soon!</description></item><item><title>Chapter Four: Hatred</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-four-hatred/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-four-hatred/</guid><description>And we’re back! What’s Sabellian here for? How is Rades doing? Why did the Broken stop? These answers and more, coming to a From Draenor near you!
We also have some other, exciting news – we’ve started a Patreon account!
Now don’t worry – From Draenor With Love will always remain free for your reading enjoyment. However, working on the comic does take us a lot of time each week, and we do have operating costs such as web hosting, brushes, inks, etc.</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 4</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 10:07:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-4/</guid><description>And that’s it for Chapter 3! &amp;gt;:D Things are getting real.
Today’s page also marks a special occasion for FDWL – it’s officially been one year since we started the story! We know this because it’s ALSO Siege of Orgrimmar’s one-year anniversary (which is…special…in its own way) and we specifically launched Chapter 1: Despair to coincide with the patch’s events.
It’s been an exciting year for FDWL, and I think we’ve definitely both learned a lot about the comic process, as well as simply what it takes to make a weekly webcomic work without killing each other.</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 3</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 09:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-3/</guid><description>document.createElement('audio'); /media/042_angryriver.mp3
One of the side benefits of being friends with WoW players who a) passionately roleplay draenei; b) hate orcs; c) all of the above, is that when it comes time to write a Broken character who has a huge hate-on for orcs, I have a huge selection of angry dialogue samples ready-made to pull from. 😉
(As for said Broken, he is of course referring back to the events of Page #18.</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-2/</guid><description>This week’s soundtrack:
(I don’t know that we’ll post a song for every page, but I figure if we have one that fits, we might as well!)
Ah, the Broken. You can’t really delve into draenei and orc lore without visiting them. If you’re unfamiliar with Broken lore, you should absolutely go read Micky Neilson’s short story Unbroken. It’s a fantastic read. Just be warned that our Broken, are not necessarily like Nobundo…</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-1/</guid><description>WELP
Seems like Rades has worse luck than Vid, doesn’t it?</description></item><item><title>Employee Loyalty</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/employee-loyalty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 10:09:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/employee-loyalty/</guid><description>Hey, it’s back to familiar territory! Personally, Zangarmarsh is my favorite zone in Outlands. The colours and environment is just so peaceful and soothing.
Writing dialogue for Four can be tough, and I admit I struggled a bit with this page. She’s guarded, with a peculiar manner of speaking. This was a LOT for her to say. But I think it turned out well, and maybe explains a bit about her and just how she ended up with a Black Dragon for an employer.</description></item><item><title>Definitely Skull Level, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-2/</guid><description>Would-be rogues know what Rades is talking about.
With this (minor) delay out of the way, our party is able to make good time to the Dark Portal and reach Draenor. Shattrath is a few days away, so they settle down and make camp for the night…</description></item><item><title>Definitely Skull Level, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 09:16:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-1/</guid><description>Is there anything more pitiful and/or annoying than running through a low level zone and accumulating a swarm of low-level grey mobs? It’s like, dudes, I’m just here to get some Goldthorn to level Alchemy, go away.
And then they DAZE YOU and DISMOUNT YOU and suddenly you’re knee-deep in a sea of blood and linen cloth.</description></item><item><title>Starring Ice Cube</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/starring-ice-cube/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/starring-ice-cube/</guid><description>Random trivia – this is the first FDWL strip (in the story arc format) that takes place on Azeroth!
(Which makes sense, I suppose. It’s not called From Azeroth With Love.)
On a similar note, it might seem a little odd that Rades &amp;amp; Vid have spent so much time in Pandaria as compared to Draenor, given our name. But this is about to change!</description></item><item><title>Ready Check</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ready-check/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 09:47:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ready-check/</guid><description>If you don’t recognize Four’s “pet”, here’s a hint.
Confused about the strange hooked shape of Wrathion’s dagger? That’s a type of knife called a white-quality vendor-purchased weapon.
(This isn’t the one Wrathion has, of course. I doubt the Black Prince would be caught dead with an ordinary, mundane knife.)</description></item><item><title>When I asked if you had BG experience, I wasn’t talking about PVP</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/when-i-asked-if-you-had-bg-experience-i-wasnt-talking-about-pvp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/when-i-asked-if-you-had-bg-experience-i-wasnt-talking-about-pvp/</guid><description>Confession: We realize the Tushui Alliance lion isn’t technically the symbol of the Brawler’s Guild, but the Brawler’s guild doesn’t actually HAVE a symbol! We checked the arena, the shirts, the NPCs, nothing.
But you know what? Both Horde and Alliance began running their Brawler’s Guild at around the same time as the two Pandaren factions joined up, so maybe Aysa and Ji brought the tradition with them.
(Shhhh, just go with it.</description></item><item><title>Four’s Company</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fours-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 04:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fours-company/</guid><description>Way, way back when we were planning out the FDWL plot, we knew that one of Wrathion’s bodyguards would become part of the story. Originally, I had penciled in Right, who – along with her partner, Left – can always be seen wherever their boss goes. I thought it would be fun to explore this cool, badass-looking woman, who despite numerous appearances in-game, never actually speaks or does anything.
But after talking it over with Vid, we realized that while it would be interesting to use Right, we had a great opportunity to create a brand new person instead!</description></item><item><title>Three’s Company</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/threes-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 04:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/threes-company/</guid><description>Hmm, who could that be up there in the balcony, listening in? Guess we’ll find out next week! 😀</description></item><item><title>The Ghost and the Darkness, Part 3</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 03:20:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-3/</guid><description>Standard hunter operating procedure 101!
Everything seems to be proceeding quite nicely according to plan, doesn’t it?</description></item><item><title>The Ghost and the Darkness, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 02:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-2/</guid><description>HAMMER OF JUSTICE!</description></item><item><title>The Ghost and the Darkness, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 04:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-1/</guid><description>And what shoulder, &amp;amp; what art.
Could twist the sinews of thy heart?
And when thy heart began to beat,
What dread hand? &amp;amp; what dread feet?
– The Tyger, William Blake
This just in: Sha really are incredibly weird, gross and ugly little buggers, when you stop and look at them closely.
They sure do match our color scheme though! 😉</description></item><item><title>Chapter Three: Violence</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-three-violence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 01:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-three-violence/</guid><description>And we’re back!
Just a reminder that even though War Crimes just came out, and Garrosh’s trial is what’s “currently” happening, FDWL takes place during the Siege of Orgrimmar timeframe.
As for whether this is directly relevant? Well, let’s just say we’ve both got the book and are pretty curious to see what all happens. 😉</description></item><item><title>Unused FDWL Strip: Archimonde Crossing</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unused-fdwl-strip-archimonde-crossing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 03:22:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unused-fdwl-strip-archimonde-crossing/</guid><description>We should be back with Chapter 3 next week! Until then, enjoy the script for a page we never ended up doing: Archimonde Crossing.
When Animal Crossing: New Leaf came out, both Vid and I were enjoying it so much we wanted to do a FDWL comic about it. We had a few different ideas, including one about how hilarious it is when you shake a tree in Animal Crossing, hoping for money or furniture, and instead you get AN ANGRY SWARM OF BEES.</description></item><item><title>Any Similarities are Purely Coincidental</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/any-similarities-are-purely-coincidental/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 04:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/any-similarities-are-purely-coincidental/</guid><description>I just want everyone to know that I combed the Auction House for weeks looking for Ethereum Prison Keys, for reference &amp;amp; accuracy. And they didn’t help at all.
So we came up with something new for the prison spheres, something that would make sense with their role in ethereal society, and with where we encounter them in Blade’s Edge and Netherstorm. And of course, something that may seem a little familiar.</description></item><item><title>The Exchange</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-exchange/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 02:15:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-exchange/</guid><description>You know what they say: Every ethereal has his price.
And remember, these Ethereum guys, they’re way out of date on their gemstones! Cardinal Rubies, Amberjewels, Lapis Lazulis, Queen’s Garnets, Primal Diamonds…we’re talking like, three whole expansions’ worth of exciting new jewels to covet! What self-respecting ethereal could resist such an offer? 😉
Next week will mark the end of Chapter 2! After that, we’ll be taking a short break for some RL vacations and script planning, but we’ll be back before you know it!</description></item><item><title>Old Friends</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/old-friends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 03:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/old-friends/</guid><description>Vid’s turn! 😉
For those unfamiliar with what Rades is talking about, he’s referring to the fact that Rexxar, Vol’jin and Chen are old war buddies. Years ago (in Warcraft III) they fought together, for Thrall’s Horde, against the then-leader of Theramore, Daelin Proudmoore (Jaina’s father), who hated the Horde and wanted to respark the Horde-Alliance war. Considering the situation and players involved in the Siege of Orgrimmar, it seems a bit of a similar situation.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Make a Deal</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/lets-make-a-deal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 02:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/lets-make-a-deal/</guid><description>Does anyone actually go back to Gezhe each month and get their monthly Membership Benefits? I don’t, and yet I feel like I almost should – the Outlands phase of leveling Jewelcrafting is always such a pain, since those gems are so scarce, and Golden Draenite is actually fairly valuable. And more importantly, I DID do all that work for the Consortium back in the day – I EARNED those gems!</description></item><item><title>Nagrand Slam</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nagrand-slam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 05:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nagrand-slam/</guid><description>My favorite moment when crafting a story (such as in a D&amp;amp;D campaign) comes when finally, after months of straightforward, introductory play, all the setup stuff is complete. The plot hooks have been put into play, the important characters have been established, and the overarching story is just starting to pick up speed.
I’ve been extra excited about FDWL lately, because I think we’re at that step. Fun times ahead!</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 04:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes/</guid><description>Because this Monday was my birthday and I was going out of town on the weekend, I asked Rades if we could take a week off the “regular” comic! We agreed to do it and just have something for filler. I thought that especially since I now do most of the comic on paper that it might be interesting for you to see where I do it and what it looks like from my end.</description></item><item><title>A Class-ic Mistake</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-class-ic-mistake/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 02:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-class-ic-mistake/</guid><description>We don’t use colour in our pages that often, but man, when we do, it’s sure a nice contrast with the black &amp;amp; white panels!
I don’t know about you, but I would totally craft a hot pink Sky Golem in-game and fly around in it.
This week’s page is actually canonical – it’s Vid’s birthday next week! The real Vid, I mean! So be sure to wish her well. To celebrate, she’s going out of town, so there won’t be an actual comic page next week.</description></item><item><title>Balance</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/balance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 03:45:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/balance/</guid><description>It of course goes without saying that this song was listened to by both Vid and I during the making of this strip, given the presence of a certain talking chandelier.
“Many lives were lost to bring you these tab collars.”</description></item><item><title>Teamwork</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/teamwork/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 02:08:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/teamwork/</guid><description>OLD DRAENEI
OLD DRAENEI WITH CANES
(CANE-EI)</description></item><item><title>City of Trite</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/city-of-trite/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 03:13:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/city-of-trite/</guid><description>I’d like to tell you that eventually mangling draenic phrases gets old, but I’d be lying. It’s one of my favorite things to do.
But it’s not just me! After reading the script, Vid told me she’s always liked the one that sounds like “buy your niece a car.”
I can’t wait until Warlords of Draenor where we’ll get even more expressions to abuse!</description></item><item><title>Random Encounter</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/random-encounter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 06:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/random-encounter/</guid><description>It’s the scene from the Chapter Title page, oooooh! Sharp-eyed readers may notice something telling on that page now, too. But what does it mean?? Time will tell.
One of the most interesting things about writing FDWL is discussing scenes, and realizing how the events in the comic are letting us establish little character traits about Vid &amp;amp; Rades. We had a good laugh when realizing what type of person Vid (the character) is when she’s on watch.</description></item><item><title>Memory Lane</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/memory-lane/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 02:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/memory-lane/</guid><description>After getting swamped last week and falling a bit behind schedule, Vid and I sat down this week and tossed some ideas around on how we could streamline the comic process a little. We realized that something that would help us out a great deal would be adopting a cleaner, more “inked” look. It’ll be a bit of a change from the pages so far, but I’ve always thought Vid’s art looked super sharp when in the inked-page step, so I’m actually really glad everyone is getting to see it now!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Colour Keys</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-colour-keys/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 02:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-colour-keys/</guid><description>Work and life stuff hit us both pretty hard this past week and unfortunately we weren’t able to get the comic finished. This doesn’t happen very often and we’d like to build some buffer, but for now we’d prefer not to rush the comic and have the quality suffer.
So what are you looking at, then? Back towards the end of Chapter One, Rades and I discussed at length to have a wardrobe change in Chapter Two.</description></item><item><title>Symbols</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/symbols/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 03:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/symbols/</guid><description>Aw yiss, inventing us some headcanon draenei lore! Observant readers may remember that we alluded to these personal symbols back in Vid’s character profile.
If you look at official WoW artwork, there are TONS of different draenei sigils/symbols depicted. Why ARE they different? Do they represent different magical abilities? Or is it like we’ve described here, something biological, like an individual’s unique DNA footprint?
Personally, I think it’s a lot cooler to imagine those symbols as displays of personal identity rather than just to indicate “I’m using magic.</description></item><item><title>Hit M for Map</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/hit-m-for-map/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 02:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/hit-m-for-map/</guid><description>Where’s the TomTom addon when you need it?</description></item><item><title>Chapter Two: Doubt</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-two-doubt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 04:41:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-two-doubt/</guid><description>Happy New Year, everyone! On to chapter two!
I worried how recognizable Zangarmarsh would be in black &amp;amp; white, without those soft, tranquil shades of blue – but I suppose those giant mushrooms are pretty distinctive. I’ve always loved Zangarmarsh, it’s probably my favorite Burning Crusade zone. Not necessarily for the quests or anything – it’s just so soothing and calming visually.
Will that carry over for comic-Vid and Rades? I guess you’ll have to wait and find out!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Happy Winter Veil!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-happy-winter-veil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 01:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-happy-winter-veil/</guid><description>Happy Winter Veil, everyone! Hope Robo-Greatfather Winter is nice to you this year!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Character Profile: Vidyala</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-vidyala/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 02:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-vidyala/</guid><description>And now, Vid’s turn for the character development questionnaire!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Character Profile: Rades</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-rades/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 18:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-rades/</guid><description>There’s been a fun little a good cook, too.)
Obviously, we don’t want to devote 30 days to this, and some of the questions didn’t really work for characters answering it about themselves, so the FDWL version of this survey is only 21 questions.
Check back next week’s for Vid’s answers!</description></item><item><title>Pieces</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pieces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 04:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pieces/</guid><description>“…Why did you play that piece just now?”
“It’s a Pandaren board game. The object is for both players to win.”
“That’s ridiculous! Why would you even play!?”
That’s it for Chapter One! The groundwork is set, the plot points have been laid out. Now – rubs hands together eagerly – it’s time to have some fun.
We will be taking a short break before starting in on the next leg of the story, to allow for Christmas holidays and whatnot.</description></item><item><title>Where The Heart Is</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/where-the-heart-is/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 03:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/where-the-heart-is/</guid><description>Y’know, I asked Vid to do something special artistically for the middle two panels, and HOLY CRAP did she nail it! Those panels might be my favorite artwork in all of FDWL so far.
Next week will mark the end of our first chapter! (Will all chapters be the same length? We don’t know yet.) We hope you’ve been enjoying the story so far! Now that we’ve laid the groundwork, it’s time to get this show on the road!</description></item><item><title>Quest Accepted</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quest-accepted/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 04:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quest-accepted/</guid><description>I always find it funny when our plot details are actually accurate/based off the real characters. For example, Rades the WoW toon really IS an honorary member of the Consortium, having reached Exalted status with them way, way back (I think I wanted the tabard? or maybe one of their engineering schematics). On the other hand, Vid never did the rep grind for them, and we’ll see this reflected later on in the comic.</description></item><item><title>Naar-who?</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/naar-who/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 02:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/naar-who/</guid><description>Look at us! Blizzcon week and not even missing a beat? YEAH! But seriously, Vid worked like a maniac to get a few strips done ahead of time, so she definitely earned the vacation time! It certainly wouldn’t have been the end of the world to have a filler strip or two, but we’re pretty pleased that we didn’t have to resort to that!
As for Blizzcon itself – WOW! Exciting stuff!</description></item><item><title>The Magic Word</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-magic-word/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 02:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-magic-word/</guid><description>It’s Blizzcon week! Hope everyone who’s attending the con or watching via Virtual Ticket has a great time! If you’re there, keep an eye out for Vid – she’ll be the one with a bunch of FDWL stickers and business cards! 😉</description></item><item><title>Awkward</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/awkward/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 02:39:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/awkward/</guid><description>One of the hazards in being an insatiably curious two-year-old dragon and knowing very little about history is not recognizing the kind of questions you simply do not ask in civilized company.
Some readers have asked us for a while now about Vid and Rades and their connection to Draenor, so here’s a few answers!</description></item><item><title>Attention Span</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/attention-span/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 02:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/attention-span/</guid><description>Something you should know about engineers: we’re constantly keeping an eye out for cliffs, staircases and towers to hurl ourselves from that we might use our gadgets to float safely to the ground in style.
Ask the engineer in your raid. They’ll verify this.</description></item><item><title>Oh, It’s You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/oh-its-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 02:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/oh-its-you/</guid><description>If you think about it, Wrathion probably IS pretty bothered by what happened to the Vale. It’s just a stone’s throw away from the Tavern in the Mists! That has to be horrible for property values.</description></item><item><title>It Probably Happens A Lot</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/it-probably-happens-a-lot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 15:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/it-probably-happens-a-lot/</guid><description>Hunters know what I’m talking about.
LOOKING AT YOU, KRUSH.</description></item><item><title>Not Again</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-again/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 09:12:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-again/</guid><description>Aw yeah, sticking to our own vaguely-established continuity! 😉</description></item><item><title>All Roads Lead to Orgrimmar</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/all-roads-lead-to-orgrimmar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 07:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/all-roads-lead-to-orgrimmar/</guid><description>DIALOGUE YAY
Oh Garrosh, look at all the trouble you’re causing.</description></item><item><title>Repercussions</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/repercussions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 14:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/repercussions/</guid><description>Starting to get underway! The impact of Garrosh’s actions in the Vale. Major events are about to be set in motion.
Apologies for the disarray of the site design right now. We updated the WordPress version and it broke everything, just like it ALWAYS DOES (seriously, it actually breaks every time we update) but thankfully the damage doesn’t seem TOO severe this time. Hopefully it shouldn’t be too long before we get everything back to how it should be.</description></item><item><title>Chapter One: Despair</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-one-despair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-one-despair/</guid><description>It’s an exciting day for From Draenor With Love! After nearly two years of making this comic, we felt we were ready to tackle some new challenges.
What does this mean? Our name is staying the same. The comic will still be about Rades and Vid. It will be an ongoing story from week to week. The format will be less static four-panel and more graphic novel. I also made some changes personally, going back to my roots a bit as it were to ink the comic by hand rather than entirely digitally.</description></item><item><title>The Siege of Orgrimmar</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-siege-of-orgrimmar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 07:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-siege-of-orgrimmar/</guid><description>Patch 5.4 is almost here! I’m totally pumped, but I’m also dreading it! I want to see the cool new raid content and bosses, but I don’t WANT to kill Nazgrim! I don’t WANT to kill the Paragons!
And I don’t want to kill Garrosh!
(He’s a major From Draenor With Love character, after all!)
Speaking of the comic, this strip marks an important milestone for us. Starting next week, everything is changing!</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes Part 3: Production</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-3-production/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 08:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-3-production/</guid><description>For a larger version of today’s strip, click here.
This is part 3 of 3 of our Behind the Scenes series! Next week we’ll have something…suitable, for the looming 5.4 patch. And then after that it’ll be SOMETHING ENTIRELY NEW AND EXCITING! We’re going to be trying something new so we hope you enjoy it!</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes Part 2: Art</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-2-art/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 08:03:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-2-art/</guid><description>Last week, Rades explained the process of how he scripts and sometimes storyboards a FDWL script! This week I’m going to be telling you about how I do the sketching and art.
For a larger version of today’s strip, click here!
The following is a transcript of text from the above image.
It’s worth noting that over the time we’ve been doing this I have simplified the art a fair bit to save time.</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes Part 1: Script</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-1-script/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 08:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-1-script/</guid><description>For a larger version of today’s strip, click here. For a text version, well, read on!
Everyone’s busy preparing for patch 5.4 and the Siege of Orgrimmar, and we’re no exception! We’re working on some significant changes to FDWL that you can expect to see when the patch goes live. For now, we thought we’d share a bit of the creative process and show just how we do this comic thing!</description></item><item><title>The Real Twelve</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-real-twelve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-real-twelve/</guid><description>Hey, I don’t think it’s too much of a stretch! Rades is an accomplished engineer, he could undoubtedly keep a TARDIS running, and he could accomplish so much with a sonic screwdriver! I think Vid would make a great companion, though she could be the Doctor just as easily.
I did this art awhile ago and thought considering this Sunday’s announcement, using it now would be pretty timely. The opportunity to put Rades in a dapper suit jacket and bow tie was too good to pass up.</description></item><item><title>Dig Dug Bug</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dig-dug-bug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dig-dug-bug/</guid><description>If it’s not a bind-on-account piece of gear to mega-buff alts, a fun vanity item to bust out during killshots, or hilariously unpredictable hearthstone replacements that randomly take you all over Azeroth, WE DON’T WANT IT.</description></item><item><title>Tourist’s Guide to Ihgaluk Crag</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tourists-guide-to-ihgaluk-crag/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 10:27:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tourists-guide-to-ihgaluk-crag/</guid><description>Yet More Things To Do and See While in The Crag:
– Jump So High You Fly Out of The Crag and The Disguise Wears Off and You Splat on The Ground, Not That This Has Ever Happened To Us
– Cleansing Baths in Natural Filth Pools
– Meet the Local Wildlife (And Crush Them Beneath Your Feet)
– Jump Around
– Jump Around
– Jump Around
– Jump Up Jump Up And Get Down</description></item><item><title>Talent Specialization</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/talent-specialization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 07:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/talent-specialization/</guid><description>Suddenly, heroic raiding guilds start prowling the Warcraft fan art forums for recruits.
(And how long would it be before Razer released a special “Gaming Tablet” for the truly hardcore?)
I’m really glad someone else in my guild handles the Celestial buffs on Twin Consorts. I’ve glanced at the constellation diagrams/paths once or twice, and immediately came to the conclusion that it was something I completely and absolutely never wanted to do.</description></item><item><title>Peons Are People Too</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/peons-are-people-too/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 09:12:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/peons-are-people-too/</guid><description>I totally get the Darkspear Rebellion, the disruption of the Kor’kron war engine, the stealing of valuable resources for the upcoming siege on Orgrimmar. That all makes sense. And if we have to take out a few Kor’kron Commanders or Goblin Mercenaries while we’re at it? Sure. No argument here.
But the workers? What did they ever do to us? They’re just laborers! Red-collar working-class civilians. They’re just doing their 9 to 5, cutting up meat, chopping down trees, and suddenly we fly in on our giant cosmic dragons, beat ’em up, blow up their machines, and then take all their stuff.</description></item><item><title>There Are Two Types of People</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-are-two-types-of-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 08:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-are-two-types-of-people/</guid><description>The most difficult thing about this comic is that I had to stop playing “Animal Crossing: New Leaf” long enough to draw it.
If you’re not familiar, ACNL is a kind of life simulator game for the Nintendo 3DS that has been sweeping through the WoW twitter community like a wildfire. I played an earlier Animal Crossing title on the Gamecube back in the day. In terms of gameplay it’s pretty basic: Grow/harvest fruit, plant flowers, laugh at things your neighbours say, fish and catch bugs, dig up fossils, design clothes.</description></item><item><title>Whateverstone is More Like It</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whateverstone-is-more-like-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 12:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whateverstone-is-more-like-it/</guid><description>I’m not sure I know of a character in any book, movie or game who has had their personality and history thrown to the wayside and trampled into the dust as much as Garrosh has this expansion. I mean, in Cataclysm he certainly wasn’t perfect, but he had distinct good points to accompany his flaws, was a good character foil for his mirror image, Varian, and was showing definite signs of growth from his hotheaded, annoying days of being a mad dog yipping at Thrall during Wrath.</description></item><item><title>Can I Keep Him?</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/can-i-keep-him/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/can-i-keep-him/</guid><description>The big evil bad guys in WoW sure do like their pets, don’t they? It seems like every tier there’s at least one boss with special pets, or a boss that is itself a giant pet. Sometimes they’re just there, leaving their connection to the boss up to your imagination, but some, like Magmaw or Rageface/Riplimb, are outright stated to be pets. And some of them are really loved! Shannox loves his little doggies!</description></item><item><title>Nomi No-No</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nomi-no-no/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 09:39:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nomi-no-no/</guid><description>As many Pandaria chefs know, achievement.
However, to become Best Friends you have to go through a ton of cooking dailies with Nomi, where you give him some mundane cooking ingredients each day so he can practice his culinary skills. He then gives you back some Fish Jerky or some other junk.
Most people just sell the stuff to a vendor. But me? I don’t want his crappy food.
SO I DESTROY IT.</description></item><item><title>A Quick AFK</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-quick-afk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 18:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-quick-afk/</guid><description>This week in lieu of a comic we have instead a quick painting I did. I’ve had family stuff come up that I had to deal with, it’s sad but sometimes life wins out. The average comic takes me around five+ hours to draw and unfortunately this week I didn’t have those hours. Back when we started FDWL they used to take me eight! I haven’t gotten that much faster, I have simplified the art significantly though.</description></item><item><title>The Proudmoore “Problem”</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</guid><description>A lot of people think Jaina has this terrible reputation regarding the men in her life, that she has “terrible taste in men”, or that she breaks guys’ hearts and/or makes them go crazy. This is utter nonsense. The problem isn’t with Jaina, the problem is that the men in her life are just plain jerks.
Have you actually LISTENED to the crap these guys say? It’s pretty sad when Garrosh of all people has treated her with more dignity and respect than her so-called close friends.</description></item><item><title>Blizzcon Badges!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</guid><description>Do you need a little something to set you apart from the crowd at Blizzcon? Would you like a small piece of art to call your own and remember all the good times you had at the convention? I’ve been painting up just the thing!
These little paintings are painted on thick, high-quality Arches watercolour paper with Winsor &amp;amp; Newton watercolours. In a world of art that’s increasingly digital, I find I am loving going back to my roots and painting with brushes and pigments again.</description></item><item><title>An Unfortunate Turnip of Events</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/an-unfortunate-turnip-of-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 08:29:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/an-unfortunate-turnip-of-events/</guid><description>Remember the good old days in the first month of Mists, when carrots, lettuce and leeks were flying off the Auction House faster than you could list them, and for outrageous prices? I don’t even remember exactly, but weren’t they going for like 100 gold each? 100 GOLD PER TURNIP. And raiders who adamantly insisted they needed the best buff foods possible were crafting those banquets requiring 50 turnips at a time.</description></item><item><title>The Mogu Menace</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-mogu-menace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 08:25:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-mogu-menace/</guid><description>Kill 10 Mogu. Kill 8 more Mogu. Hey guess what? Kill a dozen more.
I wonder just how many Mogu we’ve taken out in our time here? All these Mogu-slaying dailies HAVE to be taking a toll on their population. Hell, I’ve slaughtered a few thousand alone.
Kill Mogu for Valor, kill Mogu for reputation, kill Mogu because they’re in the way while doing Archaeology…name a reason, and we’ve probably killed a Mogu for it.</description></item><item><title>Double Digits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</guid><description>I imagine tanks everywhere are shaking their heads in grim recognition of this scene. After all, how many times have they turned, scanning for the next pack of mobs to pull, only to hear that dreaded “FWOOSH” sound as an enormous ball of fire hurtles past them? Because EVERYONE KNOWS you can’t just WASTE A HOT STREAK PROC.
MAGES.
However, Vid’s lightning-fast DPS instincts served her well when it came to get Blizzcon tickets, netting her an unbelievably low 33rd in queue!</description></item><item><title>The Scarlet Letters</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-scarlet-letters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 08:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-scarlet-letters/</guid><description>WE REGRET NOTHING</description></item><item><title>Your New Undisputed Champion</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-new-undisputed-champion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 08:36:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-new-undisputed-champion/</guid><description>You know, at first I thought Hagara’s ice walls were bad. Saw a lot of people get insta-gibbed by those in LFR back during Cataclysm.
Then Elegon and his magic floor came and caused hilariously large quantities of surprise deaths, and I thought we had a new winner.
But then…came Durumu.
I can honestly say this was the first time I’ve ever seen the entire LFR group instantly perish in the blink of an eye.</description></item><item><title>Desserter Debuff</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/desserter-debuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/desserter-debuff/</guid><description>At the end of March I was thrilled to be taking a trip to Toronto/Montréal because it meant I’d have the chance to meet lots of great WoW people I’d gotten to know online. When I looked for “Things To Do in Toronto” I found a listing for a cupcake decorating class, and that was just icing on the cake. I was thrilled when Serrinne, Kaleri and Jasyla agreed to go with me.</description></item><item><title>Blingtrolled</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blingtrolled/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blingtrolled/</guid><description>Yet another reason why Engineering is the best profession!
Seriously, there’s few things funnier than plopping down Blingtron in a hard-to-reach spot in a well-populated area and sitting back to watch people go MAD as they try to find that elusive free loot. My personal favorites include trees in Halfhill, the upper balconies in Pandalaran, or in the normally-inaccessible catwalk in Orgrimmar’s front auction house.
Thanks to Raijair, Kalbeari, Hachidori, Dhevon and Korrath for the use of your likenesses this week!</description></item><item><title>Our New Favorite Boss</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-new-favorite-boss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 07:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-new-favorite-boss/</guid><description>Could this really be that far off, after seeing Tortos?
There’s been a lot of interesting raid boss mechanics – vehicles, flying, spirit realms – but few things are as satisfying or funny as just hauling off and punting a giant turtle at an even BIGGER turtle.
Bravo, Blizzard encounter design team. Bravo.</description></item><item><title>Fortune and Glory, Kid</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fortune-and-glory-kid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 08:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fortune-and-glory-kid/</guid><description>I think the solo loot scenario is my favorite thing in Mists so far. And I don’t even mean the loot! The loot’s okay, but really, Elder Charms are SO Patch 5.1. I just love running the place! And finding hidden chests and secret paths to said chests. There’s been a few chests in the first room, and one in the hallway leading to the second room, that I have no idea at all how to reach.</description></item><item><title>iWrynny</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/iwrynny/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 08:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/iwrynny/</guid><description>Somewhere out there in Pandaria, there’s an armorsmith with one twisted sense of humor.
Poor clueless little Anduin. Hands up if you saw him step onto that platform covered in Sha magic and walk right up to Garrosh, and thought to yourself “welp, I have a bad feeling about how this is going to turn out.” AND SURE ENOUGH.
Should have listened to Dezco, kid. Even if he does wear babies as armor.</description></item><item><title>Pretty Much a Constant Thing With Us</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pretty-much-a-constant-thing-with-us/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pretty-much-a-constant-thing-with-us/</guid><description>Hey, this feels familiar, doesn’t it?
Anyway, WE’RE BACK! /blows kisses from amidst a sea of fluttering rose petals
The time off has been good to us and we’re ready to leap headfirst into all the exciting new 5.2 stuff! Let’s just hope we can remember how to do this comic thing! (Confession, it took me nearly 10 minutes to remember the WordPress login info.)
Now yes, we know that Heart of Fear is technically old content now, but we had this script in the queue and we can’t just WASTE it!</description></item><item><title>Rested Experience</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</guid><description>Well, it finally happened: Vid’s drawing arm fell off. Like, literally, just sketching away and plop! it’s a scene right out of the Undercity. It’s all good though, she’s out talking to Mekkatorque right now about a steam-powered mechanical replacement. She says it’s no big deal, but as a veteran engineer, I remain skeptical.
But joking aside, the unfortunate reality is we’re starting to feel a bit of burnout, and there’s been some real-life commitments that are rearing their unavoidable and time-consuming heads.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 12:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</guid><description>The inevitable result of last week’s devious scheme.
(Really, this moment was so amazing, how could we NOT give it the full-comic spotlight it deserves??)
You know, in-game Garrosh is unpleasant and thoroughly unlikeable, and Blizzard is going to great lengths to portray him as an absolute monster. But I’m a big fan of THIS Garrosh, the one who isn’t concerned about world domination or wiping cities off the map, but just sticking it to Varian and being a general pain in the ass.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Too</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-too/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 08:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-too/</guid><description>Still the highlight of the expansion so far, in my opinion.
Let’s be honest. How many of us re-did this quest, over and over again, just to repeatedly wallop Varian in his giant chin? Who could possibly resist??
Headcanon: Garrosh sitting down in his throne room with a paper and clipboard.
On the left-hand side of the page: Strong new allies. Much-needed boost to the Horde’s ranks. New culture and knowledge that will strengthen the Horde.</description></item><item><title>Sated</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/sated/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 10:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/sated/</guid><description>Whoa, whoa, where did 2013 come from? It totally snuck up and [Ambushed] us when we weren’t expecting it. We’ve both been a little busy the last few days with RL travel, festivities and the ever pleasant-but-emotionally-draining family visits, but we’ll be back on pace next week with new stuff!
Also, I don’t know if we’ve ever mentioned this, but we’re always open to ideas and suggestions! Many of our strips are inspired by actual conversations or experiences we’ve had in-game, so if you come across something that you think we absolutely should know about, let us know in a comment, or tweet us at @fromdraenor!</description></item><item><title>He Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</guid><description>Hey, he IS a Prophet, after all. Also, I just need to point this out while Rades is gone: Orcs are currently on the very naughty list.
But the idea of Velen as Greatfather Winter and the faction leaders as little kids was actually all Rades’, so you can’t accuse me of bias in this case. We agreed that it even makes sense, when you think about it – to a draenei who is thousands of years old maybe the rest of us would seem like children.</description></item><item><title>Here We Come A-Wakening</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/here-we-come-a-wakening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 11:08:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/here-we-come-a-wakening/</guid><description>It’s that time of year again! Perhaps you recognize the new and improved Greatfather Winter from last year’s escapades?
I love everything about this strip, but particularly tiny adorable Rades and Vid hanging off of Kovok there. Look for these as our Twitter avatars for a while!
(You may also be amused that an in-depth discussion about Klaxxi anatomical features and the specific societal roles of Klaxxi of different body types preceded the completion of this comic.</description></item><item><title>what</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what/</guid><description>When Heart of Fear LFR came out, Garalon was…how shall we say…an interesting experience. And by interesting I mean painful, excruciating agony. It really became almost a joke that first week, to see how badly an LFR group would fail. And it’s not even necessarily people’s fault! Tag-team pass a kiting debuff back and forth with a stranger? And transmit it through touch? As in, the same mechanic that gave hardcore progression guilds migraines on Heroic Putricide back in ICC?</description></item><item><title>Unique-Equipped</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unique-equipped/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 09:17:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unique-equipped/</guid><description>It really was at Velen’s Book Club.
If you’ve been reading FDWL regularly since around May, you might remember this comic about Millya’s lost tail ring. Inspired by an unfortunate true story, it was around that time that I realized I had lost my wedding rings. We looked everywhere for them, upended everything, and ultimately concluded that they were lost forever. (A process that involved no small amount of hand-wringing and angst, I’ll admit).</description></item><item><title>WTB Real-life Alter Time</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wtb-real-life-alter-time/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wtb-real-life-alter-time/</guid><description>Please accept this pseudo-comic along with my apologies for this week. Last Friday we went to a concert! It was great and we had a great time. But the guy sitting next to Voss was coughing the entire time almost nonstop.
Voss told me darkly as we left, “I sure hope I didn’t catch germs from whatever was making that guy cough up his lung.”
Unfortunately, we both did. I’ll spare you the gory details except to say that I can’t remember having a cold that floored me like this one, ever.</description></item><item><title>Never Trust A Mage</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 11:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</guid><description>You know, dealing with mages was hard enough before Mists, when they’d just portal-troll you by sending you to inconvenient, middle-of-nowhere locations.
Or when they’d summon 5-6 portals on top of one another and you’d have to click and see where you’d end up (Portal Roulette).
Or when they’d start casting you a portal, and then “accidentally” just Teleport themselves back to Orgrimmar, leaving the rest of you stuck in some wretched abyssal lair, miles from home.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Even Blink</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</guid><description>This comic will probably make the most sense to you if you are a mage, and/or if you have been a mage’s victim in this scenario. I have personally tallied my Blink kill count at probably four people. With Antigen it involved a rocket boots incident, with Itanya, we each headed the wrong way. With Thracks it was completely an accident, and with Ibra I swear I thought I saw Jasper Overload and was so excited I could break the chains.</description></item><item><title>Surprisingly Often, Actually</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:44:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</guid><description>From Draenor With Love launched November 1, 2011, which means it’s been an entire year! 😀 I am pretty pleased that we put out a comic each and every week, even when life kicked us around a bit, or when one of us was traveling. Thanks to everyone who’s read our stuff over the past year! We appreciate your visits, your comments, your retweets, all of it!
Also, a special thanks to Dee, Ayms/Mits, and Walks, who gave us awesome guest strips!</description></item><item><title>Kindred Spirits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</guid><description>If there was ONE THING that could bring these eternal rivals/enemies together…
I mean, I’m not even one of these classes and even I appreciate the FREEDOM they must be feeling! Free to summon their mana buns and fel candy any time they please! No longer shackled to the fickle whims of their groupmates, begging, PLEADING for them to please, just please COME OVER HERE AND CLICK ALREADY.
And of course, no longer prone to the excruciating frustration of attempting to summon a mage table – for other people’s benefit – only to have some oaf walk up and start summoning, but then wander away, cancelling the spell BUT still triggering the 10-minute cooldown.</description></item><item><title>Insert Emotion Here</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/insert-emotion-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 09:54:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/insert-emotion-here/</guid><description>When we wrote this joke in our script page three weeks ago, little did we know that the “Sha of ____” joke would become so popular and so prolific before we had a chance to publish. Ah well, live and learn.
There really are unlimited possibilities when it comes to these other, lesser-known Sha. And if they really are manifestation of our emotions, would there not be one for our increasingly weary attitudes about dailies, or the utterly-minor-but-totally-palpable sense of irritation at seeing half a dozen “Wiggling” and “Alluring” crops that you’re going to have to deal with?</description></item><item><title>Straight Outta Halfhill</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/straight-outta-halfhill/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 12:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/straight-outta-halfhill/</guid><description>VEGGIE. BLING.
The best part about this comic is how utterly unfamiliar both Vid and myself are with these themes. We’re about as un-thug-life as you can get.
Anyway…so uh, yeah. About those farms.
We can’t be the only ones making MAD BANK off our daily produce harvests, right? It’s absurd how much these pumpkins, turnips and melons are going for! I mean, I want to level my Way cooking skills, but how can I use these priceless items for lowly FOOD when they could be netting me hundreds of pure, organically-grown profit every day?</description></item><item><title>Priorities</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</guid><description>This is actually a true story. On launch night, we were a few hours in and realized that our Legendary-toting Boomkin was sitting in the Barrens somewhere fishing up Tasty Crapfish and Garbage Trout trying to get realm-first fishing, two of us were hanging out in starter zones furiously battling and taming new pets, and our infamous guild AH tycoon was expanding his financial empire with lucrative Pandaria ore/herb sales.</description></item><item><title>Wish You Were Here</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wish-you-were-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 10:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wish-you-were-here/</guid><description>Today’s comic is a very special guest strip from our amazingly talented friend Walks! The Dread Wastes are so horrifically mutated and ugly (I personally think they feel like the Ghostlands, except on acid) and Walks totally nailed the vintage travel poster look. Thanks Walks! 😀
I think of all the factions in Mists, the Dread Wastes’ Klaxxi are my favorite. Well, okay, maybe the Tillers take the cake but that’s more because I AM ADDICTED TO CULTIVATING MY PRICELESS PRODUCE than any particular love for the faction itself.</description></item><item><title>Masks of Pandaria</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/masks-of-pandaria/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 19:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/masks-of-pandaria/</guid><description>AHHHH IT’S HERE AT LAST
PET BATTLES
NEW QUESTS AND LORE AND STORIES
TRANSMOG GEAR
DUNGEONS
CHALLENGE MODES
MONKS
PANDAREN
Where do you even start??
I’m not going to even TRY to suggest what you should be doing, because it’s ALL amazing and beautiful and completely awesome. I’ve been taking my time leveling, enjoying the scenery, the voice-acting, the unfolding story. It’s all so good! And I’m not even near level cap, or seeing the actual end-game content, or challenge modes, or the new battlegrounds.</description></item><item><title>Tarecohshutup</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tarecohshutup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 08:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tarecohshutup/</guid><description>I knew from folks spending time in the beta that Dragonwrath had a new feature. Yet after 5.0.4 went live, it still scared the bejeebers out of me the first time she talked out loud. I tend to keep my volume up pretty high!
I don’t actually find Tarecgosa annoying in-game, I like the occasional interjections (but I have my sound turned down so low now that I seldom hear all the things she says.</description></item><item><title>Stagway to Heaven</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stagway-to-heaven/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 08:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stagway-to-heaven/</guid><description>Stag stacking was BY FAR one of the coolest and funniest random side effects of patch 5.0.4. Tragically, this bug has since been fixed and you can no longer pile druids to the heavens and walk around as a teetering tower of antlers and fur. Such a shame!
Was it supposed to work like that? Well, probably not. But my gosh, was it hilarious. Ah well, R.I.P. stag stacking.
If you never got the chance to see it in action, here’s a Youtube video.</description></item><item><title>Everything is New Again</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/everything-is-new-again/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/everything-is-new-again/</guid><description>Patch 5.0.4 is here and there’s so many exciting things to check out! Account-wide mounts! New talent systems! AoE looting! Revamped Scarlet Monastery, Scholomance and Ragefire Chasm! And there’s even apparently a new ferocious Darkmoon Rabbit world boss owning fools out at the Darkmoon Faire? I haven’t seen this fellow myself yet, but I’ve heard the hilarious horror stories.
The world (of Warcraft) is suddenly a very new and thrilling place to be, and I love it.</description></item><item><title>Tides of War</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tides-of-war/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tides-of-war/</guid><description>Cross-faction friendships may be unorthodox, but they certainly aren’t unheard of. Jaina and Thrall have been friends since before he started calling himself Go’el. Asric and Jadaar are a pair of lesser-known but still significant “friends,” a blood elf and a draenei who seem to love to hate each other. Game mechanics prevent us from communicating with each other and they do an excellent job of keeping us divided. Ignorance breeds contempt and fear, and it’s easier to attack and kill an enemy that is strange and foreign to you.</description></item><item><title>Player Versus Panda</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/player-versus-panda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/player-versus-panda/</guid><description>Have you seen the Mists of Pandaria trailer yet? If not, WHY NOT?
Seriously though. It’s no wonder they’re scared. This invincible ninja bear just flew out of the mists, kicking their ass, parrying their combined attacks…
Oh, and also, he’s level 90.
IT’S PVP GANKFESTS IN STRANGLETHORN VALE ALL OVER AGAIN, OH GOD RUN AWAY</description></item><item><title>Not a Chance, Thrall</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-a-chance-thrall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 08:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-a-chance-thrall/</guid><description>Seriously dude, we all know why this is a bad idea.
Speaking of orc babies, Vid brought up an interesting question while doing the art – what color skin would the baby of a green-skinned orc and a brown-skinned orc have? We settled on sort of an olive complexion, but only time will tell!
As for Thrall and Aggra’s kid? It’d be nice if it were a girl orc, who goes on to accomplish great things.</description></item><item><title>There Will Be Blood</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</guid><description>From a recent Mists beta build: Glyph of Gushing Wound.
WTF is it with WARRIOR glyphs in Mists? Cripes. Lighting themselves on fire, lightning strikes, flocks of crows, and now MORE BLOOD? Blizz is sure giving them some pretty fun cosmetic options!
Also, these might seriously be my favorite type of strip. I don’t know if Vid was quite as big a fan of this particular one though.
July 24</description></item><item><title>Did You Think We Had Forgotten</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/did-you-think-we-had-forgotten/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 08:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/did-you-think-we-had-forgotten/</guid><description>Did you think we had forgotten?
Did you think we had forgiven?
Yes, that’s right, Critter Kill Squad achievement. And yes, we definitely remember your gleeful experiments into finding out just how big a creature you could inhale.
Oh, there will be a RECKONING, CREEPY CRATE! Your days are numbered! When Mists of Pandaria comes out, your victims will finally be able to fight back. Prepare yourself, Crate, for the terrible vengeance of the CRITTERS!</description></item><item><title>Seriously, Just Buy One Already</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/seriously-just-buy-one-already/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 09:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/seriously-just-buy-one-already/</guid><description>More like “Hour of Waiting For Thrall To Run The Entire Stupid Way in Ghost Wolf Form”, right?
Anyway, we never DO find out what happens to Thrall’s horse in Escape from Durnholde. Everyone else in Old Hillsbrad seemed destined for big things – Kel’Thuzad, Herod, Thrall himself, Old Blanchy – so wouldn’t it be funny if the horse also had some great destiny?
And when you think “when in history would a SURPRISE HORSE be absolutely perfect?</description></item><item><title>Just Not the Same</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/just-not-the-same/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 11:22:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/just-not-the-same/</guid><description>Cataclysm’s general removal of group quests and elite mobs sure has made questing a lot easier, but man, Nagrand just does not feel the same anymore.
For example, take the final “bosses” of Nesingwary’s slaughter quests, Bach’lor, Banthar and Gutripper. These formerly-elite beasts always felt like the perfect foes to wrap up the questline – too strong to just take on without some strategy, but definitely soloable if you put some thought and effort into it.</description></item><item><title>Ahn’Qiraj Awkwardness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ahnqiraj-awkwardness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 08:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ahnqiraj-awkwardness/</guid><description>(If you got the reference already, high-five.)</description></item><item><title>Yak in Business</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yak-in-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 09:57:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yak-in-business/</guid><description>Disappointment was high on the Mists beta this week, as the price of the Grand Expedition Yak skyrocketed to 120,000 gold. If you think about it though, the price hike makes total sense! The ethereals aren’t the sort of people to let this kind of potential profit slip through their bandage-fingers. And besides, with the yak’s portable reforger making their Orgrimmar/Stormwind services obsolete, they’d actually be losing money!
Ethereal interference aside, have you SEEN how much stuff is on one of these yaks?</description></item><item><title>Well Read</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/well-read/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 08:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/well-read/</guid><description>When we did the “Ring of Lost” strip, a few different people were intrigued at the idea of Velen’s Book Club. So consider today’s comic a bit of a follow-up!
Actually, there’s almost enough readable books in WoW that you COULD have a book club! You’ve got the Crawgol’s Silithid Field Guide (The Authoritotal Handbook)…the list goes on and on.
Personally, some of my favorite books are the ones that can be found during the Death Knight starter zone.</description></item><item><title>Glyph of Ireworks</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/glyph-of-ireworks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 09:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/glyph-of-ireworks/</guid><description>It may come as no surprise to you that I absolutely adore a good pun. And, I say with absolute shame pride that this is a true story, upon hearing of Mists’ Glyph of Fireworks.
Judging from how people on Twitter reacted, I think Vid’s reaction in the last panel is one many people can relate with. What can I say? Those moments are just too funny. In fact, when my D&amp;amp;D group gets together to play, I have a private goal to produce at least one huge pun/groan moment each session.</description></item><item><title>Rage of the Friendlands</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 07:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</guid><description>While folks were helping me out to get my legendary, it occurred to me that I wanted to do something to thank them. You know, apart from just – thanking them. Initially I was going to do little character portraits for everyone, but as the list of people who were involved grew, I started to understand that might be a bit unwieldy.
So instead, Rades and I put our heads together and came up with the idea of a strip featuring all the people.</description></item><item><title>Limit Break</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/limit-break/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 08:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/limit-break/</guid><description>This week’s strip is a guest strip from Ayms and Mits, who you may know from their great webcomic, Fourth Wall! They’re no longer doing new strips, but they heard we needed some help this week and came out of “retirement” to lend us a hand. Thanks guys! Fourth Wall isn’t online anymore, but you can find Ayms’ artwork at her sketchblog – do go check out her stuff!
We should be back on schedule this week, so thanks again to Dee, Ayms and Mits who really came through for us when we needed a hand.</description></item><item><title>There’s Something Different About You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/theres-something-different-about-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 08:31:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/theres-something-different-about-you/</guid><description>Today’s comic is a special guest strip by our WONDERFUL and TALENTED friend Dee, who came through AMAZINGLY, considering she had only like half a day’s notice! You can check out her WoW blog at @mainfloortank!
(She really, really likes elves.)
THANKS DEE! You really helped us out. Much love!
Unfortunately, the reason Vid couldn’t finish this week’s strip was due to a sudden family emergency. Send some good thoughts and wishes her way, as she and her family could really use them.</description></item><item><title>Ring of Lost</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ring-of-lost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 08:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ring-of-lost/</guid><description>Ever wonder if WoW characters have the same day-to-day problems that plague us in real life? In this case, Vid had a minor crisis this week regarding a lost wedding ring, which sounds a lot like a quest, only there’s no handy directional guide in real life, and no reward other than a tremendous sense of relief.
Anyway, we thought that, you know, for the amount of travel and continent-hopping the average WoW hero does, remembering where you put something down must be a tremendous hassle.</description></item><item><title>The Lord of Terror</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-lord-of-terror/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-lord-of-terror/</guid><description>Like everyone else on the planet, we’ve sunk some time into Diablo III so far, and it’s a blast. So far I’m greatly enjoying the Wizard (LASER FREEZE RAY) and the Demon Hunter is also a lot of fun. I’ve played around with the Monk a bit, but I don’t think I enjoy the melee playstyle. I’ll stick with my blasters.
Vid, of course, is playing a Wizard. Shocking, I know!</description></item><item><title>From Draenor with Mischief</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/from-draenor-with-mischief/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 09:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/from-draenor-with-mischief/</guid><description>This is the special prize strip Cymre of Bubbles of Mischief won by taking 1st place in the Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt!
Congratulations Cymre! We hope you enjoy your guest appearance!
Cymre maintains an amazing gallery of World of Warcraft rare spawns on her blog – aka, “Silver Dragons” – so we thought, hey, what better way to celebrate her egg-hunting victory than with some Silver Dragon love of her own?</description></item><item><title>Our Poor, Tired Feet</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-poor-tired-feet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 05:19:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-poor-tired-feet/</guid><description>The Calgary Expo was on the weekend, and, well, it was an…interesting experience.
There was waiting. There were photos with Patrick Stewart and autographs from Wil Wheaton. There was more waiting. There was the chance to meet Fyreuni of Daily Quests.
Oh, and there was a near-riot when the Expo shut the doors because they had oversold and weren’t letting in any more attendees, regardless of pre-purchased tickets, “we have a scheduled photoshoot with Patrick Stewart”, or “I just stepped outside for a smoke and my family is still inside!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 09:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</guid><description>HEY MURADIN PUT A BIRD ON IT
Like we said last week…Warrior glyphs in Mists = THE COOLEST.
Some news about the next few weeks! This weekend, we’ll be attending a Comic Expo in Calgary! Excitement! Our strip next week will be something based off the Expo, we hope. Then, the week after that we plan on presenting the special guest strip for Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt! So keep your eyes peeled!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</guid><description>A Glyph that causes a lightning strike?
…I have a sudden urge to play a warrior in Mists.
Seriously though, it’s terrific that Blizzard is giving us all these new fun cosmetic glyphs. They’re little touches, but damn are they cool.
My personal favorite so far? That would be Glyph of the Geist. BECAUSE GEISTS ARE AWESOME.
(In other news, I think Vid is going to revolt if I make her draw Garrosh again.</description></item><item><title>For This Moment Alone</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-this-moment-alone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 07:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-this-moment-alone/</guid><description>It’s a good thing hitting the button on LFR Ultraxion isn’t necessary to beat the fight, because if it was, I don’t think a single LFR group would ever kill him. Like, seriously, it’s NOT THAT HARD, PEOPLE. PUSH THE DAMN BUTTON. IT’S RIGHT THERE IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR SCREEN, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
But no. It’s enough to make a healer tear their hair out in frustration.
In other news, here is a snippet of the From Draenor creative process at work:</description></item><item><title>The Legacy of Kip Diskin</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-legacy-of-kip-diskin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 08:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-legacy-of-kip-diskin/</guid><description>The new glyphs on the Mists of Pandaria beta sound amazing. Trust me, this is not the only glyph feature you’ll be seeing on From Draenor.
I was actually surprised to see an Orca glyph, since they seem more suitable for Northrend than the lush, temperate zones of Pandaria. Wouldn’t it be funny if there were a huge assortment of minor glyphs that changed the appearance of druid travel and aquatic forms?</description></item><item><title>Not Who We Expected</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-who-we-expected/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 12:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-who-we-expected/</guid><description>As everyone knows by now, Garrosh Hellscream will be the boss of Mists of Pandaria’s final content patch, and we take him down in an exciting-sounding “Siege of Orgrimmar.”
Now, there’s a lot of time between now and then, but I have to say…given what we’ve seen of Sylvanas in Cataclysm – being quite dastardly towards the Worgen during their starting zone, raising unwilling humans into new Forsaken and conscripting them into her forces, and her cold and callous treatment towards Koltira – I really expected her to be the Horde leader we’d end up killing as a raid boss.</description></item><item><title>Our Unsung Hero</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-unsung-hero/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-unsung-hero/</guid><description>From Draenor presents, Real Azerothian Geniuses.
Today we salute you, Mr. Lamp Hum Sound Creator Guy.
You work tirelessly to capture the tranquil sound of a summer breeze or the frantic buzz of fireflies trapped in a jar, just to make our weary trek through the wild a little less scary.
In the darkest of nights, we pause on our journey, wondering if that subtle rustling we just heard was one of your masterpieces singing its peaceful song of illumination, or a horrible flesh-eating zombie lurking in the bushes.</description></item><item><title>Resurrection Sickness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</guid><description>Everyone’s been buzzing about the new &amp;amp; improved Scroll of Resurrection, and why not? A free level 80, realm transfer AND faction transfer? Just for coming back to the game? Yeah, it’s no wonder the new Scroll offer has been so popular.
Of course, we all know what’s REALLY behind the Scroll frenzy.
SPECTRAL MOUNTS.
Awww yeah. That’s the kind of incentive that gets RESULTS.
PS: Did you know Stormwind really does have a War Room?</description></item><item><title>Darkmoon Foul</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkmoon-foul/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkmoon-foul/</guid><description>Seriously, does no one else at the Faire raise an eyebrow at the fact that each month, Kerri Hicks is collecting thousands of bloody ears? I mean, the icon is an ear, and Blizzard has a tendency to encourage ear-collecting, ever since Diablo. What the heck is she DOING with all of these bloody trophies??
It seems such a disproportionate reward, too – you bring back proof of 250(!) kills and you get 10 little tickets.</description></item><item><title>To the Ground</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 09:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</guid><description>The idea of class abilities repeating endlessly was actually really hard to make a comic for, because there were so many awesome options! The mental images of Healing Rain, Hurricane or Fan of Knives duplicating over and over again are too funny.
In the end, we decided to go with a theme preferred by Vid: CAKES (you can never have too much cake, according to her) and dead Warlocks. Also, the opportunity to have a sea of cakes was too great to pass up.</description></item><item><title>Every Day I’m Transmogging</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/every-day-im-transmogging/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:09:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/every-day-im-transmogging/</guid><description>This may be my favourite FDWL in the history of ever. (I know, we’ve only done less than 20 strips but even so!)
Usually the way we make strips is one of us has an idea and pitches it to the other, then we start to brain-storm and perhaps refine or change a few things. Sometimes the strip is fully formed, as when Rades presented this one to me like so:</description></item><item><title>Your Racial Leader is Thinking About You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-racial-leader-is-thinking-about-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 09:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-racial-leader-is-thinking-about-you/</guid><description>It occurred to Vid and I yesterday that perhaps we should have saved the comic with the NAKED ORC for our Valentine’s Day update. Apparently we are unable to read calendars.
We figured we needed to do SOMETHING love-themed for this week – after all, the comic IS From Draenor With LOVE!
Well, who better to feature on our special Valentine’s Day card than another local from Draenor, the Warchief himself!</description></item><item><title>Maximum Cupacity</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/maximum-cupacity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 10:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/maximum-cupacity/</guid><description>I really, really wish we had ampm stores in Canada. I would totally buy those cups! The art on them looks great, and they’d be nice collectibles to own.
The three “rejected” cup ideas we came up with for this strip should all be sadly familiar to most WoW players. I don’t think anyone will EVER forget Sindragosa’s famous line, and Neptulon’s PUUUURE WATERRRR line from Throne of the Tides has quickly become a fan favorite.</description></item><item><title>Squeaky Green</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/squeaky-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/squeaky-green/</guid><description>When we heard that there would be no Blizzcon this year, Vid and I knew we had to cover it somehow. We ran down the list of Blizzcon cliches (true or not), one of which was the inevitable pungent result of cramming hundreds of bodies into a cramped, enclosed convention center.
Then, somehow, it became this.
To say Vid was mortified when I sent her the script would be an understatement.</description></item><item><title>Choose Wisely</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choose-wisely/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choose-wisely/</guid><description>Yes, we know Droids and Hutts are not actually available player races in SWTOR. Too bad – I would totally be a Hutt so I could use awful HUTT YOUR MOUTH and HUTT UP puns and make everyone hate me.
Also, I wish I could say we were joking when talking about Vid’s overpowering love for anyone blue. Let’s just say that panel 4 isn’t entirely off the mark. 😉</description></item><item><title>Magic Touch</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/magic-touch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/magic-touch/</guid><description>…Then I finally found a suitable mold for the chassis or I thought it was a suitable chassis mold but actually they meant it for a gyrocopter and it wasn’t quite right so I tried to convince a friend to model for it but he wouldn’t because he said, and I quote, “Your inventions have a way of proving fatal to people who agree to test them,” I ask you, is that fair?</description></item><item><title>Thrall, Aspect of Derp</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/thrall-aspect-of-derp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 11:04:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/thrall-aspect-of-derp/</guid><description>In the final fight of Dragon Soul, players have to fight Deathwing while leaping back and forth between a few different islands, carried by Thrall’s winds.
Unfortunately, Thrall has some…issues…and will occasionally NOT give a player the wind buff, which sends them plummeting to their death in the churning Maelstrom below. This usually results in much anger and frustration, and usually a wipe.
Is he just trolling us? Or is he just really, really incompetent?</description></item><item><title>Damn You, Murglesnout</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/damn-you-murglesnout/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 09:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/damn-you-murglesnout/</guid><description>Oh, Murglesnout. Fisher’s bane. So plentiful. So abundant.
So utterly, completely worthless.
True, Blizzard did eventually add in a Cooking recipe so that the dreaded Murglesnout wasn’t COMPLETELY pointless. But it’s TOO LATE! Even now, the mere sight of THIS TERRIBLE FISH fills me with rage. MURGLESNOUT!
…however, it really does make a fun “gift” to give friends.
If you want to MAKE THEM ANGRY!
MURGLESNOUT!</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Four</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-four/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 12:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-four/</guid><description>I wasn’t actually sure how Rades intended to end our little odyssey. Needless to say, my jaw dropped when I got this far in the script. It’s great for him, though, because he gets to show his mad genius! Vid, who has no compunction about blasting a rocket straight into Ironforge or any other environs, is a little uneasy when it comes to FrankenWinter. But ultimately, she decides that it’s better to let a cyborg version of Greatfather Winter do all of the Winter’s Veil stuff – so that she and Rades don’t have to.</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Three</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-three/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 02:40:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-three/</guid><description>Part 3 of 4! Rades and Vid do their best to fill the late Greatfather Winter’s shoes – in their own, unique fashion, of course.
Locations where Vid is now no longer permitted to operate: The Exodar AND Ironforge.
Hey, isn’t that rocket in panel 4 the same type as the one that blew up Greatfather Winter? Oh well, what those Druids don’t know, won’t hurt them…hopefully.
Next week’s Part 4 will come out a few days after Christmas, so consider it our special (belated) gift to you for reading!</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-two/</guid><description>The saga continues! Oh no, poor Greatfather Winter!
Vid did an awesome job with the expressions in this strip, I think you’ll all agree. I’m now using the “Sad Rades” face as my avatar, and I can’t even look at panel 3 without laughing.
There was some debate about which Greatfather Winter to use – the dwarven Alliance version, or the orcish Horde version! In the end though, we decided to go with the dwarf, to include more races.</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 07:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-one/</guid><description>It’s a cliche often used that “the journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.” In this case, a journey of approximately 17,500 miles per hour begins with a single rocket and a large explosion.
This is how engineers work.
Rades and I wanted to do something a little special and different for the upcoming holiday season, as well as try our hands at a mini story-arc! So expect this story to run for pretty much the rest of the month, until we reach its epic conclusion.</description></item><item><title>Transmogalypse</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/transmogalypse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/transmogalypse/</guid><description>Has there ever been a feature more eagerly anticipated than Transmogrification? If there is, I sure haven’t seen it. So many options! So much potential for nostalgia! The future has arrived, and its name is World of Dresscraft.
Of course, for every person who can’t wait to dig out their old Tier 1 or Tier 0.5 sets, there’s someone who is going to gleefully turn their fearsome, godly “I’m-About-to-Kill-Deathwing” armor into a neon nightmare Burning Crusade clown suit.</description></item><item><title>For Science, You Monster</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</guid><description>Hey guys, Vid’s been crit by real life this week, so send her warm thoughts because until she’s back, you’re stuck with my terrible WoW Model Viewer comics!
Last night Blizzard released an updated Mists of Pandaria talent calculator, complete with new baseline talents. One of the new baseline Warlock talents was Demonic Portal, as pictured above. Needless to say, the Portal comparisons were instant and furious! So I figured it was an appropriate time to break out ye old Undercity Companion Cube image from this year’s Love is in the Air seasonal event.</description></item><item><title>Yellow Angry Man</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yellow-angry-man/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yellow-angry-man/</guid><description>If you’ve played a paladin at level 85 for any length of time, hopefully this requires no explanation. For those of you who haven’t, well. Perhaps you play a melee DPS. You’re at the boss’ feet, stabbing/slicing/cutting (or whatever else it is that you melee folks do).
You hear an odd grunt.
“ARRRRGH!”
“GRRRRRR!”
“RRRRRAAA!”
This, my friends, is the Yellow, Angry Man. His anger knows no bounds. Likewise, his yellow-ness is unsurpassed.</description></item><item><title>Grudge Match</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/grudge-match/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/grudge-match/</guid><description>When the Pet Battle System was announced at Blizzcon, everyone had a wide range of reactions. Were they serious? Was this an elaborate joke? How much more like Pokemon could this possibly be? But without question, the most important possibility was the potential hilarity of absurd pet matchups, such as Alliance Balloon vs. Horde Balloon, or Enchanted Broom vs. Magic Lamp. Can you say EXCITEMENT??
Personally, I’m banking on my Toxic Wasteling.</description></item><item><title>Rare Spawn</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rare-spawn-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 06:21:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rare-spawn-3/</guid><description>I’m not especially good at keeping secrets. So the fact that you are only seeing this, now, after over a month of loving work is nothing short of a miracle. The idea of doing a webcomic wasn’t a new one for Rades and I – we’d talked about it before, sometime last year – but the time wasn’t right. We were on different pages about what a comic should be (I was thinking epic story, he was thinking gag) and so we just shelved it.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/about-us/</guid><description>Stacey is the author of Manalicious, a World of Warcraft blog about mages, guild leading, and heroic internet dragons. She is a freelance artist/illustrator who likes digital painting, making tiny Sculpey figurines, and drawing with Staedtler pigment liners (0.5, thanks!) She also enjoys writing, reading a wide variety of books, video games, and baking things for other people to eat. She lives with her husband Vosskah and a large silly chocolate Labrador Retriever named Rufus.</description></item><item><title>Characters</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/characters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/characters/</guid><description>Rades Class: Hunter Affiliation: Horde Race: Orc Left Horde army after attack on Theramore. Engineer. Adores beasts. Unlucky. Vidyala Class: Paladin Affiliation: Alliance Race: Draenei Battle healer. Military upbringing. Engineer. Doesn&amp;#8217;t mind a good brawl. Wrathion Class: Black Prince Affiliation: Blacktalon Race: Black Dragon Only untainted member of the Black Dragonflight. Confident. Personal crusade to kill all other black dragons.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/contact-us/</guid><description>Have a question or need to get in touch with us? We can be reached at:
fromdraenor@gmail.com
Twitter: twitter.com/fromdraenor
If you have an issue with this site, please contact Sean on Twitter @Llanion</description></item><item><title>Patreon</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/patreon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/patreon/</guid><description>We now have a Patreon account! If you’d like to support us, and maybe pick up some cool artwork, wallpapers and other treats, please go to patreon.com/fromdraenor and check things out!
Thank you!
Rades &amp;amp; Vid</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy &amp; Terms of Service</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/privacy/</guid><description>Please read this page carefully, as it explains what data is collected from you and in what ways it is intended to be used, as well as what rights you are giving up by submitting that data.
Definitions Third-Party Services Rights Assignment Data is Public Facing Information we collect from you directly GDPR Explicit Third-Party Sharing Intended Audience (No Children) Cookie Policy Definitions The terms &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo; are used as a convention.</description></item><item><title>Rades</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/author/rades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/author/rades/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Sean</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/author/sean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/author/sean/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Vidyala</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/author/vidyala/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/author/vidyala/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>