<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Varian on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/varian/</link><description>Recent content in Varian on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/varian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Proudmoore “Problem”</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</guid><description>A lot of people think Jaina has this terrible reputation regarding the men in her life, that she has “terrible taste in men”, or that she breaks guys’ hearts and/or makes them go crazy. This is utter nonsense. The problem isn’t with Jaina, the problem is that the men in her life are just plain jerks.
Have you actually LISTENED to the crap these guys say? It’s pretty sad when Garrosh of all people has treated her with more dignity and respect than her so-called close friends.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 12:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</guid><description>The inevitable result of last week’s devious scheme.
(Really, this moment was so amazing, how could we NOT give it the full-comic spotlight it deserves??)
You know, in-game Garrosh is unpleasant and thoroughly unlikeable, and Blizzard is going to great lengths to portray him as an absolute monster. But I’m a big fan of THIS Garrosh, the one who isn’t concerned about world domination or wiping cities off the map, but just sticking it to Varian and being a general pain in the ass.</description></item><item><title>He Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</guid><description>Hey, he IS a Prophet, after all. Also, I just need to point this out while Rades is gone: Orcs are currently on the very naughty list.
But the idea of Velen as Greatfather Winter and the faction leaders as little kids was actually all Rades’, so you can’t accuse me of bias in this case. We agreed that it even makes sense, when you think about it – to a draenei who is thousands of years old maybe the rest of us would seem like children.</description></item><item><title>Surprisingly Often, Actually</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:44:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</guid><description>From Draenor With Love launched November 1, 2011, which means it’s been an entire year! 😀 I am pretty pleased that we put out a comic each and every week, even when life kicked us around a bit, or when one of us was traveling. Thanks to everyone who’s read our stuff over the past year! We appreciate your visits, your comments, your retweets, all of it!
Also, a special thanks to Dee, Ayms/Mits, and Walks, who gave us awesome guest strips!</description></item><item><title>There Will Be Blood</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</guid><description>From a recent Mists beta build: Glyph of Gushing Wound.
WTF is it with WARRIOR glyphs in Mists? Cripes. Lighting themselves on fire, lightning strikes, flocks of crows, and now MORE BLOOD? Blizz is sure giving them some pretty fun cosmetic options!
Also, these might seriously be my favorite type of strip. I don’t know if Vid was quite as big a fan of this particular one though.
July 24</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 09:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</guid><description>HEY MURADIN PUT A BIRD ON IT
Like we said last week…Warrior glyphs in Mists = THE COOLEST.
Some news about the next few weeks! This weekend, we’ll be attending a Comic Expo in Calgary! Excitement! Our strip next week will be something based off the Expo, we hope. Then, the week after that we plan on presenting the special guest strip for Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt! So keep your eyes peeled!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</guid><description>A Glyph that causes a lightning strike?
…I have a sudden urge to play a warrior in Mists.
Seriously though, it’s terrific that Blizzard is giving us all these new fun cosmetic glyphs. They’re little touches, but damn are they cool.
My personal favorite so far? That would be Glyph of the Geist. BECAUSE GEISTS ARE AWESOME.
(In other news, I think Vid is going to revolt if I make her draw Garrosh again.</description></item><item><title>Resurrection Sickness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</guid><description>Everyone’s been buzzing about the new &amp;amp; improved Scroll of Resurrection, and why not? A free level 80, realm transfer AND faction transfer? Just for coming back to the game? Yeah, it’s no wonder the new Scroll offer has been so popular.
Of course, we all know what’s REALLY behind the Scroll frenzy.
SPECTRAL MOUNTS.
Awww yeah. That’s the kind of incentive that gets RESULTS.
PS: Did you know Stormwind really does have a War Room?</description></item></channel></rss>