<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mages on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/mages/</link><description>Recent content in mages on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 11:23:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/mages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Never Trust A Mage</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 11:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</guid><description>You know, dealing with mages was hard enough before Mists, when they’d just portal-troll you by sending you to inconvenient, middle-of-nowhere locations.
Or when they’d summon 5-6 portals on top of one another and you’d have to click and see where you’d end up (Portal Roulette).
Or when they’d start casting you a portal, and then “accidentally” just Teleport themselves back to Orgrimmar, leaving the rest of you stuck in some wretched abyssal lair, miles from home.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Even Blink</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</guid><description>This comic will probably make the most sense to you if you are a mage, and/or if you have been a mage’s victim in this scenario. I have personally tallied my Blink kill count at probably four people. With Antigen it involved a rocket boots incident, with Itanya, we each headed the wrong way. With Thracks it was completely an accident, and with Ibra I swear I thought I saw Jasper Overload and was so excited I could break the chains.</description></item><item><title>Kindred Spirits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</guid><description>If there was ONE THING that could bring these eternal rivals/enemies together…
I mean, I’m not even one of these classes and even I appreciate the FREEDOM they must be feeling! Free to summon their mana buns and fel candy any time they please! No longer shackled to the fickle whims of their groupmates, begging, PLEADING for them to please, just please COME OVER HERE AND CLICK ALREADY.
And of course, no longer prone to the excruciating frustration of attempting to summon a mage table – for other people’s benefit – only to have some oaf walk up and start summoning, but then wander away, cancelling the spell BUT still triggering the 10-minute cooldown.</description></item><item><title>Everything is New Again</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/everything-is-new-again/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/everything-is-new-again/</guid><description>Patch 5.0.4 is here and there’s so many exciting things to check out! Account-wide mounts! New talent systems! AoE looting! Revamped Scarlet Monastery, Scholomance and Ragefire Chasm! And there’s even apparently a new ferocious Darkmoon Rabbit world boss owning fools out at the Darkmoon Faire? I haven’t seen this fellow myself yet, but I’ve heard the hilarious horror stories.
The world (of Warcraft) is suddenly a very new and thrilling place to be, and I love it.</description></item><item><title>To the Ground</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 09:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</guid><description>The idea of class abilities repeating endlessly was actually really hard to make a comic for, because there were so many awesome options! The mental images of Healing Rain, Hurricane or Fan of Knives duplicating over and over again are too funny.
In the end, we decided to go with a theme preferred by Vid: CAKES (you can never have too much cake, according to her) and dead Warlocks. Also, the opportunity to have a sea of cakes was too great to pass up.</description></item></channel></rss>