<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Millya on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/millya/</link><description>Recent content in Millya on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 07:52:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/millya/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Talent Specialization</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/talent-specialization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 07:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/talent-specialization/</guid><description>Suddenly, heroic raiding guilds start prowling the Warcraft fan art forums for recruits.
(And how long would it be before Razer released a special “Gaming Tablet” for the truly hardcore?)
I’m really glad someone else in my guild handles the Celestial buffs on Twin Consorts. I’ve glanced at the constellation diagrams/paths once or twice, and immediately came to the conclusion that it was something I completely and absolutely never wanted to do.</description></item><item><title>Blizzcon Badges!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</guid><description>Do you need a little something to set you apart from the crowd at Blizzcon? Would you like a small piece of art to call your own and remember all the good times you had at the convention? I’ve been painting up just the thing!
These little paintings are painted on thick, high-quality Arches watercolour paper with Winsor &amp;amp; Newton watercolours. In a world of art that’s increasingly digital, I find I am loving going back to my roots and painting with brushes and pigments again.</description></item><item><title>Double Digits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</guid><description>I imagine tanks everywhere are shaking their heads in grim recognition of this scene. After all, how many times have they turned, scanning for the next pack of mobs to pull, only to hear that dreaded “FWOOSH” sound as an enormous ball of fire hurtles past them? Because EVERYONE KNOWS you can’t just WASTE A HOT STREAK PROC.
MAGES.
However, Vid’s lightning-fast DPS instincts served her well when it came to get Blizzcon tickets, netting her an unbelievably low 33rd in queue!</description></item><item><title>The Scarlet Letters</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-scarlet-letters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 08:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-scarlet-letters/</guid><description>WE REGRET NOTHING</description></item><item><title>Blingtrolled</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blingtrolled/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blingtrolled/</guid><description>Yet another reason why Engineering is the best profession!
Seriously, there’s few things funnier than plopping down Blingtron in a hard-to-reach spot in a well-populated area and sitting back to watch people go MAD as they try to find that elusive free loot. My personal favorites include trees in Halfhill, the upper balconies in Pandalaran, or in the normally-inaccessible catwalk in Orgrimmar’s front auction house.
Thanks to Raijair, Kalbeari, Hachidori, Dhevon and Korrath for the use of your likenesses this week!</description></item><item><title>Pretty Much a Constant Thing With Us</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pretty-much-a-constant-thing-with-us/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pretty-much-a-constant-thing-with-us/</guid><description>Hey, this feels familiar, doesn’t it?
Anyway, WE’RE BACK! /blows kisses from amidst a sea of fluttering rose petals
The time off has been good to us and we’re ready to leap headfirst into all the exciting new 5.2 stuff! Let’s just hope we can remember how to do this comic thing! (Confession, it took me nearly 10 minutes to remember the WordPress login info.)
Now yes, we know that Heart of Fear is technically old content now, but we had this script in the queue and we can’t just WASTE it!</description></item><item><title>Rested Experience</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</guid><description>Well, it finally happened: Vid’s drawing arm fell off. Like, literally, just sketching away and plop! it’s a scene right out of the Undercity. It’s all good though, she’s out talking to Mekkatorque right now about a steam-powered mechanical replacement. She says it’s no big deal, but as a veteran engineer, I remain skeptical.
But joking aside, the unfortunate reality is we’re starting to feel a bit of burnout, and there’s been some real-life commitments that are rearing their unavoidable and time-consuming heads.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Even Blink</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</guid><description>This comic will probably make the most sense to you if you are a mage, and/or if you have been a mage’s victim in this scenario. I have personally tallied my Blink kill count at probably four people. With Antigen it involved a rocket boots incident, with Itanya, we each headed the wrong way. With Thracks it was completely an accident, and with Ibra I swear I thought I saw Jasper Overload and was so excited I could break the chains.</description></item><item><title>Surprisingly Often, Actually</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:44:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</guid><description>From Draenor With Love launched November 1, 2011, which means it’s been an entire year! 😀 I am pretty pleased that we put out a comic each and every week, even when life kicked us around a bit, or when one of us was traveling. Thanks to everyone who’s read our stuff over the past year! We appreciate your visits, your comments, your retweets, all of it!
Also, a special thanks to Dee, Ayms/Mits, and Walks, who gave us awesome guest strips!</description></item><item><title>Tarecohshutup</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tarecohshutup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 08:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tarecohshutup/</guid><description>I knew from folks spending time in the beta that Dragonwrath had a new feature. Yet after 5.0.4 went live, it still scared the bejeebers out of me the first time she talked out loud. I tend to keep my volume up pretty high!
I don’t actually find Tarecgosa annoying in-game, I like the occasional interjections (but I have my sound turned down so low now that I seldom hear all the things she says.</description></item><item><title>Rage of the Friendlands</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 07:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</guid><description>While folks were helping me out to get my legendary, it occurred to me that I wanted to do something to thank them. You know, apart from just – thanking them. Initially I was going to do little character portraits for everyone, but as the list of people who were involved grew, I started to understand that might be a bit unwieldy.
So instead, Rades and I put our heads together and came up with the idea of a strip featuring all the people.</description></item><item><title>Every Day I’m Transmogging</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/every-day-im-transmogging/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:09:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/every-day-im-transmogging/</guid><description>This may be my favourite FDWL in the history of ever. (I know, we’ve only done less than 20 strips but even so!)
Usually the way we make strips is one of us has an idea and pitches it to the other, then we start to brain-storm and perhaps refine or change a few things. Sometimes the strip is fully formed, as when Rades presented this one to me like so:</description></item></channel></rss>