<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Velen on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/velen/</link><description>Recent content in Velen on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/velen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>He Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</guid><description>Hey, he IS a Prophet, after all. Also, I just need to point this out while Rades is gone: Orcs are currently on the very naughty list.
But the idea of Velen as Greatfather Winter and the faction leaders as little kids was actually all Rades’, so you can’t accuse me of bias in this case. We agreed that it even makes sense, when you think about it – to a draenei who is thousands of years old maybe the rest of us would seem like children.</description></item><item><title>Well Read</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/well-read/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 08:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/well-read/</guid><description>When we did the “Ring of Lost” strip, a few different people were intrigued at the idea of Velen’s Book Club. So consider today’s comic a bit of a follow-up!
Actually, there’s almost enough readable books in WoW that you COULD have a book club! You’ve got the Crawgol’s Silithid Field Guide (The Authoritotal Handbook)…the list goes on and on.
Personally, some of my favorite books are the ones that can be found during the Death Knight starter zone.</description></item><item><title>Resurrection Sickness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</guid><description>Everyone’s been buzzing about the new &amp;amp; improved Scroll of Resurrection, and why not? A free level 80, realm transfer AND faction transfer? Just for coming back to the game? Yeah, it’s no wonder the new Scroll offer has been so popular.
Of course, we all know what’s REALLY behind the Scroll frenzy.
SPECTRAL MOUNTS.
Awww yeah. That’s the kind of incentive that gets RESULTS.
PS: Did you know Stormwind really does have a War Room?</description></item></channel></rss>