<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Comics! on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/comic/</link><description>Recent content in Comics! on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 07:49:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/comic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Siege of Orgrimmar</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-siege-of-orgrimmar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 07:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-siege-of-orgrimmar/</guid><description>Patch 5.4 is almost here! I’m totally pumped, but I’m also dreading it! I want to see the cool new raid content and bosses, but I don’t WANT to kill Nazgrim! I don’t WANT to kill the Paragons!
And I don’t want to kill Garrosh!
(He’s a major From Draenor With Love character, after all!)
Speaking of the comic, this strip marks an important milestone for us. Starting next week, everything is changing!</description></item><item><title>The Real Twelve</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-real-twelve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-real-twelve/</guid><description>Hey, I don’t think it’s too much of a stretch! Rades is an accomplished engineer, he could undoubtedly keep a TARDIS running, and he could accomplish so much with a sonic screwdriver! I think Vid would make a great companion, though she could be the Doctor just as easily.
I did this art awhile ago and thought considering this Sunday’s announcement, using it now would be pretty timely. The opportunity to put Rades in a dapper suit jacket and bow tie was too good to pass up.</description></item><item><title>Dig Dug Bug</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dig-dug-bug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dig-dug-bug/</guid><description>If it’s not a bind-on-account piece of gear to mega-buff alts, a fun vanity item to bust out during killshots, or hilariously unpredictable hearthstone replacements that randomly take you all over Azeroth, WE DON’T WANT IT.</description></item><item><title>Tourist’s Guide to Ihgaluk Crag</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tourists-guide-to-ihgaluk-crag/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 10:27:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tourists-guide-to-ihgaluk-crag/</guid><description>Yet More Things To Do and See While in The Crag:
– Jump So High You Fly Out of The Crag and The Disguise Wears Off and You Splat on The Ground, Not That This Has Ever Happened To Us
– Cleansing Baths in Natural Filth Pools
– Meet the Local Wildlife (And Crush Them Beneath Your Feet)
– Jump Around
– Jump Around
– Jump Around
– Jump Up Jump Up And Get Down</description></item><item><title>Talent Specialization</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/talent-specialization/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2013 07:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/talent-specialization/</guid><description>Suddenly, heroic raiding guilds start prowling the Warcraft fan art forums for recruits.
(And how long would it be before Razer released a special “Gaming Tablet” for the truly hardcore?)
I’m really glad someone else in my guild handles the Celestial buffs on Twin Consorts. I’ve glanced at the constellation diagrams/paths once or twice, and immediately came to the conclusion that it was something I completely and absolutely never wanted to do.</description></item><item><title>Peons Are People Too</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/peons-are-people-too/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 09:12:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/peons-are-people-too/</guid><description>I totally get the Darkspear Rebellion, the disruption of the Kor’kron war engine, the stealing of valuable resources for the upcoming siege on Orgrimmar. That all makes sense. And if we have to take out a few Kor’kron Commanders or Goblin Mercenaries while we’re at it? Sure. No argument here.
But the workers? What did they ever do to us? They’re just laborers! Red-collar working-class civilians. They’re just doing their 9 to 5, cutting up meat, chopping down trees, and suddenly we fly in on our giant cosmic dragons, beat ’em up, blow up their machines, and then take all their stuff.</description></item><item><title>There Are Two Types of People</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-are-two-types-of-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 08:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-are-two-types-of-people/</guid><description>The most difficult thing about this comic is that I had to stop playing “Animal Crossing: New Leaf” long enough to draw it.
If you’re not familiar, ACNL is a kind of life simulator game for the Nintendo 3DS that has been sweeping through the WoW twitter community like a wildfire. I played an earlier Animal Crossing title on the Gamecube back in the day. In terms of gameplay it’s pretty basic: Grow/harvest fruit, plant flowers, laugh at things your neighbours say, fish and catch bugs, dig up fossils, design clothes.</description></item><item><title>Whateverstone is More Like It</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whateverstone-is-more-like-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 12:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whateverstone-is-more-like-it/</guid><description>I’m not sure I know of a character in any book, movie or game who has had their personality and history thrown to the wayside and trampled into the dust as much as Garrosh has this expansion. I mean, in Cataclysm he certainly wasn’t perfect, but he had distinct good points to accompany his flaws, was a good character foil for his mirror image, Varian, and was showing definite signs of growth from his hotheaded, annoying days of being a mad dog yipping at Thrall during Wrath.</description></item><item><title>Can I Keep Him?</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/can-i-keep-him/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/can-i-keep-him/</guid><description>The big evil bad guys in WoW sure do like their pets, don’t they? It seems like every tier there’s at least one boss with special pets, or a boss that is itself a giant pet. Sometimes they’re just there, leaving their connection to the boss up to your imagination, but some, like Magmaw or Rageface/Riplimb, are outright stated to be pets. And some of them are really loved! Shannox loves his little doggies!</description></item><item><title>Nomi No-No</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nomi-no-no/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 09:39:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nomi-no-no/</guid><description>As many Pandaria chefs know, achievement.
However, to become Best Friends you have to go through a ton of cooking dailies with Nomi, where you give him some mundane cooking ingredients each day so he can practice his culinary skills. He then gives you back some Fish Jerky or some other junk.
Most people just sell the stuff to a vendor. But me? I don’t want his crappy food.
SO I DESTROY IT.</description></item><item><title>A Quick AFK</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-quick-afk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 18:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-quick-afk/</guid><description>This week in lieu of a comic we have instead a quick painting I did. I’ve had family stuff come up that I had to deal with, it’s sad but sometimes life wins out. The average comic takes me around five+ hours to draw and unfortunately this week I didn’t have those hours. Back when we started FDWL they used to take me eight! I haven’t gotten that much faster, I have simplified the art significantly though.</description></item><item><title>The Proudmoore “Problem”</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</guid><description>A lot of people think Jaina has this terrible reputation regarding the men in her life, that she has “terrible taste in men”, or that she breaks guys’ hearts and/or makes them go crazy. This is utter nonsense. The problem isn’t with Jaina, the problem is that the men in her life are just plain jerks.
Have you actually LISTENED to the crap these guys say? It’s pretty sad when Garrosh of all people has treated her with more dignity and respect than her so-called close friends.</description></item><item><title>Blizzcon Badges!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</guid><description>Do you need a little something to set you apart from the crowd at Blizzcon? Would you like a small piece of art to call your own and remember all the good times you had at the convention? I’ve been painting up just the thing!
These little paintings are painted on thick, high-quality Arches watercolour paper with Winsor &amp;amp; Newton watercolours. In a world of art that’s increasingly digital, I find I am loving going back to my roots and painting with brushes and pigments again.</description></item><item><title>An Unfortunate Turnip of Events</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/an-unfortunate-turnip-of-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 08:29:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/an-unfortunate-turnip-of-events/</guid><description>Remember the good old days in the first month of Mists, when carrots, lettuce and leeks were flying off the Auction House faster than you could list them, and for outrageous prices? I don’t even remember exactly, but weren’t they going for like 100 gold each? 100 GOLD PER TURNIP. And raiders who adamantly insisted they needed the best buff foods possible were crafting those banquets requiring 50 turnips at a time.</description></item><item><title>The Mogu Menace</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-mogu-menace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 08:25:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-mogu-menace/</guid><description>Kill 10 Mogu. Kill 8 more Mogu. Hey guess what? Kill a dozen more.
I wonder just how many Mogu we’ve taken out in our time here? All these Mogu-slaying dailies HAVE to be taking a toll on their population. Hell, I’ve slaughtered a few thousand alone.
Kill Mogu for Valor, kill Mogu for reputation, kill Mogu because they’re in the way while doing Archaeology…name a reason, and we’ve probably killed a Mogu for it.</description></item><item><title>Double Digits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 09:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/double-digits/</guid><description>I imagine tanks everywhere are shaking their heads in grim recognition of this scene. After all, how many times have they turned, scanning for the next pack of mobs to pull, only to hear that dreaded “FWOOSH” sound as an enormous ball of fire hurtles past them? Because EVERYONE KNOWS you can’t just WASTE A HOT STREAK PROC.
MAGES.
However, Vid’s lightning-fast DPS instincts served her well when it came to get Blizzcon tickets, netting her an unbelievably low 33rd in queue!</description></item><item><title>The Scarlet Letters</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-scarlet-letters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 08:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-scarlet-letters/</guid><description>WE REGRET NOTHING</description></item><item><title>Your New Undisputed Champion</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-new-undisputed-champion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 08:36:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-new-undisputed-champion/</guid><description>You know, at first I thought Hagara’s ice walls were bad. Saw a lot of people get insta-gibbed by those in LFR back during Cataclysm.
Then Elegon and his magic floor came and caused hilariously large quantities of surprise deaths, and I thought we had a new winner.
But then…came Durumu.
I can honestly say this was the first time I’ve ever seen the entire LFR group instantly perish in the blink of an eye.</description></item><item><title>Desserter Debuff</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/desserter-debuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/desserter-debuff/</guid><description>At the end of March I was thrilled to be taking a trip to Toronto/Montréal because it meant I’d have the chance to meet lots of great WoW people I’d gotten to know online. When I looked for “Things To Do in Toronto” I found a listing for a cupcake decorating class, and that was just icing on the cake. I was thrilled when Serrinne, Kaleri and Jasyla agreed to go with me.</description></item><item><title>Blingtrolled</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blingtrolled/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blingtrolled/</guid><description>Yet another reason why Engineering is the best profession!
Seriously, there’s few things funnier than plopping down Blingtron in a hard-to-reach spot in a well-populated area and sitting back to watch people go MAD as they try to find that elusive free loot. My personal favorites include trees in Halfhill, the upper balconies in Pandalaran, or in the normally-inaccessible catwalk in Orgrimmar’s front auction house.
Thanks to Raijair, Kalbeari, Hachidori, Dhevon and Korrath for the use of your likenesses this week!</description></item><item><title>Our New Favorite Boss</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-new-favorite-boss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 07:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-new-favorite-boss/</guid><description>Could this really be that far off, after seeing Tortos?
There’s been a lot of interesting raid boss mechanics – vehicles, flying, spirit realms – but few things are as satisfying or funny as just hauling off and punting a giant turtle at an even BIGGER turtle.
Bravo, Blizzard encounter design team. Bravo.</description></item><item><title>Fortune and Glory, Kid</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fortune-and-glory-kid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2013 08:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fortune-and-glory-kid/</guid><description>I think the solo loot scenario is my favorite thing in Mists so far. And I don’t even mean the loot! The loot’s okay, but really, Elder Charms are SO Patch 5.1. I just love running the place! And finding hidden chests and secret paths to said chests. There’s been a few chests in the first room, and one in the hallway leading to the second room, that I have no idea at all how to reach.</description></item><item><title>iWrynny</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/iwrynny/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 08:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/iwrynny/</guid><description>Somewhere out there in Pandaria, there’s an armorsmith with one twisted sense of humor.
Poor clueless little Anduin. Hands up if you saw him step onto that platform covered in Sha magic and walk right up to Garrosh, and thought to yourself “welp, I have a bad feeling about how this is going to turn out.” AND SURE ENOUGH.
Should have listened to Dezco, kid. Even if he does wear babies as armor.</description></item><item><title>Pretty Much a Constant Thing With Us</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pretty-much-a-constant-thing-with-us/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pretty-much-a-constant-thing-with-us/</guid><description>Hey, this feels familiar, doesn’t it?
Anyway, WE’RE BACK! /blows kisses from amidst a sea of fluttering rose petals
The time off has been good to us and we’re ready to leap headfirst into all the exciting new 5.2 stuff! Let’s just hope we can remember how to do this comic thing! (Confession, it took me nearly 10 minutes to remember the WordPress login info.)
Now yes, we know that Heart of Fear is technically old content now, but we had this script in the queue and we can’t just WASTE it!</description></item><item><title>Rested Experience</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</guid><description>Well, it finally happened: Vid’s drawing arm fell off. Like, literally, just sketching away and plop! it’s a scene right out of the Undercity. It’s all good though, she’s out talking to Mekkatorque right now about a steam-powered mechanical replacement. She says it’s no big deal, but as a veteran engineer, I remain skeptical.
But joking aside, the unfortunate reality is we’re starting to feel a bit of burnout, and there’s been some real-life commitments that are rearing their unavoidable and time-consuming heads.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 12:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</guid><description>The inevitable result of last week’s devious scheme.
(Really, this moment was so amazing, how could we NOT give it the full-comic spotlight it deserves??)
You know, in-game Garrosh is unpleasant and thoroughly unlikeable, and Blizzard is going to great lengths to portray him as an absolute monster. But I’m a big fan of THIS Garrosh, the one who isn’t concerned about world domination or wiping cities off the map, but just sticking it to Varian and being a general pain in the ass.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Too</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-too/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 08:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-too/</guid><description>Still the highlight of the expansion so far, in my opinion.
Let’s be honest. How many of us re-did this quest, over and over again, just to repeatedly wallop Varian in his giant chin? Who could possibly resist??
Headcanon: Garrosh sitting down in his throne room with a paper and clipboard.
On the left-hand side of the page: Strong new allies. Much-needed boost to the Horde’s ranks. New culture and knowledge that will strengthen the Horde.</description></item><item><title>Sated</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/sated/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 10:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/sated/</guid><description>Whoa, whoa, where did 2013 come from? It totally snuck up and [Ambushed] us when we weren’t expecting it. We’ve both been a little busy the last few days with RL travel, festivities and the ever pleasant-but-emotionally-draining family visits, but we’ll be back on pace next week with new stuff!
Also, I don’t know if we’ve ever mentioned this, but we’re always open to ideas and suggestions! Many of our strips are inspired by actual conversations or experiences we’ve had in-game, so if you come across something that you think we absolutely should know about, let us know in a comment, or tweet us at @fromdraenor!</description></item><item><title>He Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</guid><description>Hey, he IS a Prophet, after all. Also, I just need to point this out while Rades is gone: Orcs are currently on the very naughty list.
But the idea of Velen as Greatfather Winter and the faction leaders as little kids was actually all Rades’, so you can’t accuse me of bias in this case. We agreed that it even makes sense, when you think about it – to a draenei who is thousands of years old maybe the rest of us would seem like children.</description></item><item><title>Here We Come A-Wakening</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/here-we-come-a-wakening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 11:08:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/here-we-come-a-wakening/</guid><description>It’s that time of year again! Perhaps you recognize the new and improved Greatfather Winter from last year’s escapades?
I love everything about this strip, but particularly tiny adorable Rades and Vid hanging off of Kovok there. Look for these as our Twitter avatars for a while!
(You may also be amused that an in-depth discussion about Klaxxi anatomical features and the specific societal roles of Klaxxi of different body types preceded the completion of this comic.</description></item><item><title>what</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what/</guid><description>When Heart of Fear LFR came out, Garalon was…how shall we say…an interesting experience. And by interesting I mean painful, excruciating agony. It really became almost a joke that first week, to see how badly an LFR group would fail. And it’s not even necessarily people’s fault! Tag-team pass a kiting debuff back and forth with a stranger? And transmit it through touch? As in, the same mechanic that gave hardcore progression guilds migraines on Heroic Putricide back in ICC?</description></item><item><title>Unique-Equipped</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unique-equipped/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 09:17:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unique-equipped/</guid><description>It really was at Velen’s Book Club.
If you’ve been reading FDWL regularly since around May, you might remember this comic about Millya’s lost tail ring. Inspired by an unfortunate true story, it was around that time that I realized I had lost my wedding rings. We looked everywhere for them, upended everything, and ultimately concluded that they were lost forever. (A process that involved no small amount of hand-wringing and angst, I’ll admit).</description></item><item><title>WTB Real-life Alter Time</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wtb-real-life-alter-time/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wtb-real-life-alter-time/</guid><description>Please accept this pseudo-comic along with my apologies for this week. Last Friday we went to a concert! It was great and we had a great time. But the guy sitting next to Voss was coughing the entire time almost nonstop.
Voss told me darkly as we left, “I sure hope I didn’t catch germs from whatever was making that guy cough up his lung.”
Unfortunately, we both did. I’ll spare you the gory details except to say that I can’t remember having a cold that floored me like this one, ever.</description></item><item><title>Never Trust A Mage</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 11:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/never-trust-a-mage/</guid><description>You know, dealing with mages was hard enough before Mists, when they’d just portal-troll you by sending you to inconvenient, middle-of-nowhere locations.
Or when they’d summon 5-6 portals on top of one another and you’d have to click and see where you’d end up (Portal Roulette).
Or when they’d start casting you a portal, and then “accidentally” just Teleport themselves back to Orgrimmar, leaving the rest of you stuck in some wretched abyssal lair, miles from home.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Even Blink</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dont-even-blink/</guid><description>This comic will probably make the most sense to you if you are a mage, and/or if you have been a mage’s victim in this scenario. I have personally tallied my Blink kill count at probably four people. With Antigen it involved a rocket boots incident, with Itanya, we each headed the wrong way. With Thracks it was completely an accident, and with Ibra I swear I thought I saw Jasper Overload and was so excited I could break the chains.</description></item><item><title>Surprisingly Often, Actually</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:44:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</guid><description>From Draenor With Love launched November 1, 2011, which means it’s been an entire year! 😀 I am pretty pleased that we put out a comic each and every week, even when life kicked us around a bit, or when one of us was traveling. Thanks to everyone who’s read our stuff over the past year! We appreciate your visits, your comments, your retweets, all of it!
Also, a special thanks to Dee, Ayms/Mits, and Walks, who gave us awesome guest strips!</description></item><item><title>Kindred Spirits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</guid><description>If there was ONE THING that could bring these eternal rivals/enemies together…
I mean, I’m not even one of these classes and even I appreciate the FREEDOM they must be feeling! Free to summon their mana buns and fel candy any time they please! No longer shackled to the fickle whims of their groupmates, begging, PLEADING for them to please, just please COME OVER HERE AND CLICK ALREADY.
And of course, no longer prone to the excruciating frustration of attempting to summon a mage table – for other people’s benefit – only to have some oaf walk up and start summoning, but then wander away, cancelling the spell BUT still triggering the 10-minute cooldown.</description></item><item><title>Insert Emotion Here</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/insert-emotion-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 09:54:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/insert-emotion-here/</guid><description>When we wrote this joke in our script page three weeks ago, little did we know that the “Sha of ____” joke would become so popular and so prolific before we had a chance to publish. Ah well, live and learn.
There really are unlimited possibilities when it comes to these other, lesser-known Sha. And if they really are manifestation of our emotions, would there not be one for our increasingly weary attitudes about dailies, or the utterly-minor-but-totally-palpable sense of irritation at seeing half a dozen “Wiggling” and “Alluring” crops that you’re going to have to deal with?</description></item><item><title>Straight Outta Halfhill</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/straight-outta-halfhill/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 12:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/straight-outta-halfhill/</guid><description>VEGGIE. BLING.
The best part about this comic is how utterly unfamiliar both Vid and myself are with these themes. We’re about as un-thug-life as you can get.
Anyway…so uh, yeah. About those farms.
We can’t be the only ones making MAD BANK off our daily produce harvests, right? It’s absurd how much these pumpkins, turnips and melons are going for! I mean, I want to level my Way cooking skills, but how can I use these priceless items for lowly FOOD when they could be netting me hundreds of pure, organically-grown profit every day?</description></item><item><title>Priorities</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</guid><description>This is actually a true story. On launch night, we were a few hours in and realized that our Legendary-toting Boomkin was sitting in the Barrens somewhere fishing up Tasty Crapfish and Garbage Trout trying to get realm-first fishing, two of us were hanging out in starter zones furiously battling and taming new pets, and our infamous guild AH tycoon was expanding his financial empire with lucrative Pandaria ore/herb sales.</description></item><item><title>Wish You Were Here</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wish-you-were-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 10:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wish-you-were-here/</guid><description>Today’s comic is a very special guest strip from our amazingly talented friend Walks! The Dread Wastes are so horrifically mutated and ugly (I personally think they feel like the Ghostlands, except on acid) and Walks totally nailed the vintage travel poster look. Thanks Walks! 😀
I think of all the factions in Mists, the Dread Wastes’ Klaxxi are my favorite. Well, okay, maybe the Tillers take the cake but that’s more because I AM ADDICTED TO CULTIVATING MY PRICELESS PRODUCE than any particular love for the faction itself.</description></item><item><title>Masks of Pandaria</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/masks-of-pandaria/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 19:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/masks-of-pandaria/</guid><description>AHHHH IT’S HERE AT LAST
PET BATTLES
NEW QUESTS AND LORE AND STORIES
TRANSMOG GEAR
DUNGEONS
CHALLENGE MODES
MONKS
PANDAREN
Where do you even start??
I’m not going to even TRY to suggest what you should be doing, because it’s ALL amazing and beautiful and completely awesome. I’ve been taking my time leveling, enjoying the scenery, the voice-acting, the unfolding story. It’s all so good! And I’m not even near level cap, or seeing the actual end-game content, or challenge modes, or the new battlegrounds.</description></item><item><title>Tarecohshutup</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tarecohshutup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2012 08:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tarecohshutup/</guid><description>I knew from folks spending time in the beta that Dragonwrath had a new feature. Yet after 5.0.4 went live, it still scared the bejeebers out of me the first time she talked out loud. I tend to keep my volume up pretty high!
I don’t actually find Tarecgosa annoying in-game, I like the occasional interjections (but I have my sound turned down so low now that I seldom hear all the things she says.</description></item><item><title>Stagway to Heaven</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stagway-to-heaven/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 08:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stagway-to-heaven/</guid><description>Stag stacking was BY FAR one of the coolest and funniest random side effects of patch 5.0.4. Tragically, this bug has since been fixed and you can no longer pile druids to the heavens and walk around as a teetering tower of antlers and fur. Such a shame!
Was it supposed to work like that? Well, probably not. But my gosh, was it hilarious. Ah well, R.I.P. stag stacking.
If you never got the chance to see it in action, here’s a Youtube video.</description></item><item><title>Everything is New Again</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/everything-is-new-again/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/everything-is-new-again/</guid><description>Patch 5.0.4 is here and there’s so many exciting things to check out! Account-wide mounts! New talent systems! AoE looting! Revamped Scarlet Monastery, Scholomance and Ragefire Chasm! And there’s even apparently a new ferocious Darkmoon Rabbit world boss owning fools out at the Darkmoon Faire? I haven’t seen this fellow myself yet, but I’ve heard the hilarious horror stories.
The world (of Warcraft) is suddenly a very new and thrilling place to be, and I love it.</description></item><item><title>Tides of War</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tides-of-war/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/tides-of-war/</guid><description>Cross-faction friendships may be unorthodox, but they certainly aren’t unheard of. Jaina and Thrall have been friends since before he started calling himself Go’el. Asric and Jadaar are a pair of lesser-known but still significant “friends,” a blood elf and a draenei who seem to love to hate each other. Game mechanics prevent us from communicating with each other and they do an excellent job of keeping us divided. Ignorance breeds contempt and fear, and it’s easier to attack and kill an enemy that is strange and foreign to you.</description></item><item><title>Player Versus Panda</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/player-versus-panda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/player-versus-panda/</guid><description>Have you seen the Mists of Pandaria trailer yet? If not, WHY NOT?
Seriously though. It’s no wonder they’re scared. This invincible ninja bear just flew out of the mists, kicking their ass, parrying their combined attacks…
Oh, and also, he’s level 90.
IT’S PVP GANKFESTS IN STRANGLETHORN VALE ALL OVER AGAIN, OH GOD RUN AWAY</description></item><item><title>Not a Chance, Thrall</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-a-chance-thrall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 08:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-a-chance-thrall/</guid><description>Seriously dude, we all know why this is a bad idea.
Speaking of orc babies, Vid brought up an interesting question while doing the art – what color skin would the baby of a green-skinned orc and a brown-skinned orc have? We settled on sort of an olive complexion, but only time will tell!
As for Thrall and Aggra’s kid? It’d be nice if it were a girl orc, who goes on to accomplish great things.</description></item><item><title>There Will Be Blood</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 09:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-will-be-blood/</guid><description>From a recent Mists beta build: Glyph of Gushing Wound.
WTF is it with WARRIOR glyphs in Mists? Cripes. Lighting themselves on fire, lightning strikes, flocks of crows, and now MORE BLOOD? Blizz is sure giving them some pretty fun cosmetic options!
Also, these might seriously be my favorite type of strip. I don’t know if Vid was quite as big a fan of this particular one though.
July 24</description></item><item><title>Did You Think We Had Forgotten</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/did-you-think-we-had-forgotten/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 08:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/did-you-think-we-had-forgotten/</guid><description>Did you think we had forgotten?
Did you think we had forgiven?
Yes, that’s right, Critter Kill Squad achievement. And yes, we definitely remember your gleeful experiments into finding out just how big a creature you could inhale.
Oh, there will be a RECKONING, CREEPY CRATE! Your days are numbered! When Mists of Pandaria comes out, your victims will finally be able to fight back. Prepare yourself, Crate, for the terrible vengeance of the CRITTERS!</description></item><item><title>Seriously, Just Buy One Already</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/seriously-just-buy-one-already/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 09:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/seriously-just-buy-one-already/</guid><description>More like “Hour of Waiting For Thrall To Run The Entire Stupid Way in Ghost Wolf Form”, right?
Anyway, we never DO find out what happens to Thrall’s horse in Escape from Durnholde. Everyone else in Old Hillsbrad seemed destined for big things – Kel’Thuzad, Herod, Thrall himself, Old Blanchy – so wouldn’t it be funny if the horse also had some great destiny?
And when you think “when in history would a SURPRISE HORSE be absolutely perfect?</description></item><item><title>Just Not the Same</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/just-not-the-same/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 11:22:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/just-not-the-same/</guid><description>Cataclysm’s general removal of group quests and elite mobs sure has made questing a lot easier, but man, Nagrand just does not feel the same anymore.
For example, take the final “bosses” of Nesingwary’s slaughter quests, Bach’lor, Banthar and Gutripper. These formerly-elite beasts always felt like the perfect foes to wrap up the questline – too strong to just take on without some strategy, but definitely soloable if you put some thought and effort into it.</description></item><item><title>Ahn’Qiraj Awkwardness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ahnqiraj-awkwardness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 08:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ahnqiraj-awkwardness/</guid><description>(If you got the reference already, high-five.)</description></item><item><title>Yak in Business</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yak-in-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 09:57:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yak-in-business/</guid><description>Disappointment was high on the Mists beta this week, as the price of the Grand Expedition Yak skyrocketed to 120,000 gold. If you think about it though, the price hike makes total sense! The ethereals aren’t the sort of people to let this kind of potential profit slip through their bandage-fingers. And besides, with the yak’s portable reforger making their Orgrimmar/Stormwind services obsolete, they’d actually be losing money!
Ethereal interference aside, have you SEEN how much stuff is on one of these yaks?</description></item><item><title>Well Read</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/well-read/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 08:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/well-read/</guid><description>When we did the “Ring of Lost” strip, a few different people were intrigued at the idea of Velen’s Book Club. So consider today’s comic a bit of a follow-up!
Actually, there’s almost enough readable books in WoW that you COULD have a book club! You’ve got the Crawgol’s Silithid Field Guide (The Authoritotal Handbook)…the list goes on and on.
Personally, some of my favorite books are the ones that can be found during the Death Knight starter zone.</description></item><item><title>Glyph of Ireworks</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/glyph-of-ireworks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 09:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/glyph-of-ireworks/</guid><description>It may come as no surprise to you that I absolutely adore a good pun. And, I say with absolute shame pride that this is a true story, upon hearing of Mists’ Glyph of Fireworks.
Judging from how people on Twitter reacted, I think Vid’s reaction in the last panel is one many people can relate with. What can I say? Those moments are just too funny. In fact, when my D&amp;amp;D group gets together to play, I have a private goal to produce at least one huge pun/groan moment each session.</description></item><item><title>Rage of the Friendlands</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 07:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rage-of-the-friendlands/</guid><description>While folks were helping me out to get my legendary, it occurred to me that I wanted to do something to thank them. You know, apart from just – thanking them. Initially I was going to do little character portraits for everyone, but as the list of people who were involved grew, I started to understand that might be a bit unwieldy.
So instead, Rades and I put our heads together and came up with the idea of a strip featuring all the people.</description></item><item><title>Limit Break</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/limit-break/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 08:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/limit-break/</guid><description>This week’s strip is a guest strip from Ayms and Mits, who you may know from their great webcomic, Fourth Wall! They’re no longer doing new strips, but they heard we needed some help this week and came out of “retirement” to lend us a hand. Thanks guys! Fourth Wall isn’t online anymore, but you can find Ayms’ artwork at her sketchblog – do go check out her stuff!
We should be back on schedule this week, so thanks again to Dee, Ayms and Mits who really came through for us when we needed a hand.</description></item><item><title>There’s Something Different About You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/theres-something-different-about-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 08:31:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/theres-something-different-about-you/</guid><description>Today’s comic is a special guest strip by our WONDERFUL and TALENTED friend Dee, who came through AMAZINGLY, considering she had only like half a day’s notice! You can check out her WoW blog at @mainfloortank!
(She really, really likes elves.)
THANKS DEE! You really helped us out. Much love!
Unfortunately, the reason Vid couldn’t finish this week’s strip was due to a sudden family emergency. Send some good thoughts and wishes her way, as she and her family could really use them.</description></item><item><title>Ring of Lost</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ring-of-lost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 08:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ring-of-lost/</guid><description>Ever wonder if WoW characters have the same day-to-day problems that plague us in real life? In this case, Vid had a minor crisis this week regarding a lost wedding ring, which sounds a lot like a quest, only there’s no handy directional guide in real life, and no reward other than a tremendous sense of relief.
Anyway, we thought that, you know, for the amount of travel and continent-hopping the average WoW hero does, remembering where you put something down must be a tremendous hassle.</description></item><item><title>The Lord of Terror</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-lord-of-terror/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-lord-of-terror/</guid><description>Like everyone else on the planet, we’ve sunk some time into Diablo III so far, and it’s a blast. So far I’m greatly enjoying the Wizard (LASER FREEZE RAY) and the Demon Hunter is also a lot of fun. I’ve played around with the Monk a bit, but I don’t think I enjoy the melee playstyle. I’ll stick with my blasters.
Vid, of course, is playing a Wizard. Shocking, I know!</description></item><item><title>From Draenor with Mischief</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/from-draenor-with-mischief/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 09:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/from-draenor-with-mischief/</guid><description>This is the special prize strip Cymre of Bubbles of Mischief won by taking 1st place in the Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt!
Congratulations Cymre! We hope you enjoy your guest appearance!
Cymre maintains an amazing gallery of World of Warcraft rare spawns on her blog – aka, “Silver Dragons” – so we thought, hey, what better way to celebrate her egg-hunting victory than with some Silver Dragon love of her own?</description></item><item><title>Our Poor, Tired Feet</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-poor-tired-feet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 05:19:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-poor-tired-feet/</guid><description>The Calgary Expo was on the weekend, and, well, it was an…interesting experience.
There was waiting. There were photos with Patrick Stewart and autographs from Wil Wheaton. There was more waiting. There was the chance to meet Fyreuni of Daily Quests.
Oh, and there was a near-riot when the Expo shut the doors because they had oversold and weren’t letting in any more attendees, regardless of pre-purchased tickets, “we have a scheduled photoshoot with Patrick Stewart”, or “I just stepped outside for a smoke and my family is still inside!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 09:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</guid><description>HEY MURADIN PUT A BIRD ON IT
Like we said last week…Warrior glyphs in Mists = THE COOLEST.
Some news about the next few weeks! This weekend, we’ll be attending a Comic Expo in Calgary! Excitement! Our strip next week will be something based off the Expo, we hope. Then, the week after that we plan on presenting the special guest strip for Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt! So keep your eyes peeled!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</guid><description>A Glyph that causes a lightning strike?
…I have a sudden urge to play a warrior in Mists.
Seriously though, it’s terrific that Blizzard is giving us all these new fun cosmetic glyphs. They’re little touches, but damn are they cool.
My personal favorite so far? That would be Glyph of the Geist. BECAUSE GEISTS ARE AWESOME.
(In other news, I think Vid is going to revolt if I make her draw Garrosh again.</description></item><item><title>For This Moment Alone</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-this-moment-alone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 07:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-this-moment-alone/</guid><description>It’s a good thing hitting the button on LFR Ultraxion isn’t necessary to beat the fight, because if it was, I don’t think a single LFR group would ever kill him. Like, seriously, it’s NOT THAT HARD, PEOPLE. PUSH THE DAMN BUTTON. IT’S RIGHT THERE IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR SCREEN, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
But no. It’s enough to make a healer tear their hair out in frustration.
In other news, here is a snippet of the From Draenor creative process at work:</description></item><item><title>The Legacy of Kip Diskin</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-legacy-of-kip-diskin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 08:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-legacy-of-kip-diskin/</guid><description>The new glyphs on the Mists of Pandaria beta sound amazing. Trust me, this is not the only glyph feature you’ll be seeing on From Draenor.
I was actually surprised to see an Orca glyph, since they seem more suitable for Northrend than the lush, temperate zones of Pandaria. Wouldn’t it be funny if there were a huge assortment of minor glyphs that changed the appearance of druid travel and aquatic forms?</description></item><item><title>Not Who We Expected</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-who-we-expected/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 12:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-who-we-expected/</guid><description>As everyone knows by now, Garrosh Hellscream will be the boss of Mists of Pandaria’s final content patch, and we take him down in an exciting-sounding “Siege of Orgrimmar.”
Now, there’s a lot of time between now and then, but I have to say…given what we’ve seen of Sylvanas in Cataclysm – being quite dastardly towards the Worgen during their starting zone, raising unwilling humans into new Forsaken and conscripting them into her forces, and her cold and callous treatment towards Koltira – I really expected her to be the Horde leader we’d end up killing as a raid boss.</description></item><item><title>Our Unsung Hero</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-unsung-hero/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-unsung-hero/</guid><description>From Draenor presents, Real Azerothian Geniuses.
Today we salute you, Mr. Lamp Hum Sound Creator Guy.
You work tirelessly to capture the tranquil sound of a summer breeze or the frantic buzz of fireflies trapped in a jar, just to make our weary trek through the wild a little less scary.
In the darkest of nights, we pause on our journey, wondering if that subtle rustling we just heard was one of your masterpieces singing its peaceful song of illumination, or a horrible flesh-eating zombie lurking in the bushes.</description></item><item><title>Resurrection Sickness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</guid><description>Everyone’s been buzzing about the new &amp;amp; improved Scroll of Resurrection, and why not? A free level 80, realm transfer AND faction transfer? Just for coming back to the game? Yeah, it’s no wonder the new Scroll offer has been so popular.
Of course, we all know what’s REALLY behind the Scroll frenzy.
SPECTRAL MOUNTS.
Awww yeah. That’s the kind of incentive that gets RESULTS.
PS: Did you know Stormwind really does have a War Room?</description></item><item><title>Darkmoon Foul</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkmoon-foul/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 11:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkmoon-foul/</guid><description>Seriously, does no one else at the Faire raise an eyebrow at the fact that each month, Kerri Hicks is collecting thousands of bloody ears? I mean, the icon is an ear, and Blizzard has a tendency to encourage ear-collecting, ever since Diablo. What the heck is she DOING with all of these bloody trophies??
It seems such a disproportionate reward, too – you bring back proof of 250(!) kills and you get 10 little tickets.</description></item><item><title>To the Ground</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 09:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</guid><description>The idea of class abilities repeating endlessly was actually really hard to make a comic for, because there were so many awesome options! The mental images of Healing Rain, Hurricane or Fan of Knives duplicating over and over again are too funny.
In the end, we decided to go with a theme preferred by Vid: CAKES (you can never have too much cake, according to her) and dead Warlocks. Also, the opportunity to have a sea of cakes was too great to pass up.</description></item><item><title>Every Day I’m Transmogging</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/every-day-im-transmogging/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 10:09:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/every-day-im-transmogging/</guid><description>This may be my favourite FDWL in the history of ever. (I know, we’ve only done less than 20 strips but even so!)
Usually the way we make strips is one of us has an idea and pitches it to the other, then we start to brain-storm and perhaps refine or change a few things. Sometimes the strip is fully formed, as when Rades presented this one to me like so:</description></item><item><title>Your Racial Leader is Thinking About You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-racial-leader-is-thinking-about-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 09:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-racial-leader-is-thinking-about-you/</guid><description>It occurred to Vid and I yesterday that perhaps we should have saved the comic with the NAKED ORC for our Valentine’s Day update. Apparently we are unable to read calendars.
We figured we needed to do SOMETHING love-themed for this week – after all, the comic IS From Draenor With LOVE!
Well, who better to feature on our special Valentine’s Day card than another local from Draenor, the Warchief himself!</description></item><item><title>Maximum Cupacity</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/maximum-cupacity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 10:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/maximum-cupacity/</guid><description>I really, really wish we had ampm stores in Canada. I would totally buy those cups! The art on them looks great, and they’d be nice collectibles to own.
The three “rejected” cup ideas we came up with for this strip should all be sadly familiar to most WoW players. I don’t think anyone will EVER forget Sindragosa’s famous line, and Neptulon’s PUUUURE WATERRRR line from Throne of the Tides has quickly become a fan favorite.</description></item><item><title>Squeaky Green</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/squeaky-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/squeaky-green/</guid><description>When we heard that there would be no Blizzcon this year, Vid and I knew we had to cover it somehow. We ran down the list of Blizzcon cliches (true or not), one of which was the inevitable pungent result of cramming hundreds of bodies into a cramped, enclosed convention center.
Then, somehow, it became this.
To say Vid was mortified when I sent her the script would be an understatement.</description></item><item><title>Choose Wisely</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choose-wisely/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choose-wisely/</guid><description>Yes, we know Droids and Hutts are not actually available player races in SWTOR. Too bad – I would totally be a Hutt so I could use awful HUTT YOUR MOUTH and HUTT UP puns and make everyone hate me.
Also, I wish I could say we were joking when talking about Vid’s overpowering love for anyone blue. Let’s just say that panel 4 isn’t entirely off the mark. 😉</description></item><item><title>Magic Touch</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/magic-touch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/magic-touch/</guid><description>…Then I finally found a suitable mold for the chassis or I thought it was a suitable chassis mold but actually they meant it for a gyrocopter and it wasn’t quite right so I tried to convince a friend to model for it but he wouldn’t because he said, and I quote, “Your inventions have a way of proving fatal to people who agree to test them,” I ask you, is that fair?</description></item><item><title>Thrall, Aspect of Derp</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/thrall-aspect-of-derp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 11:04:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/thrall-aspect-of-derp/</guid><description>In the final fight of Dragon Soul, players have to fight Deathwing while leaping back and forth between a few different islands, carried by Thrall’s winds.
Unfortunately, Thrall has some…issues…and will occasionally NOT give a player the wind buff, which sends them plummeting to their death in the churning Maelstrom below. This usually results in much anger and frustration, and usually a wipe.
Is he just trolling us? Or is he just really, really incompetent?</description></item><item><title>Damn You, Murglesnout</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/damn-you-murglesnout/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 09:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/damn-you-murglesnout/</guid><description>Oh, Murglesnout. Fisher’s bane. So plentiful. So abundant.
So utterly, completely worthless.
True, Blizzard did eventually add in a Cooking recipe so that the dreaded Murglesnout wasn’t COMPLETELY pointless. But it’s TOO LATE! Even now, the mere sight of THIS TERRIBLE FISH fills me with rage. MURGLESNOUT!
…however, it really does make a fun “gift” to give friends.
If you want to MAKE THEM ANGRY!
MURGLESNOUT!</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Four</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-four/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 12:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-four/</guid><description>I wasn’t actually sure how Rades intended to end our little odyssey. Needless to say, my jaw dropped when I got this far in the script. It’s great for him, though, because he gets to show his mad genius! Vid, who has no compunction about blasting a rocket straight into Ironforge or any other environs, is a little uneasy when it comes to FrankenWinter. But ultimately, she decides that it’s better to let a cyborg version of Greatfather Winter do all of the Winter’s Veil stuff – so that she and Rades don’t have to.</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Three</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-three/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 02:40:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-three/</guid><description>Part 3 of 4! Rades and Vid do their best to fill the late Greatfather Winter’s shoes – in their own, unique fashion, of course.
Locations where Vid is now no longer permitted to operate: The Exodar AND Ironforge.
Hey, isn’t that rocket in panel 4 the same type as the one that blew up Greatfather Winter? Oh well, what those Druids don’t know, won’t hurt them…hopefully.
Next week’s Part 4 will come out a few days after Christmas, so consider it our special (belated) gift to you for reading!</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-two/</guid><description>The saga continues! Oh no, poor Greatfather Winter!
Vid did an awesome job with the expressions in this strip, I think you’ll all agree. I’m now using the “Sad Rades” face as my avatar, and I can’t even look at panel 3 without laughing.
There was some debate about which Greatfather Winter to use – the dwarven Alliance version, or the orcish Horde version! In the end though, we decided to go with the dwarf, to include more races.</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 07:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-one/</guid><description>It’s a cliche often used that “the journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.” In this case, a journey of approximately 17,500 miles per hour begins with a single rocket and a large explosion.
This is how engineers work.
Rades and I wanted to do something a little special and different for the upcoming holiday season, as well as try our hands at a mini story-arc! So expect this story to run for pretty much the rest of the month, until we reach its epic conclusion.</description></item><item><title>Transmogalypse</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/transmogalypse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/transmogalypse/</guid><description>Has there ever been a feature more eagerly anticipated than Transmogrification? If there is, I sure haven’t seen it. So many options! So much potential for nostalgia! The future has arrived, and its name is World of Dresscraft.
Of course, for every person who can’t wait to dig out their old Tier 1 or Tier 0.5 sets, there’s someone who is going to gleefully turn their fearsome, godly “I’m-About-to-Kill-Deathwing” armor into a neon nightmare Burning Crusade clown suit.</description></item><item><title>For Science, You Monster</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</guid><description>Hey guys, Vid’s been crit by real life this week, so send her warm thoughts because until she’s back, you’re stuck with my terrible WoW Model Viewer comics!
Last night Blizzard released an updated Mists of Pandaria talent calculator, complete with new baseline talents. One of the new baseline Warlock talents was Demonic Portal, as pictured above. Needless to say, the Portal comparisons were instant and furious! So I figured it was an appropriate time to break out ye old Undercity Companion Cube image from this year’s Love is in the Air seasonal event.</description></item><item><title>Yellow Angry Man</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yellow-angry-man/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/yellow-angry-man/</guid><description>If you’ve played a paladin at level 85 for any length of time, hopefully this requires no explanation. For those of you who haven’t, well. Perhaps you play a melee DPS. You’re at the boss’ feet, stabbing/slicing/cutting (or whatever else it is that you melee folks do).
You hear an odd grunt.
“ARRRRGH!”
“GRRRRRR!”
“RRRRRAAA!”
This, my friends, is the Yellow, Angry Man. His anger knows no bounds. Likewise, his yellow-ness is unsurpassed.</description></item><item><title>Grudge Match</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/grudge-match/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/grudge-match/</guid><description>When the Pet Battle System was announced at Blizzcon, everyone had a wide range of reactions. Were they serious? Was this an elaborate joke? How much more like Pokemon could this possibly be? But without question, the most important possibility was the potential hilarity of absurd pet matchups, such as Alliance Balloon vs. Horde Balloon, or Enchanted Broom vs. Magic Lamp. Can you say EXCITEMENT??
Personally, I’m banking on my Toxic Wasteling.</description></item><item><title>Rare Spawn</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rare-spawn-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 06:21:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rare-spawn-3/</guid><description>I’m not especially good at keeping secrets. So the fact that you are only seeing this, now, after over a month of loving work is nothing short of a miracle. The idea of doing a webcomic wasn’t a new one for Rades and I – we’d talked about it before, sometime last year – but the time wasn’t right. We were on different pages about what a comic should be (I was thinking epic story, he was thinking gag) and so we just shelved it.</description></item></channel></rss>