<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extras! on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/extras/</link><description>Recent content in Extras! on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 10:25:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/extras/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vacation Vid</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/vacation-vid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 10:25:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/vacation-vid/</guid><description>I’m sorry there’s no “regular” comic this Wednesday! We did our best to get a bunch of them done but the last few pages have been complicated and we’re only human, and I was going on vacation. Please accept this sketch doodle of vacation mode Vidyala instead. It’s much more pleasant than the current FDWL reality. We’ll be back with our regular updates next week!</description></item><item><title>The FDWL Awakens</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-fdwl-awakens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-fdwl-awakens/</guid><description>Happy Star Wars Day, and May the Fourth be with you!
We don’t normally skip a week for a special page like this, but when we noticed the date coincidence a few weeks back, we just couldn’t pass up the opportunity to have a little fun. And now, after seeing what Vid came up with, I think we definitely made the right call. (Sorry Poe, there just wasn’t room, buddy!)</description></item><item><title>Happy Noblegarden!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-noblegarden/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-noblegarden/</guid><description>Happy Noblegarden, everyone! If you’re a Mage, make sure you go gather enough chocolate eggs to buy the Tome of Polymorph: Rabbit! 😀</description></item><item><title>Quieter Days</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quieter-days/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 10:03:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quieter-days/</guid><description>I’ve been very sick this past week, so we’re taking a brief pause from the action. In the meantime, readers seemed to really take to the nameless Aldor and Scryer characters on the last few pages! We imagined them as rivals representing opposing factions, sure, but ones where any enmity or opposition had ultimately faded into a comfortably friendly rivalry over the years of defending Shattrath together.</description></item><item><title>Colouring Page</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/colouring-page/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 10:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/colouring-page/</guid><description>Hey folks, my apologies. Due to some personal stuff I wasn’t able to get a comic done this week. Please accept instead this colouring page – it’s a slightly edited version of our page 100 comic that you can print out and colour yourself if you’d like! It was originally available only to our patrons. We’ll be back with the regular comic on schedule next week.
(A note from Sean: Though the image appears the same size as any other comic, it is much higher resolution.</description></item><item><title>Patch Notes!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/patch-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/patch-notes/</guid><description>Hey all, no FDWL update this week as Vid has some RL family stuff going on. (This isn’t an April First gag.)
However, Blizzard did release their special patch notes for today! As always, they’re amazing. but also check out that first screenshot!! 😀
FDWL will be back next week like normal – think it’s maybe time to check in on Rades, we haven’t seen him in a while! Until then, have a great day, and as male Forsaken NPCs say, “Trust no one.</description></item><item><title>Happy Winter Veil!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-winter-veil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/happy-winter-veil/</guid><description>Hope everyone is enjoying the season and holidays! Vid and I are both traveling for Christmas, so no new strip next week, but in the meantime enjoy this bit of FDWL holiday art! And click here to enjoy it full-size!
In other exciting news, thank you to Rachel for being our latest Patreon supporter! With this, we’ve now reached our milestone goal to have a monthly wallpaper each month for all of our patrons!</description></item><item><title>Unused FDWL Strip: Archimonde Crossing</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unused-fdwl-strip-archimonde-crossing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 03:22:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unused-fdwl-strip-archimonde-crossing/</guid><description>We should be back with Chapter 3 next week! Until then, enjoy the script for a page we never ended up doing: Archimonde Crossing.
When Animal Crossing: New Leaf came out, both Vid and I were enjoying it so much we wanted to do a FDWL comic about it. We had a few different ideas, including one about how hilarious it is when you shake a tree in Animal Crossing, hoping for money or furniture, and instead you get AN ANGRY SWARM OF BEES.</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 04:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes/</guid><description>Because this Monday was my birthday and I was going out of town on the weekend, I asked Rades if we could take a week off the “regular” comic! We agreed to do it and just have something for filler. I thought that especially since I now do most of the comic on paper that it might be interesting for you to see where I do it and what it looks like from my end.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Colour Keys</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-colour-keys/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 02:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-colour-keys/</guid><description>Work and life stuff hit us both pretty hard this past week and unfortunately we weren’t able to get the comic finished. This doesn’t happen very often and we’d like to build some buffer, but for now we’d prefer not to rush the comic and have the quality suffer.
So what are you looking at, then? Back towards the end of Chapter One, Rades and I discussed at length to have a wardrobe change in Chapter Two.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Happy Winter Veil!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-happy-winter-veil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2013 01:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-happy-winter-veil/</guid><description>Happy Winter Veil, everyone! Hope Robo-Greatfather Winter is nice to you this year!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Character Profile: Vidyala</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-vidyala/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 02:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-vidyala/</guid><description>And now, Vid’s turn for the character development questionnaire!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Character Profile: Rades</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-rades/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 18:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/bonus-character-profile-rades/</guid><description>There’s been a fun little a good cook, too.)
Obviously, we don’t want to devote 30 days to this, and some of the questions didn’t really work for characters answering it about themselves, so the FDWL version of this survey is only 21 questions.
Check back next week’s for Vid’s answers!</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes Part 3: Production</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-3-production/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 08:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-3-production/</guid><description>For a larger version of today’s strip, click here.
This is part 3 of 3 of our Behind the Scenes series! Next week we’ll have something…suitable, for the looming 5.4 patch. And then after that it’ll be SOMETHING ENTIRELY NEW AND EXCITING! We’re going to be trying something new so we hope you enjoy it!</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes Part 2: Art</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-2-art/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 08:03:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-2-art/</guid><description>Last week, Rades explained the process of how he scripts and sometimes storyboards a FDWL script! This week I’m going to be telling you about how I do the sketching and art.
For a larger version of today’s strip, click here!
The following is a transcript of text from the above image.
It’s worth noting that over the time we’ve been doing this I have simplified the art a fair bit to save time.</description></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes Part 1: Script</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-1-script/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 08:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/behind-the-scenes-part-1-script/</guid><description>For a larger version of today’s strip, click here. For a text version, well, read on!
Everyone’s busy preparing for patch 5.4 and the Siege of Orgrimmar, and we’re no exception! We’re working on some significant changes to FDWL that you can expect to see when the patch goes live. For now, we thought we’d share a bit of the creative process and show just how we do this comic thing!</description></item></channel></rss>