<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>warlocks on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/warlocks/</link><description>Recent content in warlocks on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 09:42:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/warlocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kindred Spirits</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kindred-spirits/</guid><description>If there was ONE THING that could bring these eternal rivals/enemies together…
I mean, I’m not even one of these classes and even I appreciate the FREEDOM they must be feeling! Free to summon their mana buns and fel candy any time they please! No longer shackled to the fickle whims of their groupmates, begging, PLEADING for them to please, just please COME OVER HERE AND CLICK ALREADY.
And of course, no longer prone to the excruciating frustration of attempting to summon a mage table – for other people’s benefit – only to have some oaf walk up and start summoning, but then wander away, cancelling the spell BUT still triggering the 10-minute cooldown.</description></item><item><title>To the Ground</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 09:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/to-the-ground/</guid><description>The idea of class abilities repeating endlessly was actually really hard to make a comic for, because there were so many awesome options! The mental images of Healing Rain, Hurricane or Fan of Knives duplicating over and over again are too funny.
In the end, we decided to go with a theme preferred by Vid: CAKES (you can never have too much cake, according to her) and dead Warlocks. Also, the opportunity to have a sea of cakes was too great to pass up.</description></item><item><title>For Science, You Monster</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</guid><description>Hey guys, Vid’s been crit by real life this week, so send her warm thoughts because until she’s back, you’re stuck with my terrible WoW Model Viewer comics!
Last night Blizzard released an updated Mists of Pandaria talent calculator, complete with new baseline talents. One of the new baseline Warlock talents was Demonic Portal, as pictured above. Needless to say, the Portal comparisons were instant and furious! So I figured it was an appropriate time to break out ye old Undercity Companion Cube image from this year’s Love is in the Air seasonal event.</description></item></channel></rss>