<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pet battles on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/pet-battles/</link><description>Recent content in pet battles on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 10:21:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/pet-battles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Priorities</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</guid><description>This is actually a true story. On launch night, we were a few hours in and realized that our Legendary-toting Boomkin was sitting in the Barrens somewhere fishing up Tasty Crapfish and Garbage Trout trying to get realm-first fishing, two of us were hanging out in starter zones furiously battling and taming new pets, and our infamous guild AH tycoon was expanding his financial empire with lucrative Pandaria ore/herb sales.</description></item><item><title>Did You Think We Had Forgotten</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/did-you-think-we-had-forgotten/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 08:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/did-you-think-we-had-forgotten/</guid><description>Did you think we had forgotten?
Did you think we had forgiven?
Yes, that’s right, Critter Kill Squad achievement. And yes, we definitely remember your gleeful experiments into finding out just how big a creature you could inhale.
Oh, there will be a RECKONING, CREEPY CRATE! Your days are numbered! When Mists of Pandaria comes out, your victims will finally be able to fight back. Prepare yourself, Crate, for the terrible vengeance of the CRITTERS!</description></item><item><title>Grudge Match</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/grudge-match/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/grudge-match/</guid><description>When the Pet Battle System was announced at Blizzcon, everyone had a wide range of reactions. Were they serious? Was this an elaborate joke? How much more like Pokemon could this possibly be? But without question, the most important possibility was the potential hilarity of absurd pet matchups, such as Alliance Balloon vs. Horde Balloon, or Enchanted Broom vs. Magic Lamp. Can you say EXCITEMENT??
Personally, I’m banking on my Toxic Wasteling.</description></item></channel></rss>