<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>non-wow on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/non-wow/</link><description>Recent content in non-wow on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:02:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/non-wow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Real Twelve</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-real-twelve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-real-twelve/</guid><description>Hey, I don’t think it’s too much of a stretch! Rades is an accomplished engineer, he could undoubtedly keep a TARDIS running, and he could accomplish so much with a sonic screwdriver! I think Vid would make a great companion, though she could be the Doctor just as easily.
I did this art awhile ago and thought considering this Sunday’s announcement, using it now would be pretty timely. The opportunity to put Rades in a dapper suit jacket and bow tie was too good to pass up.</description></item><item><title>There Are Two Types of People</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-are-two-types-of-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 08:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/there-are-two-types-of-people/</guid><description>The most difficult thing about this comic is that I had to stop playing “Animal Crossing: New Leaf” long enough to draw it.
If you’re not familiar, ACNL is a kind of life simulator game for the Nintendo 3DS that has been sweeping through the WoW twitter community like a wildfire. I played an earlier Animal Crossing title on the Gamecube back in the day. In terms of gameplay it’s pretty basic: Grow/harvest fruit, plant flowers, laugh at things your neighbours say, fish and catch bugs, dig up fossils, design clothes.</description></item><item><title>Blizzcon Badges!</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/blizzcon-badges/</guid><description>Do you need a little something to set you apart from the crowd at Blizzcon? Would you like a small piece of art to call your own and remember all the good times you had at the convention? I’ve been painting up just the thing!
These little paintings are painted on thick, high-quality Arches watercolour paper with Winsor &amp;amp; Newton watercolours. In a world of art that’s increasingly digital, I find I am loving going back to my roots and painting with brushes and pigments again.</description></item><item><title>Desserter Debuff</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/desserter-debuff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/desserter-debuff/</guid><description>At the end of March I was thrilled to be taking a trip to Toronto/Montréal because it meant I’d have the chance to meet lots of great WoW people I’d gotten to know online. When I looked for “Things To Do in Toronto” I found a listing for a cupcake decorating class, and that was just icing on the cake. I was thrilled when Serrinne, Kaleri and Jasyla agreed to go with me.</description></item><item><title>Rested Experience</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/rested-experience/</guid><description>Well, it finally happened: Vid’s drawing arm fell off. Like, literally, just sketching away and plop! it’s a scene right out of the Undercity. It’s all good though, she’s out talking to Mekkatorque right now about a steam-powered mechanical replacement. She says it’s no big deal, but as a veteran engineer, I remain skeptical.
But joking aside, the unfortunate reality is we’re starting to feel a bit of burnout, and there’s been some real-life commitments that are rearing their unavoidable and time-consuming heads.</description></item><item><title>Sated</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/sated/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 10:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/sated/</guid><description>Whoa, whoa, where did 2013 come from? It totally snuck up and [Ambushed] us when we weren’t expecting it. We’ve both been a little busy the last few days with RL travel, festivities and the ever pleasant-but-emotionally-draining family visits, but we’ll be back on pace next week with new stuff!
Also, I don’t know if we’ve ever mentioned this, but we’re always open to ideas and suggestions! Many of our strips are inspired by actual conversations or experiences we’ve had in-game, so if you come across something that you think we absolutely should know about, let us know in a comment, or tweet us at @fromdraenor!</description></item><item><title>Unique-Equipped</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unique-equipped/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 09:17:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/unique-equipped/</guid><description>It really was at Velen’s Book Club.
If you’ve been reading FDWL regularly since around May, you might remember this comic about Millya’s lost tail ring. Inspired by an unfortunate true story, it was around that time that I realized I had lost my wedding rings. We looked everywhere for them, upended everything, and ultimately concluded that they were lost forever. (A process that involved no small amount of hand-wringing and angst, I’ll admit).</description></item><item><title>WTB Real-life Alter Time</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wtb-real-life-alter-time/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 09:42:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wtb-real-life-alter-time/</guid><description>Please accept this pseudo-comic along with my apologies for this week. Last Friday we went to a concert! It was great and we had a great time. But the guy sitting next to Voss was coughing the entire time almost nonstop.
Voss told me darkly as we left, “I sure hope I didn’t catch germs from whatever was making that guy cough up his lung.”
Unfortunately, we both did. I’ll spare you the gory details except to say that I can’t remember having a cold that floored me like this one, ever.</description></item><item><title>Ring of Lost</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ring-of-lost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 08:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ring-of-lost/</guid><description>Ever wonder if WoW characters have the same day-to-day problems that plague us in real life? In this case, Vid had a minor crisis this week regarding a lost wedding ring, which sounds a lot like a quest, only there’s no handy directional guide in real life, and no reward other than a tremendous sense of relief.
Anyway, we thought that, you know, for the amount of travel and continent-hopping the average WoW hero does, remembering where you put something down must be a tremendous hassle.</description></item><item><title>The Lord of Terror</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-lord-of-terror/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-lord-of-terror/</guid><description>Like everyone else on the planet, we’ve sunk some time into Diablo III so far, and it’s a blast. So far I’m greatly enjoying the Wizard (LASER FREEZE RAY) and the Demon Hunter is also a lot of fun. I’ve played around with the Monk a bit, but I don’t think I enjoy the melee playstyle. I’ll stick with my blasters.
Vid, of course, is playing a Wizard. Shocking, I know!</description></item><item><title>Our Poor, Tired Feet</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-poor-tired-feet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 05:19:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/our-poor-tired-feet/</guid><description>The Calgary Expo was on the weekend, and, well, it was an…interesting experience.
There was waiting. There were photos with Patrick Stewart and autographs from Wil Wheaton. There was more waiting. There was the chance to meet Fyreuni of Daily Quests.
Oh, and there was a near-riot when the Expo shut the doors because they had oversold and weren’t letting in any more attendees, regardless of pre-purchased tickets, “we have a scheduled photoshoot with Patrick Stewart”, or “I just stepped outside for a smoke and my family is still inside!</description></item><item><title>Choose Wisely</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choose-wisely/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/choose-wisely/</guid><description>Yes, we know Droids and Hutts are not actually available player races in SWTOR. Too bad – I would totally be a Hutt so I could use awful HUTT YOUR MOUTH and HUTT UP puns and make everyone hate me.
Also, I wish I could say we were joking when talking about Vid’s overpowering love for anyone blue. Let’s just say that panel 4 isn’t entirely off the mark. 😉</description></item><item><title>For Science, You Monster</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/for-science-you-monster/</guid><description>Hey guys, Vid’s been crit by real life this week, so send her warm thoughts because until she’s back, you’re stuck with my terrible WoW Model Viewer comics!
Last night Blizzard released an updated Mists of Pandaria talent calculator, complete with new baseline talents. One of the new baseline Warlock talents was Demonic Portal, as pictured above. Needless to say, the Portal comparisons were instant and furious! So I figured it was an appropriate time to break out ye old Undercity Companion Cube image from this year’s Love is in the Air seasonal event.</description></item></channel></rss>