<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter 6: Anger on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-6-anger/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter 6: Anger on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 09:53:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-6-anger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 6</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-6/</guid><description>That does it for Chapter 6. One more to go!
It’s funny, but it’s looking like FDWL might possibly span the entire length of Warlords of Draenor. While it’s definitely not something we planned (FDWL actually started a few weeks before the Warlords announcement) it’s rather appropriate!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 5</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-5/</guid><description>Everyone knows the unspoken rules of pun battles! You should know better, Vid!
Oh, and if you don’t remember what that thing is that hit the sphere, here’s a reminder. Can’t really blame you if you’ve forgotten — that was a year and a half ago, holy crap!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 4</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-4/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 3</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-3/</guid><description>Welp, I sure hope Vid got insurance, because those Golems are not cheap!
It’s a little strange hearing all the news about the Legion alpha going on, when we’re still exploring the storyline of Mists here. Hopefully anyone reading this hasn’t forgotten about everything that happened back on Pandaria!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 11:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-2/</guid><description>And in this moment, Vid was reminded that Kura and Rades are siblings, after all…
Thanks for your patience, everyone! Right back into the action! As always, your comments and feedback is appreciated, or you can find us on Twitter!</description></item><item><title>Terokkar Tussle, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/terokkar-tussle-part-1/</guid><description>FIGHT! FIGHT! FIGHT!
(Okay, the Sky Golem doesn’t technically have combat capabilities in-game. But it SHOULD. Look at those claws!)</description></item><item><title>Reunion</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reunion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 10:31:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/reunion/</guid><description>It’s been a long time since Rades and Vid have seen each other – 42 pages, actually! That’s half the comic!!</description></item><item><title>Logistics</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/logistics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/logistics/</guid><description>Engineers: Life’s finest problem-solvers!</description></item><item><title>Faith</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/faith/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/faith/</guid><description>And we’re finally back to the rest of the cast. 😀 It’s been a while since we’ve seen them!</description></item><item><title>Almost</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/almost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 09:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/almost/</guid><description>Well, at least now Vid won’t have to feel bad about the Mechano-Hog getting destroyed.
Speaking of, the real Vid sure was happy when she saw the script for this page, and realized she wouldn’t have to draw the motorcycles anymore! Which just means I suppose I’ll have to give her something MORE complicated to draw now…</description></item><item><title>Results</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/results/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/results/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Exit Strategy</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/exit-strategy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 09:37:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/exit-strategy/</guid><description>A few people were asking what Rades was pouring out of that bag back on Page #80 — I told you it’d be explained! Granted, maybe he originally intended to use it just as a distraction, but I think it still served its purpose. (We also love seeing your comments trying to predict things that haven’t been revealed or explained yet in the story — we always get a kick when you guess right!</description></item><item><title>Command</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/command/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/command/</guid><description/></item><item><title>We Always Hurt The Ones We Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/we-always-hurt-the-ones-we-love/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/we-always-hurt-the-ones-we-love/</guid><description>I guess Rades shouldn’t have turned such a blind eye to his sister’s behavior all those years ago.</description></item><item><title>Helping</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/helping/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/helping/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Stealth Mission</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stealth-mission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 09:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/stealth-mission/</guid><description>First of all, curse you Blizzard for already using the funny joke!
I’ve always imagined Rades (the character) as more of a scout than a straight-up soldier, so it stands to reason he might be pretty sneaky. Not sneaky enough though, it seems…</description></item><item><title>Found</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/found/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/found/</guid><description>Annnnd we’re back! It’s been a great month off for us to get our batteries recharged, and we can’t wait to finish this story! It’s been a long undertaking, perhaps longer than either Vid or I initially realized, but we’re confident that in the end it’ll be one we can look back on proudly.
Now that Warlords’ story has mostly been told, we can breathe a slight sigh of relief, as there was always the slight worry that some of the lore events might overlap or clash with what we had in mind with FDWL.</description></item><item><title>A Little Patience</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-little-patience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 09:36:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-little-patience/</guid><description>Poor Vid. It looks like she’ll be waiting awhile longer. Actually, you’ll have to wait along with her a bit too because we are taking a vacation for the month of July!
For many personal reasons, this year has been exhausting. I’m proud we were able to maintain our schedule throughout it, but I’m going on vacation in July and getting ahead on as many comics as we would’ve needed just wasn’t feasible.</description></item><item><title>Orcient History</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/orcient-history/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/orcient-history/</guid><description>Aw yeah, going back to some old TBC lore! If you never quested through Nagrand as Horde, here’s a few links:
http://wow.gamepedia.com/Jorin_Deadeye
http://wow.gamepedia.com/Garrosh_Hellscream</description></item><item><title>Kura</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kura/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 09:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/kura/</guid><description>I think one of our favorite things is designing new characters. Sure, it takes us forever because we usually have vastly different ideas about attire and equipment, and then naming them takes even longer as we toss ideas back and forth and examine existing naming conventions. But EVENTUALLY they get completed and then we can love them. 😀</description></item><item><title>Speechless</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/speechless/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/speechless/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Chapter 6: Anger</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-six-anger/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-six-anger/</guid><description>Hmm, the title for this Chapter is sort of fitting, given the temperature of the WoW community right now regarding some things. Things that ultimately will not affect FDWL or its characters, however! After all, they’re on Outland. Everything’s cool there.</description></item></channel></rss>