<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>greatfather winter on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/greatfather-winter/</link><description>Recent content in greatfather winter on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 11:08:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/greatfather-winter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Here We Come A-Wakening</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/here-we-come-a-wakening/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 11:08:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/here-we-come-a-wakening/</guid><description>It’s that time of year again! Perhaps you recognize the new and improved Greatfather Winter from last year’s escapades?
I love everything about this strip, but particularly tiny adorable Rades and Vid hanging off of Kovok there. Look for these as our Twitter avatars for a while!
(You may also be amused that an in-depth discussion about Klaxxi anatomical features and the specific societal roles of Klaxxi of different body types preceded the completion of this comic.</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Four</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-four/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 12:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-four/</guid><description>I wasn’t actually sure how Rades intended to end our little odyssey. Needless to say, my jaw dropped when I got this far in the script. It’s great for him, though, because he gets to show his mad genius! Vid, who has no compunction about blasting a rocket straight into Ironforge or any other environs, is a little uneasy when it comes to FrankenWinter. But ultimately, she decides that it’s better to let a cyborg version of Greatfather Winter do all of the Winter’s Veil stuff – so that she and Rades don’t have to.</description></item><item><title>Winter Fail Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/winter-fail-part-two/</guid><description>The saga continues! Oh no, poor Greatfather Winter!
Vid did an awesome job with the expressions in this strip, I think you’ll all agree. I’m now using the “Sad Rades” face as my avatar, and I can’t even look at panel 3 without laughing.
There was some debate about which Greatfather Winter to use – the dwarven Alliance version, or the orcish Horde version! In the end though, we decided to go with the dwarf, to include more races.</description></item></channel></rss>