<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter 2: Doubt on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-2-doubt/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter 2: Doubt on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 04:05:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-2-doubt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Any Similarities are Purely Coincidental</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/any-similarities-are-purely-coincidental/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 04:05:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/any-similarities-are-purely-coincidental/</guid><description>I just want everyone to know that I combed the Auction House for weeks looking for Ethereum Prison Keys, for reference &amp;amp; accuracy. And they didn’t help at all.
So we came up with something new for the prison spheres, something that would make sense with their role in ethereal society, and with where we encounter them in Blade’s Edge and Netherstorm. And of course, something that may seem a little familiar.</description></item><item><title>The Exchange</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-exchange/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 02:15:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-exchange/</guid><description>You know what they say: Every ethereal has his price.
And remember, these Ethereum guys, they’re way out of date on their gemstones! Cardinal Rubies, Amberjewels, Lapis Lazulis, Queen’s Garnets, Primal Diamonds…we’re talking like, three whole expansions’ worth of exciting new jewels to covet! What self-respecting ethereal could resist such an offer? 😉
Next week will mark the end of Chapter 2! After that, we’ll be taking a short break for some RL vacations and script planning, but we’ll be back before you know it!</description></item><item><title>Old Friends</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/old-friends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 03:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/old-friends/</guid><description>Vid’s turn! 😉
For those unfamiliar with what Rades is talking about, he’s referring to the fact that Rexxar, Vol’jin and Chen are old war buddies. Years ago (in Warcraft III) they fought together, for Thrall’s Horde, against the then-leader of Theramore, Daelin Proudmoore (Jaina’s father), who hated the Horde and wanted to respark the Horde-Alliance war. Considering the situation and players involved in the Siege of Orgrimmar, it seems a bit of a similar situation.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Make a Deal</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/lets-make-a-deal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 02:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/lets-make-a-deal/</guid><description>Does anyone actually go back to Gezhe each month and get their monthly Membership Benefits? I don’t, and yet I feel like I almost should – the Outlands phase of leveling Jewelcrafting is always such a pain, since those gems are so scarce, and Golden Draenite is actually fairly valuable. And more importantly, I DID do all that work for the Consortium back in the day – I EARNED those gems!</description></item><item><title>Nagrand Slam</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nagrand-slam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 05:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/nagrand-slam/</guid><description>My favorite moment when crafting a story (such as in a D&amp;amp;D campaign) comes when finally, after months of straightforward, introductory play, all the setup stuff is complete. The plot hooks have been put into play, the important characters have been established, and the overarching story is just starting to pick up speed.
I’ve been extra excited about FDWL lately, because I think we’re at that step. Fun times ahead!</description></item><item><title>A Class-ic Mistake</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-class-ic-mistake/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 02:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/a-class-ic-mistake/</guid><description>We don’t use colour in our pages that often, but man, when we do, it’s sure a nice contrast with the black &amp;amp; white panels!
I don’t know about you, but I would totally craft a hot pink Sky Golem in-game and fly around in it.
This week’s page is actually canonical – it’s Vid’s birthday next week! The real Vid, I mean! So be sure to wish her well. To celebrate, she’s going out of town, so there won’t be an actual comic page next week.</description></item><item><title>Balance</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/balance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 03:45:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/balance/</guid><description>It of course goes without saying that this song was listened to by both Vid and I during the making of this strip, given the presence of a certain talking chandelier.
“Many lives were lost to bring you these tab collars.”</description></item><item><title>Teamwork</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/teamwork/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 02:08:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/teamwork/</guid><description>OLD DRAENEI
OLD DRAENEI WITH CANES
(CANE-EI)</description></item><item><title>City of Trite</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/city-of-trite/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 03:13:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/city-of-trite/</guid><description>I’d like to tell you that eventually mangling draenic phrases gets old, but I’d be lying. It’s one of my favorite things to do.
But it’s not just me! After reading the script, Vid told me she’s always liked the one that sounds like “buy your niece a car.”
I can’t wait until Warlords of Draenor where we’ll get even more expressions to abuse!</description></item><item><title>Random Encounter</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/random-encounter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 06:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/random-encounter/</guid><description>It’s the scene from the Chapter Title page, oooooh! Sharp-eyed readers may notice something telling on that page now, too. But what does it mean?? Time will tell.
One of the most interesting things about writing FDWL is discussing scenes, and realizing how the events in the comic are letting us establish little character traits about Vid &amp;amp; Rades. We had a good laugh when realizing what type of person Vid (the character) is when she’s on watch.</description></item><item><title>Memory Lane</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/memory-lane/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 02:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/memory-lane/</guid><description>After getting swamped last week and falling a bit behind schedule, Vid and I sat down this week and tossed some ideas around on how we could streamline the comic process a little. We realized that something that would help us out a great deal would be adopting a cleaner, more “inked” look. It’ll be a bit of a change from the pages so far, but I’ve always thought Vid’s art looked super sharp when in the inked-page step, so I’m actually really glad everyone is getting to see it now!</description></item><item><title>Symbols</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/symbols/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 03:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/symbols/</guid><description>Aw yiss, inventing us some headcanon draenei lore! Observant readers may remember that we alluded to these personal symbols back in Vid’s character profile.
If you look at official WoW artwork, there are TONS of different draenei sigils/symbols depicted. Why ARE they different? Do they represent different magical abilities? Or is it like we’ve described here, something biological, like an individual’s unique DNA footprint?
Personally, I think it’s a lot cooler to imagine those symbols as displays of personal identity rather than just to indicate “I’m using magic.</description></item><item><title>Hit M for Map</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/hit-m-for-map/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 02:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/hit-m-for-map/</guid><description>Where’s the TomTom addon when you need it?</description></item><item><title>Chapter Two: Doubt</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-two-doubt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 04:41:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-two-doubt/</guid><description>Happy New Year, everyone! On to chapter two!
I worried how recognizable Zangarmarsh would be in black &amp;amp; white, without those soft, tranquil shades of blue – but I suppose those giant mushrooms are pretty distinctive. I’ve always loved Zangarmarsh, it’s probably my favorite Burning Crusade zone. Not necessarily for the quests or anything – it’s just so soothing and calming visually.
Will that carry over for comic-Vid and Rades? I guess you’ll have to wait and find out!</description></item></channel></rss>