<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter 4: Hatred on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-4-hatred/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter 4: Hatred on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 09:46:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-4-hatred/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guest of Honour</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/guest-of-honour/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/guest-of-honour/</guid><description>That wraps up Chapter Four! What does Sablemane want with Wrathion? What’s going to happen to Rades? What happened to Four? At least Vid’s received some happy news…
Speaking of Wrathion, I sure am curious what we’ll see of him in Warlords. I believe his only appearance so far takes place “off-camera”, mentioned in Admiral Taylor’s Garrison Log, which doesn’t really tell us much. Clearly the Black Prince has SOMETHING in mind, SOME objective here on AU-Draenor.</description></item><item><title>DoT</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 09:39:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/dot/</guid><description>Rades, you should know better than to travel with such an injury! But then again I suppose your options were rather limited.
(Technically in-game Rades has maxed out First Aid, but let’s just assume that this type of wound is beyond the scope of a few bandages.)
Many thanks to our latest Daily Quests, one of our favorite WoW comics, and tremor3258! 😀</description></item><item><title>What Goes Up</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what-goes-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 10:07:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/what-goes-up/</guid><description>Poor Four. Brawler’s Guild just couldn’t really prepare her for what to do when hitchhiking on the back of an unwilling flying black dragon, I guess.
Now, if only she were an engineer, she’d be fine here! A parachute cloak, or a goblin glider, and she’d be laughing.
Sadly, Four is not an engineer.
In other business, thank you to Jasyla for being our latest Patreon supporter! &amp;lt;3</description></item><item><title>The Light Reveals, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-two/</guid><description>The funny thing about creating a weekly comic strip is that sometimes events take a little while to unfold. Though we’ve had this particular moment Patreon supporters will forgive me for not showing the sketch for this page a day early as usual – I didn’t want to spoil the final version!
If you want to be further emotionally devastated today, Unbroken is necessary reading. We used much of the physical description of the process of becoming Broken from this short story to help determine what our important character should look like.</description></item><item><title>The Light Reveals, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-light-reveals-part-one/</guid><description>I wonder if we’ll see any Broken this expansion. I know history has changed, and the orcs didn’t drink the blood of Mannoroth…but Gul’dan IS out there, green-skinned and demon-tainted. So there’s definitely fel magic on the table, albeit on a smaller scale – for now, at least. And judging from the questlines, you KNOW Gul’dan has some pretty significant plans of his own meant to further his own schemes, and probably those of the Legion, who clearly still have their eyes on Draenor…</description></item><item><title>Home Swamp Home</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/home-swamp-home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/home-swamp-home/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Be our guest</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/be-our-guest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/be-our-guest/</guid><description>What an expensive bit of therapy. The engineer in me is crying.
Hope everyone is enjoying Warlords so far! I know both Vid and I are LOVING all the new lore, familiar faces, and overall storyline. And GARRISONS! Oh my god, the garrisons. What more needs to be said. Now if you’ll excuse me, I think it’s almost time to send my followers out on today’s missions.</description></item><item><title>The one that got away</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-one-that-got-away/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 09:45:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-one-that-got-away/</guid><description>Funny story about panel 5 on this page – without meaning to, I had unconsciously modeled Four’s pose after Spider-Man comic I read twenty-four years ago. And then, after realizing this fact, I was able to identify, track down and download said comic to examine the angle of the pose. God bless the internet.
IT’S WARLORDS LAUNCH TOMORROW! If you’re taking the day off to enjoy it, make sure you have some snacks and drinks to keep you going!</description></item><item><title>More than you can chew</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/more-than-you-can-chew/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 09:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/more-than-you-can-chew/</guid><description>It’s like that Feist song.
It’s Blizzcon time! Last time Vid and I were stunned with the announcement that WoW was returning to Draenor – one might say “with love” – so it’ll be interesting to see what the big news and surprises are this time! It’s funny – when the news about Warlords of Draenor hit, we were actually a little alarmed, wondering if it was going to affect FDWL’s storyline.</description></item><item><title>Eyes on the Prize</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/eyes-on-the-prize/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/eyes-on-the-prize/</guid><description>Okay, this isn’t exactly how Flare works in-game, but Rades IS an engineer, after all.
This week’s patch notes were pretty funny, especially “Thrall received a reminder that he is currently still on Azeroth.” Of course, instead of talking like he was already on Draenor, Thrall now talks like he’s back in Orgrimmar as Horde Warchief. Oh, Thrall.
Vid got a Grand Expedition Yak this week, which means Transmog ANYWHERE, ANYTIME.</description></item><item><title>Righteous Defense</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/righteous-defense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/righteous-defense/</guid><description>Somewhere, Protection Paladins are crying in remembrance.</description></item><item><title>The Nose Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-nose-knows/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 09:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-nose-knows/</guid><description>When Vid &amp;amp; Rades were making their travel plans way back at the start of Chapter 2, there were some comments wondering about Sablemane and Wrathion. These queries continued when Sablemane actually showed up on page 25. Well, trust us, these two meeting and interacting has ALWAYS been one of the stories we’ve wanted to tell in FDWL. They’re such interesting personalities, with such great potential!
In other news, thanks to some very generous Patreon patrons, we’re looking to get our website looked at sometime soon!</description></item><item><title>Chapter Four: Hatred</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-four-hatred/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 09:58:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-four-hatred/</guid><description>And we’re back! What’s Sabellian here for? How is Rades doing? Why did the Broken stop? These answers and more, coming to a From Draenor near you!
We also have some other, exciting news – we’ve started a Patreon account!
Now don’t worry – From Draenor With Love will always remain free for your reading enjoyment. However, working on the comic does take us a lot of time each week, and we do have operating costs such as web hosting, brushes, inks, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>