<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter 3: Violence on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-3-violence/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter 3: Violence on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 10:07:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-3-violence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 4</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 10:07:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-4/</guid><description>document.createElement('audio'); /media/043.mp3
And that’s it for Chapter 3! &amp;gt;:D Things are getting real.
Today’s page also marks a special occasion for FDWL – it’s officially been one year since we started the story! We know this because it’s ALSO Siege of Orgrimmar’s one-year anniversary (which is…special…in its own way) and we specifically launched Chapter 1: Despair to coincide with the patch’s events.
It’s been an exciting year for FDWL, and I think we’ve definitely both learned a lot about the comic process, as well as simply what it takes to make a weekly webcomic work without killing each other.</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 3</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 09:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-3/</guid><description>document.createElement('audio'); /media/042_angryriver.mp3
One of the side benefits of being friends with WoW players who a) passionately roleplay draenei; b) hate orcs; c) all of the above, is that when it comes time to write a Broken character who has a huge hate-on for orcs, I have a huge selection of angry dialogue samples ready-made to pull from. 😉
(As for said Broken, he is of course referring back to the events of Page #18.</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-2/</guid><description>This week’s soundtrack:
(I don’t know that we’ll post a song for every page, but I figure if we have one that fits, we might as well!)
Ah, the Broken. You can’t really delve into draenei and orc lore without visiting them. If you’re unfamiliar with Broken lore, you should absolutely go read Micky Neilson’s short story Unbroken. It’s a fantastic read. Just be warned that our Broken, are not necessarily like Nobundo…</description></item><item><title>Darkness, My Old Friend, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 09:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/darkness-my-old-friend-part-1/</guid><description>WELP
Seems like Rades has worse luck than Vid, doesn’t it?</description></item><item><title>Employee Loyalty</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/employee-loyalty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 10:09:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/employee-loyalty/</guid><description>Hey, it’s back to familiar territory! Personally, Zangarmarsh is my favorite zone in Outlands. The colours and environment is just so peaceful and soothing.
Writing dialogue for Four can be tough, and I admit I struggled a bit with this page. She’s guarded, with a peculiar manner of speaking. This was a LOT for her to say. But I think it turned out well, and maybe explains a bit about her and just how she ended up with a Black Dragon for an employer.</description></item><item><title>Definitely Skull Level, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-2/</guid><description>Would-be rogues know what Rades is talking about.
With this (minor) delay out of the way, our party is able to make good time to the Dark Portal and reach Draenor. Shattrath is a few days away, so they settle down and make camp for the night…</description></item><item><title>Definitely Skull Level, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 09:16:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/definitely-skull-level-part-1/</guid><description>Is there anything more pitiful and/or annoying than running through a low level zone and accumulating a swarm of low-level grey mobs? It’s like, dudes, I’m just here to get some Goldthorn to level Alchemy, go away.
And then they DAZE YOU and DISMOUNT YOU and suddenly you’re knee-deep in a sea of blood and linen cloth.</description></item><item><title>Starring Ice Cube</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/starring-ice-cube/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 09:53:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/starring-ice-cube/</guid><description>Random trivia – this is the first FDWL strip (in the story arc format) that takes place on Azeroth!
(Which makes sense, I suppose. It’s not called From Azeroth With Love.)
On a similar note, it might seem a little odd that Rades &amp;amp; Vid have spent so much time in Pandaria as compared to Draenor, given our name. But this is about to change!</description></item><item><title>Ready Check</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ready-check/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 09:47:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/ready-check/</guid><description>If you don’t recognize Four’s “pet”, here’s a hint.
Confused about the strange hooked shape of Wrathion’s dagger? That’s a type of knife called a white-quality vendor-purchased weapon.
(This isn’t the one Wrathion has, of course. I doubt the Black Prince would be caught dead with an ordinary, mundane knife.)</description></item><item><title>When I asked if you had BG experience, I wasn’t talking about PVP</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/when-i-asked-if-you-had-bg-experience-i-wasnt-talking-about-pvp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 09:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/when-i-asked-if-you-had-bg-experience-i-wasnt-talking-about-pvp/</guid><description>Confession: We realize the Tushui Alliance lion isn’t technically the symbol of the Brawler’s Guild, but the Brawler’s guild doesn’t actually HAVE a symbol! We checked the arena, the shirts, the NPCs, nothing.
But you know what? Both Horde and Alliance began running their Brawler’s Guild at around the same time as the two Pandaren factions joined up, so maybe Aysa and Ji brought the tradition with them.
(Shhhh, just go with it.</description></item><item><title>Four’s Company</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fours-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 04:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/fours-company/</guid><description>Way, way back when we were planning out the FDWL plot, we knew that one of Wrathion’s bodyguards would become part of the story. Originally, I had penciled in Right, who – along with her partner, Left – can always be seen wherever their boss goes. I thought it would be fun to explore this cool, badass-looking woman, who despite numerous appearances in-game, never actually speaks or does anything.
But after talking it over with Vid, we realized that while it would be interesting to use Right, we had a great opportunity to create a brand new person instead!</description></item><item><title>Three’s Company</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/threes-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 04:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/threes-company/</guid><description>Hmm, who could that be up there in the balcony, listening in? Guess we’ll find out next week! 😀</description></item><item><title>The Ghost and the Darkness, Part 3</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 03:20:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-3/</guid><description>Standard hunter operating procedure 101!
Everything seems to be proceeding quite nicely according to plan, doesn’t it?</description></item><item><title>The Ghost and the Darkness, Part 2</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 02:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-2/</guid><description>HAMMER OF JUSTICE!</description></item><item><title>The Ghost and the Darkness, Part 1</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 04:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-ghost-and-the-darkness-part-1/</guid><description>And what shoulder, &amp;amp; what art.
Could twist the sinews of thy heart?
And when thy heart began to beat,
What dread hand? &amp;amp; what dread feet?
– The Tyger, William Blake
This just in: Sha really are incredibly weird, gross and ugly little buggers, when you stop and look at them closely.
They sure do match our color scheme though! 😉</description></item><item><title>Chapter Three: Violence</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-three-violence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 01:38:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-three-violence/</guid><description>And we’re back!
Just a reminder that even though War Crimes just came out, and Garrosh’s trial is what’s “currently” happening, FDWL takes place during the Siege of Orgrimmar timeframe.
As for whether this is directly relevant? Well, let’s just say we’ve both got the book and are pretty curious to see what all happens. 😉</description></item></channel></rss>