<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>guest strips on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/guest-strips/</link><description>Recent content in guest strips on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 10:26:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/guest-strips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wish You Were Here</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wish-you-were-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 10:26:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/wish-you-were-here/</guid><description>Today’s comic is a very special guest strip from our amazingly talented friend Walks! The Dread Wastes are so horrifically mutated and ugly (I personally think they feel like the Ghostlands, except on acid) and Walks totally nailed the vintage travel poster look. Thanks Walks! 😀
I think of all the factions in Mists, the Dread Wastes’ Klaxxi are my favorite. Well, okay, maybe the Tillers take the cake but that’s more because I AM ADDICTED TO CULTIVATING MY PRICELESS PRODUCE than any particular love for the faction itself.</description></item><item><title>Limit Break</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/limit-break/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 08:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/limit-break/</guid><description>This week’s strip is a guest strip from Ayms and Mits, who you may know from their great webcomic, Fourth Wall! They’re no longer doing new strips, but they heard we needed some help this week and came out of “retirement” to lend us a hand. Thanks guys! Fourth Wall isn’t online anymore, but you can find Ayms’ artwork at her sketchblog – do go check out her stuff!
We should be back on schedule this week, so thanks again to Dee, Ayms and Mits who really came through for us when we needed a hand.</description></item><item><title>There’s Something Different About You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/theres-something-different-about-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 08:31:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/theres-something-different-about-you/</guid><description>Today’s comic is a special guest strip by our WONDERFUL and TALENTED friend Dee, who came through AMAZINGLY, considering she had only like half a day’s notice! You can check out her WoW blog at @mainfloortank!
(She really, really likes elves.)
THANKS DEE! You really helped us out. Much love!
Unfortunately, the reason Vid couldn’t finish this week’s strip was due to a sudden family emergency. Send some good thoughts and wishes her way, as she and her family could really use them.</description></item></channel></rss>