<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter 1: Despair on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-1-despair/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter 1: Despair on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 04:50:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/chapters/chapter-1-despair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pieces</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pieces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 04:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/pieces/</guid><description>“…Why did you play that piece just now?”
“It’s a Pandaren board game. The object is for both players to win.”
“That’s ridiculous! Why would you even play!?”
That’s it for Chapter One! The groundwork is set, the plot points have been laid out. Now – rubs hands together eagerly – it’s time to have some fun.
We will be taking a short break before starting in on the next leg of the story, to allow for Christmas holidays and whatnot.</description></item><item><title>Where The Heart Is</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/where-the-heart-is/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 03:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/where-the-heart-is/</guid><description>Y’know, I asked Vid to do something special artistically for the middle two panels, and HOLY CRAP did she nail it! Those panels might be my favorite artwork in all of FDWL so far.
Next week will mark the end of our first chapter! (Will all chapters be the same length? We don’t know yet.) We hope you’ve been enjoying the story so far! Now that we’ve laid the groundwork, it’s time to get this show on the road!</description></item><item><title>Quest Accepted</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quest-accepted/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 04:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/quest-accepted/</guid><description>I always find it funny when our plot details are actually accurate/based off the real characters. For example, Rades the WoW toon really IS an honorary member of the Consortium, having reached Exalted status with them way, way back (I think I wanted the tabard? or maybe one of their engineering schematics). On the other hand, Vid never did the rep grind for them, and we’ll see this reflected later on in the comic.</description></item><item><title>Naar-who?</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/naar-who/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 02:14:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/naar-who/</guid><description>Look at us! Blizzcon week and not even missing a beat? YEAH! But seriously, Vid worked like a maniac to get a few strips done ahead of time, so she definitely earned the vacation time! It certainly wouldn’t have been the end of the world to have a filler strip or two, but we’re pretty pleased that we didn’t have to resort to that!
As for Blizzcon itself – WOW! Exciting stuff!</description></item><item><title>The Magic Word</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-magic-word/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 02:50:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-magic-word/</guid><description>It’s Blizzcon week! Hope everyone who’s attending the con or watching via Virtual Ticket has a great time! If you’re there, keep an eye out for Vid – she’ll be the one with a bunch of FDWL stickers and business cards! 😉</description></item><item><title>Awkward</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/awkward/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 02:39:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/awkward/</guid><description>One of the hazards in being an insatiably curious two-year-old dragon and knowing very little about history is not recognizing the kind of questions you simply do not ask in civilized company.
Some readers have asked us for a while now about Vid and Rades and their connection to Draenor, so here’s a few answers!</description></item><item><title>Attention Span</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/attention-span/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 02:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/attention-span/</guid><description>Something you should know about engineers: we’re constantly keeping an eye out for cliffs, staircases and towers to hurl ourselves from that we might use our gadgets to float safely to the ground in style.
Ask the engineer in your raid. They’ll verify this.</description></item><item><title>Oh, It’s You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/oh-its-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 02:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/oh-its-you/</guid><description>If you think about it, Wrathion probably IS pretty bothered by what happened to the Vale. It’s just a stone’s throw away from the Tavern in the Mists! That has to be horrible for property values.</description></item><item><title>It Probably Happens A Lot</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/it-probably-happens-a-lot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 15:32:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/it-probably-happens-a-lot/</guid><description>Hunters know what I’m talking about.
LOOKING AT YOU, KRUSH.</description></item><item><title>Not Again</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-again/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 09:12:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-again/</guid><description>Aw yeah, sticking to our own vaguely-established continuity! 😉</description></item><item><title>All Roads Lead to Orgrimmar</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/all-roads-lead-to-orgrimmar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 07:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/all-roads-lead-to-orgrimmar/</guid><description>DIALOGUE YAY
Oh Garrosh, look at all the trouble you’re causing.</description></item><item><title>Repercussions</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/repercussions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2013 14:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/repercussions/</guid><description>Starting to get underway! The impact of Garrosh’s actions in the Vale. Major events are about to be set in motion.
Apologies for the disarray of the site design right now. We updated the WordPress version and it broke everything, just like it ALWAYS DOES (seriously, it actually breaks every time we update) but thankfully the damage doesn’t seem TOO severe this time. Hopefully it shouldn’t be too long before we get everything back to how it should be.</description></item><item><title>Chapter One: Despair</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-one-despair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:06:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/chapter-one-despair/</guid><description>It’s an exciting day for From Draenor With Love! After nearly two years of making this comic, we felt we were ready to tackle some new challenges.
What does this mean? Our name is staying the same. The comic will still be about Rades and Vid. It will be an ongoing story from week to week. The format will be less static four-panel and more graphic novel. I also made some changes personally, going back to my roots a bit as it were to ink the comic by hand rather than entirely digitally.</description></item></channel></rss>