<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Garrosh on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/garrosh/</link><description>Recent content in Garrosh on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 07:49:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/garrosh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Siege of Orgrimmar</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-siege-of-orgrimmar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 07:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-siege-of-orgrimmar/</guid><description>Patch 5.4 is almost here! I’m totally pumped, but I’m also dreading it! I want to see the cool new raid content and bosses, but I don’t WANT to kill Nazgrim! I don’t WANT to kill the Paragons!
And I don’t want to kill Garrosh!
(He’s a major From Draenor With Love character, after all!)
Speaking of the comic, this strip marks an important milestone for us. Starting next week, everything is changing!</description></item><item><title>Whateverstone is More Like It</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whateverstone-is-more-like-it/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 12:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/whateverstone-is-more-like-it/</guid><description>I’m not sure I know of a character in any book, movie or game who has had their personality and history thrown to the wayside and trampled into the dust as much as Garrosh has this expansion. I mean, in Cataclysm he certainly wasn’t perfect, but he had distinct good points to accompany his flaws, was a good character foil for his mirror image, Varian, and was showing definite signs of growth from his hotheaded, annoying days of being a mad dog yipping at Thrall during Wrath.</description></item><item><title>The Proudmoore “Problem”</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:35:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-proudmoore-problem/</guid><description>A lot of people think Jaina has this terrible reputation regarding the men in her life, that she has “terrible taste in men”, or that she breaks guys’ hearts and/or makes them go crazy. This is utter nonsense. The problem isn’t with Jaina, the problem is that the men in her life are just plain jerks.
Have you actually LISTENED to the crap these guys say? It’s pretty sad when Garrosh of all people has treated her with more dignity and respect than her so-called close friends.</description></item><item><title>iWrynny</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/iwrynny/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 08:48:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/iwrynny/</guid><description>Somewhere out there in Pandaria, there’s an armorsmith with one twisted sense of humor.
Poor clueless little Anduin. Hands up if you saw him step onto that platform covered in Sha magic and walk right up to Garrosh, and thought to yourself “welp, I have a bad feeling about how this is going to turn out.” AND SURE ENOUGH.
Should have listened to Dezco, kid. Even if he does wear babies as armor.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 12:23:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-part-two/</guid><description>The inevitable result of last week’s devious scheme.
(Really, this moment was so amazing, how could we NOT give it the full-comic spotlight it deserves??)
You know, in-game Garrosh is unpleasant and thoroughly unlikeable, and Blizzard is going to great lengths to portray him as an absolute monster. But I’m a big fan of THIS Garrosh, the one who isn’t concerned about world domination or wiping cities off the map, but just sticking it to Varian and being a general pain in the ass.</description></item><item><title>You Know He Would, Too</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-too/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 08:49:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/you-know-he-would-too/</guid><description>Still the highlight of the expansion so far, in my opinion.
Let’s be honest. How many of us re-did this quest, over and over again, just to repeatedly wallop Varian in his giant chin? Who could possibly resist??
Headcanon: Garrosh sitting down in his throne room with a paper and clipboard.
On the left-hand side of the page: Strong new allies. Much-needed boost to the Horde’s ranks. New culture and knowledge that will strengthen the Horde.</description></item><item><title>Surprisingly Often, Actually</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 10:44:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/surprisingly-often-actually/</guid><description>From Draenor With Love launched November 1, 2011, which means it’s been an entire year! 😀 I am pretty pleased that we put out a comic each and every week, even when life kicked us around a bit, or when one of us was traveling. Thanks to everyone who’s read our stuff over the past year! We appreciate your visits, your comments, your retweets, all of it!
Also, a special thanks to Dee, Ayms/Mits, and Walks, who gave us awesome guest strips!</description></item><item><title>Priorities</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 10:21:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/priorities/</guid><description>This is actually a true story. On launch night, we were a few hours in and realized that our Legendary-toting Boomkin was sitting in the Barrens somewhere fishing up Tasty Crapfish and Garbage Trout trying to get realm-first fishing, two of us were hanging out in starter zones furiously battling and taming new pets, and our infamous guild AH tycoon was expanding his financial empire with lucrative Pandaria ore/herb sales.</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part Two</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 09:34:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-two/</guid><description>HEY MURADIN PUT A BIRD ON IT
Like we said last week…Warrior glyphs in Mists = THE COOLEST.
Some news about the next few weeks! This weekend, we’ll be attending a Comic Expo in Calgary! Excitement! Our strip next week will be something based off the Expo, we hope. Then, the week after that we plan on presenting the special guest strip for Great Blog Noblegarden Egg Hunt! So keep your eyes peeled!</description></item><item><title>The Art of War, Part One</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/the-art-of-war-part-one/</guid><description>A Glyph that causes a lightning strike?
…I have a sudden urge to play a warrior in Mists.
Seriously though, it’s terrific that Blizzard is giving us all these new fun cosmetic glyphs. They’re little touches, but damn are they cool.
My personal favorite so far? That would be Glyph of the Geist. BECAUSE GEISTS ARE AWESOME.
(In other news, I think Vid is going to revolt if I make her draw Garrosh again.</description></item><item><title>Not Who We Expected</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-who-we-expected/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 12:18:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/not-who-we-expected/</guid><description>As everyone knows by now, Garrosh Hellscream will be the boss of Mists of Pandaria’s final content patch, and we take him down in an exciting-sounding “Siege of Orgrimmar.”
Now, there’s a lot of time between now and then, but I have to say…given what we’ve seen of Sylvanas in Cataclysm – being quite dastardly towards the Worgen during their starting zone, raising unwilling humans into new Forsaken and conscripting them into her forces, and her cold and callous treatment towards Koltira – I really expected her to be the Horde leader we’d end up killing as a raid boss.</description></item><item><title>Your Racial Leader is Thinking About You</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-racial-leader-is-thinking-about-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2012 09:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/your-racial-leader-is-thinking-about-you/</guid><description>It occurred to Vid and I yesterday that perhaps we should have saved the comic with the NAKED ORC for our Valentine’s Day update. Apparently we are unable to read calendars.
We figured we needed to do SOMETHING love-themed for this week – after all, the comic IS From Draenor With LOVE!
Well, who better to feature on our special Valentine’s Day card than another local from Draenor, the Warchief himself!</description></item></channel></rss>