<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tyrande on From Draenor With Love</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/tyrande/</link><description>Recent content in Tyrande on From Draenor With Love</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fromdraenor.ca/tags/tyrande/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>He Knows</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 17:46:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/he-knows/</guid><description>Hey, he IS a Prophet, after all. Also, I just need to point this out while Rades is gone: Orcs are currently on the very naughty list.
But the idea of Velen as Greatfather Winter and the faction leaders as little kids was actually all Rades’, so you can’t accuse me of bias in this case. We agreed that it even makes sense, when you think about it – to a draenei who is thousands of years old maybe the rest of us would seem like children.</description></item><item><title>Resurrection Sickness</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2012 11:11:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/resurrection-sickness/</guid><description>Everyone’s been buzzing about the new &amp;amp; improved Scroll of Resurrection, and why not? A free level 80, realm transfer AND faction transfer? Just for coming back to the game? Yeah, it’s no wonder the new Scroll offer has been so popular.
Of course, we all know what’s REALLY behind the Scroll frenzy.
SPECTRAL MOUNTS.
Awww yeah. That’s the kind of incentive that gets RESULTS.
PS: Did you know Stormwind really does have a War Room?</description></item><item><title>Maximum Cupacity</title><link>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/maximum-cupacity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2012 10:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://fromdraenor.ca/comic/maximum-cupacity/</guid><description>I really, really wish we had ampm stores in Canada. I would totally buy those cups! The art on them looks great, and they’d be nice collectibles to own.
The three “rejected” cup ideas we came up with for this strip should all be sadly familiar to most WoW players. I don’t think anyone will EVER forget Sindragosa’s famous line, and Neptulon’s PUUUURE WATERRRR line from Throne of the Tides has quickly become a fan favorite.</description></item></channel></rss>